[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: オオカミさんと七人の仲間たち 11
Original Script: HKG&CASO
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H32AA5500,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,2,2,30,30,5,1
Style: kuroko,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H322855B0,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,2,8,30,30,8,1
Style: OPJP,FOT-PopJoy Std B,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H016A5BE2,&H013F3F3F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,2,2,15,15,10,1
Style: OPCH,方正少儿_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H016A5BE2,&H012F2F2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,2,8,15,15,10,1
Style: EDJP,FOT-PopJoy Std B,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H016A5BE2,&H013F3F3F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,2,2,15,15,8,1
Style: EDCH,方正少儿_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H016A5BE2,&H012F2F2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,2,8,15,15,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.33,0:00:04.00,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久很久以前...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.42,0:00:07.32,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是上回故事的后续
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.01,0:00:10.34,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士在和猫先生一起修行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.84,0:00:12.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着上啊亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.16,0:00:13.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.09,0:00:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.99,0:00:20.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:22.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  凉子她?!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.60,0:00:27.15,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  我们继续讲述御伽银行最大的危机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.30,0:00:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}大神与披着羊皮的狼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.96,0:00:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  你醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.56,0:00:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽狐你...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起喔  都是士狼他非要我把你带到这儿来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.31,0:00:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羡慕你啊  有人这么爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.50,0:01:00.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都有点嫉妒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.42,0:01:04.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽狐  别对她动粗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.00,0:01:09.89,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼之岛高中学生会会长  羊饲士狼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.35,0:01:16.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  我现在不会对你出手的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.07,0:01:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.68,0:01:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢看别人遭遇不幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.84,0:01:24.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想着抓你的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.64,0:01:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便把御伽银行的人也牵扯进来的话肯定有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.13,0:01:31.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过真没想到进展如此顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.98,0:01:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.16,0:01:35.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就只等森野上门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.96,0:01:37.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好戏这才要开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.43,0:01:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来整理一下目前的状况吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.94,0:01:44.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进行了多方调查
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.44,0:01:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来可以断定是羊饲在幕后一手策划的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.29,0:01:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们完全中了对方的圈套
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.32,0:01:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也因此攒下了不少的人情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.87,0:01:59.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的同伴很有可能分别被抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.40,0:02:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来考虑作战计划吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.87,0:02:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋  给老子站住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.76,0:02:13.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是死胡同
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.98,0:02:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.81,0:02:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的逃到哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.20,0:02:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  去那边找
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.79,0:02:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像走了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.73,0:02:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.60,0:02:35.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪我...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.99,0:02:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪我轻易相信了她的花言巧语
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.18,0:02:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以后一定会偿还...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.14,0:02:43.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.11,0:02:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你这么老实的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.67,0:02:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  「原来」这词很多余诶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.41,0:02:51.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.05,0:03:02.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神真的在鬼之岛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.18,0:03:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故意引我上钩也是羊饲绑架凉子的目的之一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.89,0:03:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他肯定在我知道的地方等着我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.67,0:03:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.39,0:03:17.04,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浦岛被飞仔们带到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.20,0:03:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.35,0:03:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乙姬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.95,0:03:22.39,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎乙姬安然无恙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.73,0:03:24.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们活腻味了是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.04,0:03:27.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啧啧  你的对手可不是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.61,0:03:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浦岛～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.47,0:03:33.95,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意料之外的伏兵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.91,0:03:38.49,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是位于城郊的废弃工厂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.22,0:03:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下你逃不掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.27,0:03:43.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了这条心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.61,0:03:45.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑嘛～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.30,0:03:54.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换上这个吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.93,0:03:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女仆小姐!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.86,0:04:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居  居然...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.02,0:04:06.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然要女仆去穿护士服!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.76,0:04:07.85,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某种意义上通正在面临危机
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.09,0:04:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浦岛～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.81,0:04:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起玩嘛～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.88,0:04:14.71,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比平时更加色相毕露的浦岛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.12,0:04:17.00,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有半点危机感
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.54,0:04:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位美女真是靓啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.85,0:04:19.82,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他的好感度直跌谷底
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.42,0:04:21.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎大人...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.53,0:04:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不能得到太郎大人的宠爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.32,0:04:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我活着还有何意义
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.00,0:04:32.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索性...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:36.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但果然最美的还是你  乙姬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:39.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  让你受惊了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.07,0:04:40.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,My Honey
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.57,0:04:42.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.59,0:04:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是最好女色吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.50,0:04:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干了他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.33,0:04:54.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.79,0:04:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此我也不能输
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.42,0:05:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人的嫉妒可是深过大海
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.01,0:05:06.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你们觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.31,0:05:11.78,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来乙姬也是招惹不得的角色之一啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.10,0:05:17.78,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这边正面临大危机的通
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.25,0:05:22.74,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道真的要就此舍弃女仆之身吗?!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.54,0:05:21.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就乖乖地从了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.81,0:05:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.20,0:05:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.92,0:05:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要告诉你们这些杂碎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.70,0:05:38.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.14,0:05:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我逃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.09,0:05:48.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.63,0:05:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿这个哟～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.00,0:05:57.07,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔女你也好这口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.01,0:05:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎  怎么会这样...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.34,0:06:02.17,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来通的危机还在继续
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.97,0:06:06.48,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而另一方面  爱丽丝和宇佐见仍处于危机之中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.23,0:06:08.80,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于爱丽丝是足不出户的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.82,0:06:10.59,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是不擅长跑步
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.43,0:06:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  站起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.36,0:06:13.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脚...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.94,0:06:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.56,0:06:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就老实地给我睡着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.54,0:06:35.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.61,0:06:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  慢死了啦李李
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.24,0:06:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,李李?!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.24,0:06:39.35,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,李李?!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.66,0:06:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行长你来得太晚啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.56,0:06:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.01,0:06:48.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事前准备费了不少工夫嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.33,0:06:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟在追你们的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.53,0:06:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把这些飞仔一个一个地干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.16,0:06:54.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一暴露了就前功尽弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.43,0:06:57.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那其他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.13,0:07:01.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在各自行动  不过...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.45,0:07:06.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最棘手的是森野他们那组啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.68,0:07:11.06,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后半终于要杀入敌人的老巢了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.96,0:07:21.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么做  别想轻易收场
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.70,0:07:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.32,0:07:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要看着你们一个一个溃败不堪就足够有意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.27,0:07:39.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就满心期待然后饱尝被背叛的滋味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.37,0:07:44.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来终于出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.69,0:07:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的王子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.56,0:07:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数可真不少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.13,0:08:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是等行长他们来了再...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.68,0:08:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.97,0:08:04.21,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这风情的声音是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.52,0:08:08.48,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃学姐和她的仆人们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.69,0:08:10.39,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然连豚田三兄弟也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.90,0:08:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家怎么都来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.26,0:08:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为之前的7折优惠欠了你们不少人情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.45,0:08:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也会助你们一臂之力噗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.67,0:08:19.56,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢到死的语尾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.60,0:08:20.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来还人情了噗嗤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.62,0:08:21.32,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢到死的语尾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.33,0:08:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.40,0:08:23.57,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老三很普通
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.72,0:08:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小桃所指之处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.28,0:08:27.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是上刀山  下火海
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.36,0:08:29.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为报黍米团子之恩  在所不辞
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.33,0:08:33.53,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的黍米团子  就是那个吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.63,0:08:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越有意思了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.66,0:08:36.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.58,0:08:37.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然瞧不起我们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.64,0:08:38.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.88,0:08:43.11,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打了7折的人情此刻派上了用场
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.90,0:08:46.06,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说行长早就预见到这一点?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.19,0:08:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门要关上了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.59,0:09:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就交给我们噗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.58,0:09:06.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们快点进去噗嗤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.18,0:09:08.74,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本热血的台词全被语尾废掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.78,0:09:10.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森野  快去救大神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.68,0:09:11.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.24,0:09:14.23,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然老三很普通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.34,0:09:18.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给老子站住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.59,0:09:22.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这身肥肉是什么做的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.98,0:09:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.09,0:09:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们久等了  豚田三兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.17,0:09:30.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  鬼之岛的飞仔们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.25,0:09:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来做你们的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.09,0:09:37.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.37,0:09:40.91,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处于绅士模式的浦岛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.77,0:09:44.91,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来那之后又被乙姬狠狠地吸榨了一番啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.57,0:09:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种打打杀杀的  我可做不来呀...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.97,0:10:05.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.65,0:10:12.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐见...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.65,0:10:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别误会喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.24,0:10:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过因为现在和你们是同一条船上的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.52,0:10:18.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才救你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.57,0:10:20.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.54,0:10:27.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊  我的仆人们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.32,0:10:29.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.22,0:10:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.87,0:10:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿亮  大神就拜托给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.56,0:10:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.11,0:10:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.15,0:10:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前问过我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.41,0:10:48.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要你修行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.52,0:10:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.11,0:10:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年前  我抛下了一个女孩自己逃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.60,0:10:59.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明她想要从一群飞仔手中救出我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.30,0:11:02.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然没有人性地抛下了她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.14,0:11:09.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不配做人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.91,0:11:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至曾经想过不如一死了之
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.25,0:11:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那么做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.42,0:11:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加对不起挺身救我的那个女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.51,0:11:18.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.72,0:11:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少要不断磨练自己  变得强大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.92,0:11:23.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做个能帮助他人的人渣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.90,0:11:25.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此历经了无数的修行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.22,0:11:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.39,0:11:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.52,0:11:33.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从心底里敬佩你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.81,0:11:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉子...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.89,0:11:51.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.31,0:11:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.13,0:11:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御伽学园高中部三年级生  猫宫参上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.76,0:12:00.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼之岛的恶鬼们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.21,0:12:04.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我把你们打个片甲不喵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.09,0:12:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...不留!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.27,0:12:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.55,0:12:14.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能保护大神的只有你一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.78,0:12:15.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.49,0:12:22.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:25.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.93,0:12:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害我等好久啊森野
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.99,0:12:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我预想的晚了那么一点点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.94,0:12:33.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊饲!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.42,0:12:37.28,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士完全失去了冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.12,0:12:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.31,0:12:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这时候还用射击武器
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好卑鄙啊森野
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.28,0:12:54.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了凉子你能努力到什么程度
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.26,0:12:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真叫人拭目以待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.76,0:12:57.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会不惜一切全力以赴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.79,0:13:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是为了凉子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.61,0:13:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真叫人期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.07,0:13:16.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.41,0:13:18.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.59,0:13:21.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在心爱的女人面前被人虐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.12,0:13:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很狼狈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.57,0:13:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉...子...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.57,0:13:30.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从心底里敬佩你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.87,0:13:33.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有做逃兵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.96,0:13:35.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是在被飞仔们包围的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.89,0:13:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是和大神一起杀入鬼之岛的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.60,0:13:41.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你察觉到大神的柔弱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.29,0:13:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在背后默默地支撑着她
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.08,0:13:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我这个逃兵不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.62,0:13:48.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说那个女孩是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.89,0:13:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是大神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.00,0:13:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是以前的你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.22,0:13:55.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是没办法保护好大神的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.81,0:13:57.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才帮助你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.80,0:14:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士  你是为什么想要保护大神
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.35,0:14:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.75,0:14:07.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份情感会让你无比强大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.18,0:14:11.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份情感会成为你保护大神的力量之源泉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.16,0:14:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.66,0:14:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要保护好大神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.82,0:14:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  老子还没玩够啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.95,0:14:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.17,0:14:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.23,0:14:34.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要保护凉子!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.05,0:14:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.39,0:14:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉搏时最重要的就是要保持冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.24,0:14:43.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须要有冷静的头脑去应对战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.90,0:15:22.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把老子打伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.51,0:15:28.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你不想活了是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.19,0:15:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.22,0:15:36.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.25,0:15:37.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林檎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:42.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被你狠狠地摆了一道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.46,0:15:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会对你采取相应的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.44,0:15:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吓唬我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.66,0:15:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堂堂御伽银行行长  居然意欲借大人之力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.79,0:15:53.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人失望
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.30,0:15:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人之力?  少在那里胡说八道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.82,0:16:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是对御伽银行的挑衅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.82,0:16:02.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会全力反击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.42,0:16:04.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好心理准备吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.94,0:16:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那么就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.22,0:16:11.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.57,0:16:14.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.17,0:16:31.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～真令人失望啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.79,0:16:35.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明人家费心做了那么多准备
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.28,0:16:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当那两个人的羁绊变得更深
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.44,0:16:41.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到互相离不开对方的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.01,0:16:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再把他们活生生地撕裂开来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.72,0:16:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尝起来才更加可口吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.54,0:16:53.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的辛苦大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.03,0:16:57.43,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由行长代表御伽银行发表慰问
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.26,0:16:56.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位能助阵  真的帮了我们很大的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.74,0:16:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢大家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.23,0:16:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  抱歉给你们添了不少麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.49,0:17:02.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好道歉的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.12,0:17:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总会有独自一个人无法办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也正因为如此才有我们御伽银行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.47,0:17:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的宗旨就是「互相帮助」嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.41,0:17:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天解散
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.49,0:17:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.02,0:17:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.43,0:17:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐见  谢谢你今天在危机中救了我的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.09,0:17:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是我先惹下的麻烦  算是赔罪啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.06,0:17:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的事是我不好  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.26,0:17:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候我总是撒气在你头上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.55,0:17:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可那都是不对的  真的很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.52,0:17:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.98,0:17:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是  学园小姐选美比赛的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.50,0:18:01.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你留下了不愉快的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.45,0:18:03.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.68,0:18:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就扯平咯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.86,0:18:11.91,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这两个人终于成了好朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.63,0:18:17.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的帮了我们很大的忙  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.83,0:18:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦  不用谢  不用
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.42,0:18:23.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说不过是饭后运动罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.05,0:18:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫宫学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.46,0:18:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.29,0:18:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.94,0:18:37.03,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太好啦  猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.84,0:18:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就跑步回家咯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.45,0:18:42.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.40,0:18:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.19,0:18:43.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.12,0:18:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.41,0:18:50.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶  亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.89,0:18:53.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次  我没有做逃兵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.75,0:18:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.26,0:19:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森野今天也是大显身手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.51,0:19:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里  都多亏猫先生和大家的帮助啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.12,0:19:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给森野一些奖励怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.31,0:19:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用毛茸茸的狗耳朵和尾巴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.15,0:19:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹭过去向他撒娇怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.40,0:19:25.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁有那些鬼东西啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.16,0:19:29.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就穿可爱的内衣向他进攻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.21,0:19:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.20,0:19:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那泳衣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.87,0:19:32.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.99,0:19:34.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花边连衣裙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.77,0:19:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我穿那种不好看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.30,0:19:39.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有的事  凉子穿什么都好看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.98,0:19:40.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.69,0:19:41.69,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人组和往常一样  开开心心地一起回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.60,0:19:50.94,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}甘い罠につられ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.62,0:19:56.08,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}胸の扉あけちゃいけないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.25,0:19:59.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ついて行っちゃだめさ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.87,0:20:03.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君はだんとつだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.78,0:20:08.35,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そうさ仲間内じゃ最高さ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.75,0:20:11.47,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰にもゆずれない
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.91,0:20:18.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}抜けがけはタブーと決めてるけれど
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.72,0:20:25.42,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰も約束を守れないよ　No No No
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.43,0:20:28.27,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}赤頭巾ちゃん御用心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.44,0:20:34.26,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}用心しなけりゃだめさ狼が牙とぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.36,0:20:37.56,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねらいを定めているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.59,0:20:40.58,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}赤頭巾ちゃん御用心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.72,0:20:45.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕が守ってあげるよ　命がけ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.15,0:20:50.97,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからさおねがい　ハートをください。
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.15,0:20:54.22,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからさ　かわりに
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.29,0:20:58.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}おねがいハートをください
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.76,0:21:01.85,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからさ　かわりに
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.93,0:21:07.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}おねがいハートをください....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.60,0:19:50.94,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}注意甜蜜陷阱的诱惑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.62,0:19:56.08,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不要轻易打开心扉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.25,0:19:59.24,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不可以随便跟别人走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.87,0:20:03.74,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你是最重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.78,0:20:08.35,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在伙伴当中是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.75,0:20:11.47,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}绝不会让给别人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.91,0:20:18.38,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明明决定好不可以抢先的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.72,0:20:25.42,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}可是谁也没有遵守诺言呢　No  No  No
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.43,0:20:28.27,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}小红帽要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.44,0:20:34.26,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不小心可不行　大灰狼正在磨牙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.36,0:20:37.56,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}就要捕捉猎物了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.59,0:20:40.58,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}小红帽要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.72,0:20:45.11,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我会拼上性命保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.15,0:20:50.97,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以求求你把你的心给我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.15,0:20:54.22,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以　作为报答
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.29,0:20:58.71,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}求求你把你的心给我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.76,0:21:01.85,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以　作为报答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.93,0:21:07.57,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}求求你把你的心给我....
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.38,0:21:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是当天晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.63,0:21:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不停逃跑而累坏的爱丽丝睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.70,0:21:20.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安  小爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.95,0:21:21.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做个好梦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.50,0:21:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说森野最近这段时间一直在修行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.20,0:21:39.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修行?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.84,0:21:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是为了保护凉子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.44,0:21:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以拜托猫宫学长帮忙让自己变强
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.59,0:21:56.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉子只需要和森野一起变强就好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.55,0:22:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.17,0:22:13.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事想和你商量...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.76,0:22:19.81,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是一个清爽的早晨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.63,0:22:25.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是个神清气爽的清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.40,0:22:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对森野来说  最大的嘉奖就是和凉子两人独处啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.21,0:22:33.59,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是大神听从这个建议
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.75,0:22:38.12,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪亮士带伊丽莎白和弗朗索瓦出来散步
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.34,0:22:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉子?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.17,0:22:42.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.13,0:22:44.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.37,0:22:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为凉子肯定在避开我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.91,0:22:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能像这样自然地聊天  就像做梦一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.94,0:22:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护凉子的人  永远都是我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.29,0:23:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那那个...  亮士
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.57,0:23:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在鬼之岛的时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.41,0:23:06.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.54,0:23:08.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.72,0:23:12.95,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得大神想努力变得坦率一点  然而...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.94,0:23:16.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我  别看我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.88,0:23:18.02,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他还是老样子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.05,0:23:21.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  凉子你继续讲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.85,0:23:24.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个废柴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.30,0:23:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁还讲得下去啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.90,0:23:31.08,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  可喜可贺  可喜可贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.90,0:23:34.78,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带下集是最终话喔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.72,0:23:40.51,kuroko,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神与虽然不卖火柴但却很不幸的少女

