[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: OP,MS UI Gothic,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,20,20,20,1
Style: ps,華康粗圓體,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,20,20,20,136
Style: Default,微软雅黑,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.26,0:00:14.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是廁所的花子的櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.04,0:00:19.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳隱藏在心裡的慾望
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.33,0:00:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在就來幫妳發洩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.31,0:00:24.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.70,0:00:28.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 饒了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.80,0:00:31.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.41,0:00:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚麼!?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.88,0:00:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丸山老師她?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.58,0:00:37.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全裸!?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.60,0:00:43.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快看啊 那裏好像放了甚麼東西一樣張開了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.31,0:00:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.77,0:00:55.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為一般人看不到我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.01,0:00:58.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以這樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.35,0:00:59.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.04,0:01:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連裡面都看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.41,0:01:10.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好激烈呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.00,0:01:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望不要對我那太粗暴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.40,0:01:16.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.65,0:01:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是淫亂的女人啊 淫水四濺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.33,0:01:27.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要說 好丟臉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.28,0:01:32.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 快忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.70,0:01:41.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真有人氣啊 丸山老師
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.31,0:01:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同一個地方插了兩根
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.00,0:01:52.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抵抗比較弱的人比較容易接受我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.30,0:01:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老二不要這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.65,0:02:02.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丸、丸山老師 我從以前開始
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.03,0:02:08.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能這樣 在教職員室做這種淫亂的事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.28,0:02:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳在說甚麼啊 乳頭都變成這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.03,0:02:20.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好…好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.08,0:02:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.80,0:02:27.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 那裏快壞掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.60,0:02:31.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把妳的身體亂搞一通
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.80,0:02:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 太激烈了 變得好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.85,0:02:42.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 多叫幾聲吧 大家都在看喔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.92,0:02:47.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.33,0:02:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.30,0:02:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我淫亂的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.78,0:02:57.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 在大家面前高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.04,0:02:59.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老師 我已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.84,0:03:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 要去了 要去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.84,0:03:11.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好…好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.74,0:03:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有點突然 不過我們學校有位廁所的花子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.78,0:03:28.83,ps,,0000,0000,0000,,(哼哼哼…真期待醒來之後啊)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.30,0:03:30.37,ps,,0000,0000,0000,,(把我老二還給我…)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.44,0:03:36.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子她常常旁若無人的做著強暴啦、殺人啦之類的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.15,0:03:41.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但不是個讓人討厭的人 我最喜歡她了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.93,0:03:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.33,0:03:47.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大城?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.32,0:03:50.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請聽我說話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.54,0:03:52.96,ps,,0000,0000,0000,,(果然還是要吃了啊)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.33,0:04:01.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ghost.2　觸手跟兩隻花子?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.66,0:04:04.09,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,shake shake your body
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.65,0:04:07.19,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,shake shake it bady
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.86,0:04:10.26,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,shake shake your body
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:14.46,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,shake shake it only you
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.49,0:04:18.50,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,君に会えそうな Sunday morning
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.68,0:04:25.09,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,すぐに駆け出すよ　I feel all right
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.06,0:04:31.33,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,君に口付け　so many time
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.59,0:04:37.88,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,浴びせ続けよ　feel my heart
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.21,0:04:46.16,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,でも本当は声もかけられない
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.21,0:04:52.89,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,体もこの胸も爆発しそうで
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.41,0:04:58.15,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,I want I like went you and you
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.25,0:05:01.78,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ会いに行こう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.88,0:05:07.39,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,抱き寄せ 大好きと言おう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:12.59,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,everytime going　だけど
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.67,0:05:22.08,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,待ってるだけじゃ本当の気持ちは誰にも届かない
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.60,0:05:33.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我無論如何都想見妳 櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.27,0:05:35.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼? 你是誰啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.40,0:05:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰…這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.78,0:05:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 妳不記得了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.00,0:05:41.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我們班上的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.82,0:05:44.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔 那時候的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.00,0:05:59.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你為什麼不能成佛啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.70,0:06:04.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實我 有個一直喜歡的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.31,0:06:08.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是因為我沒有自信所以一直沒說
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.41,0:06:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 總覺得好浪漫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.30,0:06:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到了現在才說也沒差了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.17,0:06:18.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 因為變成幽靈了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.03,0:06:23.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以想說去見見她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.03,0:06:27.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知怎的似乎無法離開學校
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.66,0:06:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔 那是因為殺你的人是我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.72,0:06:36.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我的地盤被殺掉 你就無法離開這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.68,0:06:40.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託妳 櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.05,0:06:42.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我活過來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.78,0:06:45.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣死去的話我會死不瞑目的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.17,0:06:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.31,0:06:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想活過來是吧 那就讓你活過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.06,0:06:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 可以嗎!?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.30,0:06:51.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.93,0:06:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 這要看心情的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.63,0:06:55.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有大城!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.70,0:07:11.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.00,0:07:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.06,0:07:17.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真難看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.20,0:07:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有東西跑出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.79,0:07:29.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大城!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.00,0:07:34.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 活過來了!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.06,0:07:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個身體…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.85,0:07:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可思議 不可思議
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.60,0:07:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚麼? 我的身體怎麼了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.21,0:07:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 等等 這是怎麼回事?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.00,0:07:48.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的身體 我的身體…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.00,0:07:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 好奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.08,0:07:58.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種地方長出了一隻老二 真不可思議啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.23,0:08:00.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 櫻子又做了好棒的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.75,0:08:02.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的老二呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.53,0:08:07.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙有這麼棒的東西還沒有自信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.00,0:08:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.43,0:08:13.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我讓你有告白的自信吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.67,0:08:16.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感謝我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.51,0:08:26.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.17,0:08:29.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弄濕一點喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.40,0:08:37.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的老二明明在櫻子身上卻還有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.21,0:08:46.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的身體真的變成女的了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.00,0:08:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.70,0:08:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔 你一邊自慰一邊在幹嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.41,0:09:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己開始自慰 真是變態啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.71,0:09:07.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明在自己的喉嚨在被自己的老二幹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.46,0:09:09.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卻這麼有感覺…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.31,0:09:12.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該射了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.35,0:09:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你應該知道吧 畢竟是自己的東西嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.71,0:09:18.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.95,0:09:21.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要喝下去喔 射在嘴巴裡喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.11,0:09:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把精液…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.60,0:09:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣太過分了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.28,0:09:55.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在吸…在吸我的精液…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.17,0:10:02.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭攪在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.78,0:10:06.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.00,0:10:14.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要休息!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.20,0:10:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要上囉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.03,0:10:24.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…插進去了 裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.56,0:10:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要動囉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:37.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.41,0:10:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話自己動吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.12,0:10:43.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.81,0:10:47.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託妳 拜託妳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.23,0:10:51.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再插更裡面一點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.03,0:10:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊 老二的感覺跟那裏的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.71,0:10:59.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起來的感覺如何啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.03,0:11:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連胸部也…不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.00,0:11:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來啊 在告白前讓你升天
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.50,0:11:10.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.25,0:11:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老二跟那裏都好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.40,0:11:21.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明明是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.48,0:11:23.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裏卻這麼濕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.70,0:11:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那給我高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.70,0:11:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好…好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.01,0:11:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的身體 再插更裡面一點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.33,0:11:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 要中出囉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.30,0:11:43.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要去了 去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:59.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 亂七八糟的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.00,0:12:05.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話我不要活過來也沒關係啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.75,0:12:11.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在這之後他怎麼了也沒人知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.31,0:12:30.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.17,0:12:35.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 高橋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.77,0:12:38.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快融化的感覺真不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.16,0:12:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在這種池子旁邊氣氛也是普普通通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.19,0:12:50.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難得量身訂做了泳裝 心情稍為好一點嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.34,0:12:53.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 既然機會難得就游一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.50,0:13:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 櫻子大膽的丁字褲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.60,0:13:00.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.31,0:13:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高橋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.35,0:13:19.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.00,0:13:21.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.60,0:13:25.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大原的老二長在妳身上嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.09,0:13:28.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因…因為這是櫻子…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.75,0:13:30.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先不管這個了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.18,0:13:32.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳還不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.71,0:13:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嵌進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.22,0:13:38.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有著一個沒資格說別人的大屁屁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.89,0:13:41.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳最差勁了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.67,0:13:45.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一臉好人樣就囂張起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.38,0:13:48.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞啥啊 妳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.00,0:13:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被打了還勃起嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.44,0:13:52.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.40,0:13:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以為可以跟櫻子一起舒服嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.16,0:14:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我老二去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.95,0:14:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 那裏的那位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.00,0:14:20.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻…櫻子?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.83,0:14:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.03,0:14:32.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳最近胸部太大了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.85,0:14:38.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為櫻子一直揉嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.60,0:14:41.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要推卸責任!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.80,0:14:47.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的櫻子 雖然小形狀卻很好看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.00,0:14:54.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 這樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.01,0:14:59.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔 很爽的樣子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.33,0:15:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久不見了 櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.86,0:15:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,椿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.81,0:15:11.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳在驚嚇個甚麼勁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.90,0:15:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,廁所的花子並不是只有她一個啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.06,0:15:21.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這傢伙從舊校舍跑出來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.20,0:15:23.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.66,0:15:24.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒甚麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.89,0:15:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是利用飄來飄去的幽靈當作能量吃掉而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.64,0:15:34.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大原他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.33,0:15:38.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過幽靈根本吃不飽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.46,0:15:41.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以來妳的地盤啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.47,0:15:45.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的地盤 有我中意的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.33,0:15:48.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳應該知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.00,0:15:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要幹嗎? 椿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.11,0:15:53.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要以為我還是以前的我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.70,0:15:57.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,二十年不見了很多東西都變了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.43,0:16:04.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這也是其中之一
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.15,0:16:10.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觸手嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.72,0:16:13.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用了舊校舍的蔦蘿嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.01,0:16:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.61,0:16:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.55,0:16:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像很享受的樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.33,0:16:51.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精液都從那裡流出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.05,0:16:52.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.00,0:16:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.31,0:16:58.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為一直跟我在一起 力量才會
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.00,0:17:01.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.21,0:17:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高橋…快逃…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.41,0:17:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是櫻子從白天開始就被搞的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.09,0:17:41.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在也變得很聽話了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.37,0:17:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這傢伙連高橋都...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.11,0:17:52.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳喜歡她啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.40,0:17:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要笑死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.60,0:17:57.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡…!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.00,0:17:59.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.68,0:18:00.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.83,0:18:04.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟人類搞在一起根本沒資格當花子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.00,0:18:11.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害呀 老二讓腰自己動起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.54,0:18:13.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像大陰蒂一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.47,0:18:16.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.28,0:18:19.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這跟老二我會有效利用的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.00,0:18:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 屁股太敏感了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.55,0:18:26.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之前被那個笨蛋一直搞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.90,0:18:28.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在隨隨便便就有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.01,0:18:33.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 要去、要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.09,0:18:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚麼嘛 屁股中出高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.66,0:18:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真難看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.02,0:18:58.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那把射在屁股上的精液都弄進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.22,0:19:03.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 快不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.75,0:19:05.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣繼續下去的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.62,0:19:08.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.22,0:19:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.03,0:19:12.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.49,0:19:16.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能不舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.33,0:19:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變這麼鬆了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.60,0:19:26.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 再更有感覺一點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.33,0:19:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我多看一下屁股被搞的淫亂樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.25,0:19:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 這就是屁股被我搞到發狂表情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.18,0:19:40.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.94,0:19:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要看 不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.61,0:19:47.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 很可愛嘛 淚眼汪汪的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.65,0:19:46.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.82,0:19:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很高興喔 給妳一點獎勵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.31,0:19:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.91,0:20:03.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進來了 進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.00,0:20:06.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面攪來攪去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.31,0:20:10.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 插更裡面一點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.53,0:20:18.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裡面 在子宮裡面動來動去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.41,0:20:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何 很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.41,0:20:26.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過總覺得觸手還不太夠啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.21,0:20:37.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞啥啊 只是插進去就高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.41,0:20:39.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在才正要開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.83,0:20:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 比屁股還要舒服好幾倍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.42,0:20:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老二果然一定要插在這裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.71,0:20:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.00,0:20:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了喔 全部射在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.01,0:20:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變成我的奴隸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.05,0:21:01.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.48,0:21:03.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.63,0:21:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.78,0:21:07.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.40,0:21:09.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高橋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.12,0:21:16.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子 很舒服喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.40,0:21:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.31,0:21:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.34,0:21:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高橋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.40,0:21:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.60,0:21:28.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.30,0:21:31.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼!?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.70,0:21:33.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還一直在射
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.22,0:21:35.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 射精停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.00,0:21:37.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.60,0:21:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,椿 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.80,0:21:43.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.06,0:21:47.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量使不上來 停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.44,0:21:53.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣 精子都跑到子宮…子宮裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.36,0:21:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,灌滿了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 沒事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.00,0:22:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.90,0:22:42.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我贏了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.41,0:22:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 想不到竟然是妳把椿吃掉了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.60,0:22:56.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是愛的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.67,0:23:07.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被這樣救了總覺得不能接受
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.68,0:23:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.00,0:23:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啥 是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.78,0:23:16.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大原!?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.36,0:23:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我變成只有老二了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.81,0:23:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以後該怎麼辦啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.88,0:23:28.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰知道 聽天由命吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.51,0:23:30.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.00,0:23:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太過分了 一直玩我 現在才說這種話…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.01,0:23:39.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,櫻…櫻子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.65,0:23:42.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 不過他太吵了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.11,0:23:45.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原本看在他是妳的朋友才特別照顧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.85,0:23:47.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是卻整天纏著我們真讓人受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.11,0:23:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再說了 無論如何妳都是我的東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.46,0:23:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以只要跟我搞就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.66,0:23:56.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我才會高興
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.81,0:23:59.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以妨礙我興趣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.31,0:24:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞啥啊 那張臉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.86,0:24:04.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.00,0:24:07.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從今以後也請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.40,0:24:15.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.21,0:26:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳要親到甚麼時候啊
