[Script Info]
Title:Umineko 07 bd gb
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: DefaultCN,方正隶变_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00838383,&H00804000,&H005E5E5E,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,2,2,5,5,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0F0F0F,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,5,134
Style: opjp,麗流隷書,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,15,15,10,128
Style: opcn,方正隶变_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,9,15,15,10,134
Style: Italian,Tempus Sans ITC,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,15,15,10,0
Style: pos,黑体,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,8,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:07.88,Italian,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Il giudizio finale sta per essere emesso
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:07.88,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs17}最後の審判は下されてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.94,0:00:14.51,Italian,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Nessuno può emendarsi dal peccato che scorre nelle vene
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.94,0:00:14.51,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs17}体を流れる血の原罪からは、誰も逃れることはできない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.59,0:00:41.99,Italian,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Sperare
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.59,0:00:41.99,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs17}この願いは
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.03,0:00:45.52,Italian,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}è peccato?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.03,0:00:45.52,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs17}罪ですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.15,0:01:30.71,Italian,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Tu sei senza peccato? Quanto sarà pesante il mio castigo?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.15,0:01:30.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs17}あなたに罪はありませんか？　私の罰はどれ位ですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.53,0:00:21.09,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}海鳴りの調べに　黑雲は空へ集う
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.13,0:00:27.16,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}嵐を呼ぶ風は　高らかに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.26,0:00:34.16,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}謎めく言ノ葉に　魔女達は含み笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.22,0:00:40.56,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}歪な夜の宴は　繰り返す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.95,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}奈落へと堕ちた　金色の蝶は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.00,0:00:57.06,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}幾つの罪に　翅を濡らしてゆくの？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.59,0:01:05.23,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}{\1c&H0000FF&\fscy135\fscx105}な{\r}かないで　囚われた　幻想を壊し
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.27,0:01:10.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一度きりの　終焉をあげよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.74,0:01:19.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}果たせない約束は　胸の奥　焦げ付いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.12,0:01:25.11,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}赤く赤く　爆ぜてくよ　ねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:07.88,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}最终审判即将公布
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.94,0:00:14.51,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}谁也无法逃脱流淌在血液中的原罪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.59,0:00:41.99,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这个心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.03,0:00:45.52,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是罪过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.15,0:01:30.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的罪孽有多深？而我的惩罚又该有多重？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.53,0:00:21.09,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}海浪之歌  令黑云聚集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.13,0:00:27.16,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}风在高声呼唤暴风雨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.26,0:00:34.16,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}充满谜团的话语  令魔女们窃笑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.22,0:00:40.56,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}扭曲的晚宴轮回流转
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.95,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}金色蝴蝶堕入无限深渊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.00,0:00:57.06,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}羽翼所染之罪孽又是几多重？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.59,0:01:05.23,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}不要哭  粉碎被囚禁的幻想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.27,0:01:10.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}迎接仅有一次的终结
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.74,0:01:19.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}无法履行的约定炙烤内心深处
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.12,0:01:25.11,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}手掌已满是血红  你说是吗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.26,0:22:06.95,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}この夜が終わり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.67,0:22:12.57,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我は何を求む
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.48,0:22:24.27,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追憶は残酷に　嘲笑うわ…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.62,0:22:33.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闇を切り裂く欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.62,0:22:33.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(127,328)}Oh Desire
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.29,0:22:38.76,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}拒むなかれ愛しい者よ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.29,0:22:38.76,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(178,328)}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.82,0:22:44.23,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}逝ける場所なき欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.82,0:22:44.23,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(131,328)}Oh My Prayers
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:50.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}最後の狂宴よ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:50.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(75,328)}うたげ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.13,0:22:55.79,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我心を切り裂く欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.13,0:22:55.79,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(18,328)}や
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.13,0:22:55.79,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(40,328)}み
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.13,0:22:55.79,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(148,328)}Oh Desire
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:23:01.39,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}叶えたまえ愛しい魔物よ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:23:01.39,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(187,328)}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:23:01.39,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(209,328)}と
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:06.75,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}赦されなき欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:06.75,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(105,328)}Oh Desire
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.77,0:23:10.63,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}今宵愚者共を汝に贈ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.77,0:23:10.63,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs15\pos(30,328)}sacrifice a sheep to a god
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.26,0:22:06.95,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}黑夜结束
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.67,0:22:12.57,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}吾所求为何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.48,0:22:24.27,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}昔日记忆残酷嘲讽…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.62,0:22:33.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}撕裂黑暗的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.29,0:22:38.76,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}勿要抗拒  我深爱的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.82,0:22:44.23,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}无处可藏的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:50.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}最后的狂宴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.13,0:22:55.79,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}撕裂我心的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:23:01.39,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}实现吾愿  亲爱的魔鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:06.75,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}不被饶恕的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.77,0:23:10.63,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}今夜将愚者献祭于汝
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.06,0:01:36.69,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.27,0:01:39.31,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要过万圣节
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.48,0:01:41.36,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要扮演魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.71,0:01:45.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲族会议可不是闹着玩  不行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.67,0:01:48.34,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给我糖果就捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.33,0:01:54.87,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  呜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.93,0:01:57.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给我糖果就捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.81,0:01:59.13,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.32,0:02:06.55,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚  怎么能随便拿别人的糖果
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.87,0:02:07.59,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我还回去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.84,0:02:10.87,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  这是给真里亚的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.12,0:02:13.85,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是一直叫你听妈妈的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.09,0:02:16.26,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是真里亚的  真里亚的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.30,0:02:17.56,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  呜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.14,0:02:20.93,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你别再「呜呜」了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.20,0:02:23.14,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  呜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.18,0:02:27.28,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你  别再「呜呜」了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.18,0:02:47.87,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.49,0:02:51.14,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备得如何了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.66,0:02:53.94,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经全部安排好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.41,0:02:56.82,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲的事情没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:03:01.53,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  源次和南条医生是站在我们这边的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.06,0:03:06.16,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不会让那些贪得无厌的兄弟见父亲的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.50,0:03:17.56,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纱音  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.91,0:03:20.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才起就心神不宁的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.72,0:03:22.69,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.23,0:03:24.27,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.95,0:03:29.09,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.54,0:03:30.06,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.44,0:03:38.85,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  今天重要的客人将会下榻此处
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.25,0:03:41.88,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能放下私事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.91,0:03:44.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我才没什么私事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.23,0:03:54.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纱音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.53,0:03:57.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你默默地收下它
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.69,0:04:00.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.45,0:04:02.95,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它戴到无名指上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.14,0:04:04.41,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.39,0:04:07.30,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也不对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.44,0:04:15.27,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留弗夫伯父
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.44,0:04:19.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越紧张就越生硬  不会有好事的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.14,0:04:24.95,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人和老头都是难伺候的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.27,0:04:26.75,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.18,0:04:28.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.64,0:04:35.62,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.45,0:04:38.61,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.64,0:04:41.19,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈给我买的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.40,0:04:44.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  现在是十月  所以是万圣节吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.54,0:04:48.37,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给我糖果就捣乱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.10,0:04:50.81,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.98,0:04:51.59,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.98,0:04:56.66,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万圣节要搞化装游行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.16,0:05:00.34,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  真里亚也想化装
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.63,0:05:02.22,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想扮演谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.52,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔女  贝亚特丽切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:05.61,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔女？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.26,0:05:06.92,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.80,0:05:14.38,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  您怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.98,0:05:20.86,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊泽婆婆  你和源次先生一样在这家里工作很久了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.26,0:05:23.90,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道很多关于贝亚特丽切的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.17,0:05:26.86,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切大人是黄金的魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.03,0:05:31.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是支配这座岛的夜晚的另一位主人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.90,0:05:33.99,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是照着爷爷说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.93,0:05:41.57,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六轩岛在很久以前被称为小豆岛而令人畏惧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.78,0:05:44.47,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「小豆」是「恶食」发音不标准而产生的一词
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.93,0:05:48.98,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近总是出现海难事故而令渔民畏惧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.23,0:05:53.18,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  恶食岛上居住着恶灵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.11,0:05:59.17,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅行中的僧侣建了祠来镇魂后才使得海难平息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.44,0:06:00.45,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这则故事的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.02,0:06:07.20,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那座镇魂祠在今年夏天被撕裂黑暗的雷击坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.24,0:06:10.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊泽婆婆可真喜欢这类故事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.30,0:06:14.25,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被觉醒的恶灵们召唤而来的贝亚特丽切大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.46,0:06:19.07,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若光临亲族会议的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.18,0:06:20.21,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光临亲族会议的话？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.04,0:06:28.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了么  秃鹫们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.62,0:06:35.59,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮盘已经开始转动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.93,0:06:41.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是红是黑  今夜轮盘将展现怎样的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.41,0:06:44.21,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  贝亚特丽切啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.36,0:06:46.35,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受我的赌博吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:54.30,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说万圣节是这个世界和死后世界的交汇时期
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.59,0:06:57.36,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对魔女们来说是个重要的机会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.74,0:07:01.78,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜  所以贝亚特丽切也一定会来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.62,0:07:06.82,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.36,0:07:09.73,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来所有的棋子都到齐了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.14,0:07:12.68,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始新一轮的游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.06,0:07:16.60,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论你使出哪一手  我都不会承认你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.16,0:07:19.06,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要贯彻这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.58,0:07:20.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会输
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.78,0:07:26.81,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这游戏直到你承认为止  会无限重复下去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:29.16,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说这是拷问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.51,0:07:33.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到你将屈服于我  承认魔女的存在为止
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.05,0:07:36.33,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远持续的拷问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.63,0:07:40.09,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  这是向你的拷问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.65,0:07:45.45,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你何时向我屈服放弃  如此重复下去的拷问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.75,0:07:46.97,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.36,0:07:49.38,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.76,0:07:52.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相折磨的拷问
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.40,0:07:54.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右代宫战人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.90,0:08:00.10,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说那贝亚特丽切是什么人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.48,0:08:01.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切她是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.15,0:08:02.77,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.31,0:08:05.32,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再提这事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.06,0:08:16.53,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你别提魔女的事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.57,0:08:17.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.37,0:08:20.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是九岁啊九岁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.34,0:08:24.76,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在电车里吵吵嚷嚷所以给你买了这恶心的糖果
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.20,0:08:27.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要给我的脸抹多少黑才满意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.05,0:08:30.73,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈好疼  妈妈好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.63,0:08:38.89,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种恶心的糖果算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.72,0:08:43.72,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心  恶心…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.25,0:08:46.10,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心  恶心…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.13,0:08:47.42,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈快回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.93,0:08:49.81,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战胜坏魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.71,0:08:53.13,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也不管你这种不听话的孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.45,0:08:54.72,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我一直在那呆着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.57,0:09:14.02,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚小姐  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.49,0:09:21.15,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啊  真里亚完全没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.73,0:09:29.55,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我只能掸掸灰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.52,0:09:34.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切能轻易修复它
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:39.72,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚小姐知道贝亚特丽切大人的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.49,0:09:46.16,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲埋头于研究  非常忙碌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.64,0:09:48.63,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾他无法到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.09,0:09:50.03,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年也这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.94,0:09:54.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望老爸也能平易近人一些啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.12,0:09:58.34,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚可是贝亚特丽切的朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.81,0:10:00.81,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也要一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.50,0:10:06.20,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寿命只剩三个月…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.59,0:10:09.90,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上会不会根本就卧床不起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.27,0:10:14.29,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金藏老爷具有超乎常人的毅力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.93,0:10:19.51,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子台风正在逼近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.35,0:10:21.89,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.90,0:10:24.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.25,0:10:26.08,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.56,0:10:29.14,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚  在吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.75,0:10:30.96,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在的话回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.16,0:10:38.21,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.69,0:10:39.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.15,0:10:41.11,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.66,0:10:44.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起真里亚…原谅妈妈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.99,0:10:47.81,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜…妈妈欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.05,0:10:51.96,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚一直在等妈妈回来  一直等着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.42,0:10:55.21,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚  原谅妈妈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.96,0:11:00.48,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是妈妈的错  只是又被坏魔女给控制了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.98,0:11:03.21,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没关系  我最喜欢妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.83,0:11:06.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…原谅妈妈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.05,0:11:11.85,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.61,0:11:18.52,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.38,0:11:21.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.24,0:11:24.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.14,0:11:27.45,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切  万圣节快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.93,0:11:31.74,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给贝亚特的  呜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.22,0:11:34.71,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个送我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.44,0:11:35.97,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.71,0:11:38.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.73,0:11:43.71,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被踩碎了…贝亚特能复原它吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.28,0:11:45.22,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.95,0:11:50.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记忆中的那支糖果一直都是饱满的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.29,0:11:53.36,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以好好回忆起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.85,0:11:56.17,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来那支糖果是什么样子的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.18,0:12:04.88,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.50,0:12:07.23,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以睁开眼睛了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.40,0:12:14.87,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切真厉害  真厉害真厉害…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.83,0:12:18.73,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真里亚  这个东西交给你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.68,0:12:21.41,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.50,0:12:22.03,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.60,0:12:28.68,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拆开它的时候很快就会来临  在那之前绝对不可以拆开
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.34,0:12:32.76,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这将成为邀请你至黄金乡的招待券
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.65,0:12:35.67,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黄金乡？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.84,0:12:37.66,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许给其他任何人看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.06,0:12:39.31,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我会遵守的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.74,0:12:42.03,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会遵守好和魔女之间的约定的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.22,0:12:49.44,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这封是给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.46,0:12:51.36,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.66,0:12:54.97,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.59,0:13:00.77,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面的内容  在所有兄弟姐妹齐聚一堂的晚餐席上读一读吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.17,0:13:23.35,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久候多时了  贝亚特丽切大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.97,0:13:25.99,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老了呢  源次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.14,0:13:41.51,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个人是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.59,0:13:48.91,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你否定我的最大的根据
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.09,0:13:52.65,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是我没有摆在棋盘上而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.54,0:13:55.48,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我这次就摆进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:58.78,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？起手就准备投降吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.46,0:14:00.30,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.91,0:14:02.76,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼才要投降啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.90,0:14:04.76,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就接我下面一招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.46,0:14:16.23,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了  家具嘉音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.20,0:14:19.82,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来履行和金藏的约定的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.01,0:14:23.35,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西归还黄金乡的日子来临了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.80,0:14:29.25,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那耻辱的家具生涯  终于走到头了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.10,0:14:36.85,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不高兴呢？还是对这尘世有所留恋呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.50,0:14:40.68,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么留恋的…我只是家具而已…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.48,0:14:44.65,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是没什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.32,0:14:47.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就用纱音来满足吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.97,0:14:53.55,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把现在想和让治白头偕老的纱音作为活祭品之一
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.15,0:14:57.96,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用她的留恋让我好好享受享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.00,0:14:58.90,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真卑鄙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.42,0:15:00.52,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我跪下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.89,0:15:05.22,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我跪下吻我靴子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.92,0:15:10.35,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定我会把纱音从活祭品中换掉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:28.22,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能接受  为什么不能让我去送餐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.35,0:15:32.60,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切大人是与馆主大人同样级别的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.00,0:15:37.18,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以规矩必须和对待馆主大人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.63,0:15:40.15,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是姐姐你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.39,0:15:43.95,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐你要是没有爱情这种留恋的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.49,0:15:47.42,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就会彼此对终于到来的这一天感到无比高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.66,0:15:48.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前往黄金乡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.10,0:15:53.36,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可能从此不再是家具而转世为人的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.80,0:15:56.05,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仪式今晚就要开始吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.62,0:15:57.20,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.70,0:16:01.24,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生气了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.60,0:16:02.61,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在指什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.04,0:16:07.13,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你的恋爱上帮你只不过是我一时兴起的玩乐之心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.56,0:16:13.13,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是为了观赏你们如何执拗  扭曲  破裂而播下的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.15,0:16:17.06,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您玩弄别人  令他们困惑难受
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.16,0:16:19.14,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而自己从中得到享受和食粮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.56,0:16:24.14,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以对抗您唯一的方法  现在我已经知晓了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.80,0:16:25.43,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.84,0:16:30.75,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将无视您的存在  接受自己的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.05,0:16:33.78,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我不会让您产生任何愉悦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.55,0:16:37.41,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我唯一所能做到的对您的反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.42,0:16:41.74,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是还有事的话  我会安排别人来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.45,0:16:54.68,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣  我要杀了你  还有你那小情人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.22,0:17:00.18,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个酱用的是波尔多酱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.69,0:17:02.98,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望大家尽心品尝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.11,0:17:05.17,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错嘛  乡田
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.53,0:17:07.08,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.67,0:17:09.72,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请慢慢享用
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.14,0:17:11.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  请问
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.51,0:17:15.93,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位客人不来一起享用晚餐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.36,0:17:21.05,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  那位客人说想在贵宾室独自用晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.31,0:17:23.84,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人？你们在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.64,0:17:25.67,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:28.62,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是贝亚特丽切大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.88,0:17:30.97,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.83,0:17:32.65,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔女？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.40,0:17:35.91,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乡田  你这是什么余兴节目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.02,0:17:40.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着演三流戏了  不是大哥叫来的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.12,0:17:41.15,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.29,0:17:43.53,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥  不要装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.76,0:17:48.28,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁啊？别跟我说那真的是贝亚特丽切本人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.39,0:17:50.26,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在说什么我完全不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.28,0:17:52.10,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是老爷子叫来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.34,0:17:53.32,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.81,0:17:55.35,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔女贝亚特丽切吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.38,0:18:00.42,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么魔女？情人吧  不然就是私生子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.45,0:18:05.64,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的人  是想要分老爷子的遗产才来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.02,0:18:11.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家主大人可没有什么情人这种见不得人的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.64,0:18:13.83,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,源次先生应该知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.42,0:18:16.19,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先应该问问他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.81,0:18:18.92,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  乡田
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.21,0:18:20.37,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.10,0:18:24.71,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱志香  你们回客舍去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.47,0:18:26.46,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.34,0:18:30.58,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也离席吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.73,0:18:36.70,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南条医生  爷爷有个叫贝亚特丽切的情人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.14,0:18:38.23,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.54,0:18:40.84,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没见过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.16,0:18:44.70,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  以前和那样一位女性有过交往
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.10,0:18:47.88,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经听金藏老爷提到过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.23,0:18:51.07,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是很久以前就已经去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.55,0:18:52.70,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道他们有孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.20,0:18:54.37,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.24,0:19:00.37,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是金藏老爷为了将贝亚特丽切复活而开始了研究
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.56,0:19:02.12,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我时常听他这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.75,0:19:04.39,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才沉迷于黑魔术…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.81,0:19:09.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成说  是为了复仇才回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.37,0:19:11.49,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复仇？那是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.62,0:19:14.10,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算她拥有魔女的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.40,0:19:16.41,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是不会使用魔法的人类女人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.54,0:19:19.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终还是什么都做不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.04,0:19:23.67,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切肯定会让大家看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.85,0:19:25.82,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类做不到的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.21,0:19:28.68,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后战人就会相信吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.91,0:19:31.18,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝亚特丽切  魔女的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.30,0:19:33.60,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  信就信
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.17,0:19:44.11,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给你  这个戒指
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.98,0:19:48.17,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.21,0:19:53.06,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.69,0:19:58.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算死了  就算只有灵魂  我们也要在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.58,0:20:00.71,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个戒指戴在你喜欢的那根手指上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.42,0:20:02.95,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此作为答复
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.56,0:20:06.76,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在明早之前…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.18,0:20:20.23,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的答复  让治
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.57,0:20:24.98,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纱音…不  纱代
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.90,0:20:30.29,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算只有灵魂  也会一直  一直在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.40,0:20:33.38,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让治
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.85,0:20:42.05,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:43.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真傻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.15,0:20:50.04,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没别的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.33,0:20:53.29,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和夏妃认同了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.59,0:20:57.30,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说不愿意相信  但那就是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.02,0:20:59.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我们也认同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.18,0:21:05.58,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点异议都没有  我们会老老实实地把对您的尊敬铭记于心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.79,0:21:06.89,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.57,0:21:11.01,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在为止也难以相信  但是没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.22,0:21:14.13,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔都已经被证明了  是你赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.15,0:21:19.82,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「恶魔的证明」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.00,0:21:24.08,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来是你对无法证实的事情喜欢使用的便利的借口
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.21,0:21:25.65,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看来适得其反呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.91,0:21:29.79,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也投降了  我也承认了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.72,0:21:34.96,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是贝亚特丽切  右代宫家的顾问炼金术师
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.21,0:21:37.51,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是伟大的魔法使
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.17,0:21:40.40,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不承认你是魔女

Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.93,0:23:17.80,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是战人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.57,0:23:21.11,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然被带到了莫名其妙的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.72,0:23:25.90,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总之  我绝不承认这是魔女所为
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.61,0:23:28.47,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要战斗到底
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.30,0:23:31.97,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  贝亚特丽切  一决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.29,0:23:37.00,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去厕所  叫我等等？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:40.54,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.10,0:23:42.47,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就等三分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.51,0:23:45.70,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  厕所之后是午茶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.94,0:23:48.03,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来又是午觉时间？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.30,0:23:51.86,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  是哪来的家里蹲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.67,0:23:56.24,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  别和真里亚一起看电视
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.17,0:23:59.03,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集  weak  square
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.70,0:24:06.07,DefaultCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竹飞机  好好玩














