[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: EDC,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,2,2,15,15,8,134
Style: title,华康娃娃体W5-A,35,&H0031a6db,&Hf0000000,&H00efefef,&H001f1f1f,-1,0,0,0,100,100,4,0.00,1,4,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPJ,A-OTF TakaHand Std B,23,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,15,15,4,128
Style: EDJ,DFHeiMedium-UN,17,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,4,2,8,15,15,8,128
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,10,8,13434
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00ffffff,&H005955fd,&H00000000,&H00ffffff,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: OPC,方正雅珠体简繁 DemiBold,26,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,15,15,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.83,0:00:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.19,0:00:17.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.18,0:00:18.28,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.18,0:00:18.28,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.34,0:00:19.05,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.34,0:00:19.05,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:20.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:20.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.30,0:00:20.94,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.30,0:00:20.94,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.06,0:00:22.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.06,0:00:22.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.27,0:00:24.40,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.27,0:00:24.40,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しょう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.46,0:00:27.32,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.46,0:00:27.32,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:43.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:43.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心が大事です
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.91,0:00:44.85,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.91,0:00:44.85,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.89,0:00:47.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抑制住急躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.89,0:00:47.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}はやる心を抑えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.88,0:00:48.72,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.88,0:00:48.72,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモンモンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.76,0:00:51.72,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}做个平常人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.76,0:00:51.72,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}常識人になりましょう！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.82,0:00:52.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.82,0:00:52.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.77,0:00:56.03,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}难应付的人也会亲密起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.77,0:00:56.03,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ヤバイ人ならすぐなれる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.30,0:01:00.37,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}两人蔚蓝的Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.30,0:01:00.37,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}青い二人のヘブン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.46,0:01:03.21,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}变成小狗的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.46,0:01:03.21,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}子犬になる夢は
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.44,0:01:04.17,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.44,0:01:04.17,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}レア
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.23,0:01:11.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}愉快灿烂地投影在脑海中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.23,0:01:11.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ユカイ特盛りの脳トレースして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.19,0:01:13.86,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在天空盘旋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.19,0:01:13.86,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}空を　駆け回りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.92,0:01:18.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在摇曳思念下的果实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.92,0:01:18.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}揺れる想いの下の　果肉には
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.26,0:01:21.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}充满恋爱的甜美
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.26,0:01:21.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}恋の美味しさだけ　ふくらんで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.81,0:01:26.14,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}如果有制作美味菜谱的野心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.81,0:01:26.14,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}凄いメニューを作ると　野望なら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.26,0:01:30.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}那就用心培育果实吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.26,0:01:30.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}まっとうに　フルーツ　はぐくみましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.42,0:01:31.63,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.42,0:01:31.63,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.75,0:01:32.46,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pa
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.75,0:01:32.46,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:33.64,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:33.64,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.73,0:01:34.27,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.73,0:01:34.27,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.39,0:01:35.65,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.39,0:01:35.65,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.77,0:01:37.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.77,0:01:37.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.70,0:01:38.36,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.70,0:01:38.36,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.46,0:01:39.51,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}努力修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.46,0:01:39.51,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}修行しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.61,0:01:40.30,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.61,0:01:40.30,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.36,0:01:41.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}拿出干劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.36,0:01:41.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}気合いしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.89,0:01:44.82,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.89,0:01:44.82,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…

Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.90,0:01:53.40,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(560,270)\fs25}“再见了白杨”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.51,0:01:57.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈你似乎很高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.57,0:02:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明刚才因为打碎了盘子还很郁闷的说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.77,0:02:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  虽然那件事的确是要反省一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过呢  至今一直够不着的破损报告表终于够到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.30,0:02:11.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.63,0:02:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个大事件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.49,0:02:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好开心呀  我长高啦  YAHOO~
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.96,0:02:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个事件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.14,0:02:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.43,0:02:30.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个事件说的是…白杨长高的事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.95,0:02:31.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.55,0:02:35.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐…佐藤…小鸟游蔑视我那眼神…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.33,0:02:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅小鸟游吧  他也是因为太过突然导致精神失常
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.51,0:02:44.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  因为小鸟游喜欢袖珍物  所以不能接受
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.31,0:02:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小白杨的身高还是长高了  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.80,0:02:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.32,0:02:51.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.78,0:02:55.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可能的  前辈长高什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.41,0:02:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  抢走她的牛奶  把她从头往下按之类
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.03,0:03:00.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都在阻碍她的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.89,0:03:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  我每天都对着夜空祈祷前辈不要长高
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天三次的说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.94,0:03:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我跟你相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:10.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在搞什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.98,0:03:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放低了这张纸的位置了吧  店长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.30,0:03:15.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.53,0:03:18.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对动过了  一定要这样  肯定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.82,0:03:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然迷惑我和前辈的长不高之心  店长真是太过份了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.73,0:03:22.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  徐娘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.08,0:03:26.44,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.10,0:03:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们搞什么飞机啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.77,0:03:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要把我和他归为一类
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.62,0:03:31.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸的位置没有动过  绝对没动过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.51,0:03:35.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为没有人比山田更熟悉破损报告表了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.53,0:03:37.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  因为你这家伙经常打破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.08,0:03:40.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破坏女王的山田在此证言
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.09,0:03:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  大家快来信奉敬拜山田吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.62,0:03:43.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.07,0:03:44.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.56,0:03:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.56,0:03:56.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.20,0:04:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫松本麻耶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.70,0:04:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有山的话也不会有谷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.78,0:04:06.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过着普通的人生  总之我就是普通的18岁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.82,0:04:13.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有着如此普通神话的我一般被人称为松本普通麻耶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.40,0:04:13.54,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}才不会有人这么叫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.89,0:04:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的我今天作为普通的学生在普通的店里打工
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.15,0:04:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  身体状况不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.62,0:04:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徐娘…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.69,0:04:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.75,0:04:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了小鸟游  总觉得你好阴郁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.67,0:04:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事都没有  这是我和前辈的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.66,0:04:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游怎么了  如果有什么烦恼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.71,0:05:01.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望他可以找我商量…什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.92,0:05:05.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在叹气  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.84,0:05:11.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有什么烦心的事  尽管来找烦心专家山田来商量吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.83,0:05:12.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专家？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.74,0:05:17.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  山田一直有着各种烦心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.50,0:05:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马哥一直不好好疼爱我  音尾先生什么时候回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.54,0:05:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做才能让他收我为养女什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.88,0:05:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最…最后那个有点难吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.53,0:05:35.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以同时烦恼伊波姐的事就像是家常便饭一样轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.01,0:05:37.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.76,0:05:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游在为种岛姐的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.08,0:05:43.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.56,0:05:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人之间到底发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.51,0:05:50.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非是小鹿乱撞心跳不已的修罗场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.41,0:05:51.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.07,0:05:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田我狂喜不已  那么山田直接去问种岛姐了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.59,0:05:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田疾跑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.85,0:06:00.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  山田
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.20,0:06:02.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爬
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.54,0:06:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么爬上阁楼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.00,0:06:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  松本也休息吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.78,0:06:08.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.50,0:06:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好在意小鸟游的烦恼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.90,0:06:18.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是真的喜欢上种岛的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.62,0:06:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要…要怎么办…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.23,0:06:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波你喜欢小鸟游吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.71,0:06:25.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…为什么你知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.62,0:06:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很普通地表露出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.94,0:06:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不…那…那个…有那回事吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.70,0:06:36.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  原来真的喜欢他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.60,0:06:38.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错啊  恋爱  好普通
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.27,0:06:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徐娘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.68,0:06:44.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是重新考虑一下比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.92,0:06:45.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.84,0:06:48.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.24,0:06:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵妹妹你在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.72,0:06:57.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦恼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.63,0:06:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.88,0:07:01.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没有什么特别的烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.99,0:07:05.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  应该有的  请仔细想想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.02,0:07:08.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有一两个的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.93,0:07:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾是最大烦恼的身高也稍微长了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.91,0:07:16.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个啊  那应该说是将来的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.71,0:07:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.97,0:07:21.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看我都高二了  差不多就要考大学了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.95,0:07:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近朋友们都开始去上补习班了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.97,0:07:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也在想是不是应该认真考虑一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.31,0:07:34.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考大学吗  山田我承受着正常人五倍的考试量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.68,0:07:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.94,0:07:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我是考试的专家  这样的山田可以给种岛姐建议
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.02,0:07:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学习能力是无法衡量人的价值的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.89,0:07:48.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说完这话后  就能有点释然了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.88,0:07:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵  经历太多失败了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.68,0:07:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个呢  前阵子妈妈也对我说“要好好考虑一下将来的事了”
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.92,0:08:02.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  山田也有过这样的经历
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.75,0:08:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视情况说不定要辞掉这份工
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.98,0:08:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  现在还没有考虑这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.08,0:08:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说为什么前辈长高了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.23,0:08:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都在纠结呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.39,0:08:29.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马  我已经陷入了迷宫里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何也不能接受她长高的事实吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.32,0:08:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对如此纠结的你们  我这里有种岛以前踮脚的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.14,0:08:41.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.45,0:08:43.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马  你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.62,0:08:45.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.82,0:08:47.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也好不到哪去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.67,0:08:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.52,0:08:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你  千万别说出什么放大了挂房间墙上之类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.44,0:08:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想把它缩小到不能再缩小  看着更小号的前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.92,0:09:00.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走这条思路了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.93,0:09:05.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到本人现场的话就能马上明白的  你果然还是不懂？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.01,0:09:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.53,0:09:09.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了山田
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.53,0:09:11.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在很忙  有话一会儿再说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.47,0:09:16.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛姐似乎要辞掉瓦古娜莉亚的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.69,0:09:22.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.65,0:09:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.61,0:09:32.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  要和种岛道别了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.08,0:09:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田说的要是真的话  那就是要道别了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.14,0:09:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一这样想  我也会有点伤感…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.97,0:09:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好难啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.51,0:09:51.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  和我没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.16,0:09:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你动摇了呢  佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.60,0:09:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤  相马  你们听说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.65,0:09:59.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小白杨要辞职了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.49,0:10:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.57,0:10:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.05,0:10:04.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞啊  有什么办法阻止她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.06,0:10:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛要是这么决定的话  一定有她的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.32,0:10:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是不要乱插手把事情弄复杂比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.09,0:10:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.20,0:10:15.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  佐藤你该不会也在想要辞职什么的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.05,0:10:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要辞职啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.29,0:10:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤你之前说过的  如果是真的话  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.26,0:10:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没决定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.81,0:10:29.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有你在  他是不会辞职的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.34,0:10:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼啊  佐藤  我很痛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.40,0:10:33.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.69,0:10:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有  总之现在没有想辞职的意向
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.66,0:10:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快回去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.14,0:10:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…你认真的吧  你认真的吧  好疼啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.95,0:10:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  真的别这样  佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.44,0:10:50.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  松本
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.20,0:10:52.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.10,0:10:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说了吗  种岛要辞职的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.62,0:10:56.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？有这回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.51,0:10:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  杏子姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.48,0:10:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.14,0:11:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑了下肚子就饿了  八千代  圣代
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.48,0:11:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.75,0:11:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游你听说种岛的事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.44,0:11:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从山田那边听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.37,0:11:26.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像种岛在考虑考大学的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.64,0:11:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  前辈也差不多要…大考了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.68,0:11:34.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大考…她可不是幼稚园小学生什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.19,0:11:37.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小鸟游老说她很小很小的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.90,0:11:39.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应…应该不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:42.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为小鸟游老摸她头？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.34,0:11:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.53,0:11:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为小鸟游…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.00,0:11:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么全部都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.08,0:11:51.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是打工啊  总会面临什么辞职的时候的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.28,0:11:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不可能揍小鸟游一辈子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.61,0:11:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算揍我一辈子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.83,0:12:00.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  如果前辈不干了的话我该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.50,0:12:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.44,0:12:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.68,0:12:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果种岛前辈不干了  是不是小鸟游也要辞职呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.69,0:12:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为小鸟游也是因为前辈在这里才开始来打工的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.76,0:12:25.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会离开的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.74,0:12:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说过我会照看伊波到最后的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.57,0:12:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起  但是谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.36,0:12:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.49,0:12:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.56,0:12:44.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波  真巧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.05,0:12:48.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到好事工作也会很顺利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.87,0:12:50.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙真是没完没了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.33,0:12:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等等等  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.44,0:12:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田  怎么了 没摔着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.05,0:12:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀  你不是之前那个小学生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.82,0:13:00.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是小学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.58,0:13:02.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  迷路了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.39,0:13:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没迷路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.91,0:13:05.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.70,0:13:08.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这玩笑开得真离谱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.89,0:13:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何小学生会穿成服务员打扮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.64,0:13:15.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是小学生啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.48,0:13:17.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看这样我也是明年就要考大学的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.01,0:13:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考大学？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.07,0:13:22.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  向前辈确认一下到底是不是要辞职了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.92,0:13:25.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  这样胡乱的闹会给她带来压力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:28.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.79,0:13:30.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈很温柔的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.42,0:13:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而会变得难以辞职
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.91,0:13:35.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会变得冷清呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.75,0:13:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.96,0:13:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  明明这么小  你真厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.64,0:13:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还参加中学考试
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.86,0:13:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不小  也不是中学考试啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.45,0:13:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于将来而言学习的确是很重要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.24,0:13:53.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也只是个嫩头青的高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.50,0:13:57.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情  找个有经验的人商量一下不是比较好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.98,0:13:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.08,0:14:00.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.36,0:14:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊  小学考试
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.60,0:14:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.50,0:14:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是什么小学考试啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.69,0:14:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确一个人也想不出啥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.74,0:14:18.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问问店里的大伙儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.29,0:14:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了好事之后心情真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.59,0:14:23.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.60,0:14:26.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了本来是来找妹妹的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.70,0:14:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是女生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.57,0:14:28.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个普通的女生在！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.17,0:14:30.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边那个普通的可爱女生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.09,0:14:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你就是我的妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.97,0:14:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的男生不会穿着白色立领边跑边问别人是不是你的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.94,0:14:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那白领染黑了再来  你这怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.41,0:14:46.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  考大学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.45,0:14:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛也到这个年龄了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.35,0:14:51.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢  我想听听有经验的人的建议
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:53.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以的话  你随便问吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.94,0:14:56.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  相马是大学生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.89,0:14:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.87,0:14:59.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么进去的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.22,0:14:59.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:01.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打过工吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.27,0:15:01.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.02,0:15:05.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说过什么都可以问你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.41,0:15:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上大学的方式不是只有一种
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.02,0:15:12.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有努力了也考不上的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.35,0:15:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有不努力而考上的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.23,0:15:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有使坏走后门入学的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.07,0:15:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走后门入学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.70,0:15:23.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学……走错了前后门会惹人生气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.15,0:15:27.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  这话题对于种岛似乎太复杂了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.29,0:15:31.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  我去问问别的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.48,0:15:32.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  相马
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.43,0:15:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.76,0:15:48.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要糟蹋粮食  松本
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.24,0:15:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也像现代人一样积蓄了很多压力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.22,0:15:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不找谁释放一下会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.82,0:15:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边反而积累压力了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.21,0:15:58.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时都是找种岛排解压力的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.81,0:15:59.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.82,0:16:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛很有趣哦  会一直不停地吵闹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.50,0:16:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算当天生气了  第二天也会若无其事的和我打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.71,0:16:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是种岛好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.28,0:16:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  松本  我非选种岛不可
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.92,0:16:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么像是我被甩了一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.26,0:16:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意啦  松本  佐藤这人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.08,0:16:25.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到种岛可能会不干了  就开始动摇了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.38,0:16:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.41,0:16:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松本是怎么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.21,0:16:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事由的话那也没有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.26,0:16:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊  普通来说一起打工的同伴不该挽留一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.08,0:16:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  普通上 普通不一定就普通吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.10,0:16:41.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通地来说普通不算是普通吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.68,0:16:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的普通如果是因为什么其他原因变得普通而普通不是很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.78,0:16:48.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通来说普通会变化吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.70,0:16:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通会随着时代普通的变化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.74,0:16:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通就是普通  普通只要普通地普通就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.07,0:16:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.91,0:17:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  为了不让前辈多心  一定要努力用笑容欢送她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.34,0:17:04.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游  那个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.21,0:17:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.44,0:17:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  前辈  这也是为了前辈的将来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.23,0:17:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.23,0:17:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从山田那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.39,0:17:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.65,0:17:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  请一直保持小小的前辈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.11,0:17:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.87,0:17:33.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说要去考试了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.39,0:17:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤也是听小葵说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.75,0:17:42.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧  考试的话  不是就没有时间打工了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.78,0:17:46.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  是不是应该好好考虑一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.87,0:17:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.31,0:17:50.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤  果然在动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.13,0:17:54.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来是没有早或迟的  我不会阻止你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.47,0:17:57.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.97,0:18:04.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小白杨  我从高中以后就没有好好去上学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.40,0:18:08.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有时也会觉得该去好好接受教育会好一些
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.95,0:18:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我希望小白杨不要留下遗憾好好努力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.71,0:18:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会为小白杨加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.75,0:18:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  八千代姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.41,0:18:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛  这个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.74,0:18:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.61,0:18:31.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.23,0:18:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了  你在烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.17,0:18:41.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认真为将来考虑的话  打工并不是学生的本分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.48,0:18:43.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不用优先考虑的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.92,0:18:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然一直拼命工作的种岛离开让人感到痛心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.76,0:18:55.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这也是没有办法的事啊  要好好把握自己的将来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.29,0:18:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.37,0:19:05.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试的事情还很遥远  但是大家都叫我好好考虑将来的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.99,0:19:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.13,0:19:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松本
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.39,0:19:15.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放弃打工啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.59,0:19:17.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是成绩下降的话很困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.03,0:19:22.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我最喜欢大家了不想离开啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.74,0:19:25.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通来说等成绩下降了再来考虑如何
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.80,0:19:29.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.67,0:19:32.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样真的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.34,0:19:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田好寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.38,0:19:44.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以任性
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.69,0:19:46.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有前辈的瓦古娜莉亚…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.51,0:19:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.13,0:19:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家聚一起在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.22,0:19:52.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前…前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.75,0:19:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  果然还是别辞职了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.27,0:19:59.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会辞职哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.81,0:20:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之打工和学习我都会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.78,0:20:11.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果成绩下降了就减少出勤时间什么的  总之我会继续的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.84,0:20:13.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大家快工作  快工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.44,0:20:17.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么似乎变得积极乐观了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.19,0:20:18.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过真的太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.96,0:20:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  小白杨不在的话会非常寂寞的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.64,0:20:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.03,0:20:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  加油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.71,0:20:28.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  但是我不会走后门的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.75,0:20:29.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.55,0:20:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都给我快去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.42,0:20:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.56,0:20:35.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是告一段落了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.93,0:20:37.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.97,0:20:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.74,0:20:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点事情想和你谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.71,0:20:45.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请救救我  大家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.73,0:20:48.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.81,0:20:52.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  过分努力把盘子摔掉的前辈真可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.27,0:20:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盘子 报告表！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.52,0:20:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.47,0:21:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.83,0:21:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踮脚技能提高了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.93,0:21:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可悲的事件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.46,0:21:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.93,0:21:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不告诉她真相没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.77,0:21:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在本人知道前  还是这样默默守护她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.36,0:21:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.32,0:21:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.00,0:21:29.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  请你一直保持这样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.76,0:21:33.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游  我已经成长了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.73,0:21:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来你会吓一跳哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.48,0:21:36.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.18,0:21:40.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有察觉的前辈真可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.76,0:21:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.16,0:21:50.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.35,0:22:13.29,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}チラリと洩れる目論見は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.35,0:22:13.29,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}不经意间流露出的意图
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.61,0:22:16.90,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}上目づかいなり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.61,0:22:16.90,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是暧昧的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.70,0:22:20.52,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}スキマに忍び込みたいと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.70,0:22:20.52,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}想要见缝插针
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.85,0:22:23.57,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}タギってるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.85,0:22:23.57,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}内心卻激动不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.77,0:22:27.32,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつものように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.77,0:22:27.32,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}一起来装作
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.46,0:22:30.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}きどっていしまょ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.46,0:22:30.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}和以往一样的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:34.69,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}その距離もまた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:34.69,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}这份距离也
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.81,0:22:38.05,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いけてるんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.81,0:22:38.05,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}感觉还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:40.12,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:40.12,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.16,0:22:42.16,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.16,0:22:42.16,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:45.81,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}飛び道具は　胸に秘め
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:45.81,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}把爱之矢  藏在心里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.93,0:22:50.09,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつか大事な　日を待とう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.93,0:22:50.09,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}等待着重要的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.43,0:22:52.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}夢の地図なら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.43,0:22:52.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}到达梦想的地图
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.93,0:22:56.70,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}瞳の奥に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.93,0:22:56.70,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}就在你眼中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.86,0:23:00.33,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器は　二人のため
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.86,0:23:00.33,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器是两个人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.45,0:23:04.65,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつも磨いて　備えよう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.45,0:23:04.65,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}随时打磨好  以备不时之需
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.91,0:23:07.25,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}本気の恋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.91,0:23:07.25,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}真正的爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.43,0:23:10.95,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}それは突然
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.43,0:23:10.95,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是突然之间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.09,0:23:15.90,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}花が咲く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.09,0:23:15.90,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}开花结果

Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.25,0:23:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 今天居然碰上了那种倒霉事…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.71,0:23:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松本小姐 听说种岛小姐不打算辞职了 山田我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.17,0:23:38.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.67,0:23:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田我的家庭成员差点就要减少了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.83,0:23:42.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.28,0:23:46.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 且说 作为眼镜备货员
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.20,0:23:48.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松本小姐你也已经成为山田大家族的一员了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.53,0:23:51.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们一起向着戏剧化的多彩人生奔跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.37,0:23:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要呢 我要坚持走我的平凡人生之路啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.90,0:23:56.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戏剧化的人生才是人生啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.97,0:23:58.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平凡才是真正的人生啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.12,0:24:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松本小姐这人果然够怪的…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.81,0:24:08.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底长高了多少  得好好确认下
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.11,0:24:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(470,320)}以前的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.65,0:24:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(180,320)}今天的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.04,0:24:14.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有变化!
