[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: EDC,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,2,2,15,15,8,134
Style: title,华康娃娃体W5-A,35,&H0031a6db,&Hf0000000,&H00efefef,&H001f1f1f,-1,0,0,0,100,100,4,0.00,1,4,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPJ,A-OTF TakaHand Std B,23,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,15,15,4,128
Style: EDJ,DFHeiMedium-UN,17,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,4,2,8,15,15,8,128
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00ffffff,&H005955fd,&H00000000,&H00ffffff,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,10,8,13434
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: OPC,方正雅珠体简繁 DemiBold,26,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,15,15,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//ED
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,======================OPCN========================
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=====================OPJP==========================
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=====================EDJP==========================
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,======================OPCN========================
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.58,0:00:02.68,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.58,0:00:02.68,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.74,0:00:03.45,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.74,0:00:03.45,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.55,0:00:04.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.55,0:00:04.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.70,0:00:05.34,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.70,0:00:05.34,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.46,0:00:06.62,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.46,0:00:06.62,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.67,0:00:08.80,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.67,0:00:08.80,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しょう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.86,0:00:11.72,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.86,0:00:11.72,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.30,0:00:28.21,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.30,0:00:28.21,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心が大事です
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.31,0:00:29.25,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.31,0:00:29.25,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.29,0:00:32.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抑制住急躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.29,0:00:32.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}はやる心を抑えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.28,0:00:33.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.28,0:00:33.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモンモンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.16,0:00:36.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}做个平常人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.16,0:00:36.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}常識人になりましょう！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.22,0:00:37.07,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.22,0:00:37.07,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.17,0:00:40.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}难应付的人也会亲密起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.17,0:00:40.43,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ヤバイ人ならすぐなれる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.70,0:00:44.77,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}两人蔚蓝的Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.70,0:00:44.77,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}青い二人のヘブン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.86,0:00:47.61,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}变成小狗的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.86,0:00:47.61,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}子犬になる夢は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.84,0:00:48.57,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.84,0:00:48.57,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}レア
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.63,0:00:55.55,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}愉快灿烂地投影在脑海中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.63,0:00:55.55,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ユカイ特盛りの脳トレースして
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.59,0:00:58.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在天空盘旋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.59,0:00:58.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}空を　駆け回りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.32,0:01:02.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在摇曳思念下的果实
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.32,0:01:02.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}揺れる想いの下の　果肉には
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.66,0:01:06.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}充满恋爱的甜美
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.66,0:01:06.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}恋の美味しさだけ　ふくらんで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.21,0:01:10.54,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}如果有制作美味菜谱的野心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.21,0:01:10.54,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}凄いメニューを作ると　野望なら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.66,0:01:14.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}那就用心培育果实吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.66,0:01:14.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}まっとうに　フルーツ　はぐくみましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.82,0:01:16.03,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.82,0:01:16.03,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.15,0:01:16.86,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pa
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.15,0:01:16.86,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.90,0:01:18.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.90,0:01:18.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.13,0:01:18.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.13,0:01:18.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.79,0:01:20.05,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.79,0:01:20.05,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.17,0:01:22.06,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.17,0:01:22.06,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.10,0:01:22.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.10,0:01:22.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.86,0:01:23.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}努力修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.86,0:01:23.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}修行しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.01,0:01:24.70,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.01,0:01:24.70,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.76,0:01:26.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}拿出干劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.76,0:01:26.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}気合いしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.29,0:01:29.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.29,0:01:29.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…

Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.40,0:01:35.94,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(490,270)\fs25}「恋爱的BAD TUNING”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.92,0:01:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  真昼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.75,0:01:42.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.75,0:01:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去打工是不是要经过超市背后那条路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.50,0:01:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  往那边走是近路  基本上没什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.75,0:01:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个你知道吗  听说那边最近有痴汉出没哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.15,0:01:59.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是你打工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.80,0:02:03.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…嗯  那我还是不往那边走比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.64,0:02:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你往那边走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.85,0:02:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼去把痴汉打翻在地的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.61,0:02:13.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律和小桃  你们想表达什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.28,0:02:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某些时候  你那问题身体还是可以派得上用场的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.02,0:02:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌啦不要这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.93,0:02:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想去买东西的商店  没有男人的时间段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.17,0:02:26.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不都是我们告诉你的吗  调查这种事可是蛮辛苦的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.36,0:02:32.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…多谢你平时的帮助  但我…我也是很害怕痴汉的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.26,0:02:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是不行的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.97,0:02:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.06,0:02:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的啦  我会害怕地然后下不了手的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.44,0:02:42.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伊波的一击估计痴汉也…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.28,0:02:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  承受不住的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.12,0:02:46.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会承受不住呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.09,0:02:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  注意分寸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.66,0:02:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要当心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.57,0:02:58.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  两个人都好过分
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.84,0:03:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痴汉真的出现了该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.12,0:03:11.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不好完全没法抵抗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫不犹豫地猛烈一击  太给力了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.29,0:03:35.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会有能够接住我一拳的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.05,0:03:37.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不甘心！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.58,0:03:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…居然会觉得不甘心的我到底是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.27,0:03:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人就是痴汉啊  要是把他打倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.01,0:03:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连痴汉都会觉得我是个奇怪女人的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.69,0:03:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前最正确的是要像普通女孩一样做出反应
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.04,0:04:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  痴汉…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.06,0:04:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真失礼  我才不是痴汉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.70,0:04:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我才不是痴汉  我只是在寻找离家出走的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.72,0:04:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.84,0:04:22.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  据说这附近有人看到过她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.79,0:04:26.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我妹妹  她很有可能变装了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.74,0:04:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不放过任何路过的女性  想滴水不漏地调查
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.20,0:04:34.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这事我想秘密地进行  所以我甚至选择了在人烟稀少的地方采取行动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.48,0:04:37.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这明显是痴汉的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.86,0:04:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  总感觉这人…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  是山田啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.93,0:04:46.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人和山田长得很像
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.91,0:04:47.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼角的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.40,0:04:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来好像山田一直住在店的阁楼里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.57,0:04:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非这个人在寻找的妹妹就是山田吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.34,0:04:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.59,0:05:02.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.89,0:05:06.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…你叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.56,0:05:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山…山田…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.23,0:05:12.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是叫山田吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.23,0:05:14.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是…我叫山田
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.04,0:05:17.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫山田桐生  17岁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.50,0:05:19.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果…果然是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.46,0:05:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  是山田啊  那么下次再在这里相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.21,0:05:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫伊波
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.68,0:05:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她居然说要下次再见…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.90,0:05:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下…下…下次再见…伊波小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.94,0:05:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痴汉出没？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.57,0:05:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才听到客人这么说的  似乎就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.57,0:05:44.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.27,0:05:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看  我们这里打工的女孩子都还年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.76,0:05:50.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我很担心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.63,0:05:51.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.64,0:05:53.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们店的女孩子都没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.87,0:05:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.19,0:05:56.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先伊波是不用担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.86,0:05:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许应该反而担心下痴汉的状况吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.84,0:06:01.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你也不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.39,0:06:05.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤君  为什么不用担心我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.73,0:06:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…佐藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.03,0:06:11.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有种岛  那家伙是在另一种意义上需要担心一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.06,0:06:14.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉一拿到好吃的点心就会跟着走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.37,0:06:15.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.49,0:06:16.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他们无视了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.03,0:06:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这家伙也没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.56,0:06:21.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.53,0:06:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然离家出走  想必山田的家人也很担心她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.61,0:06:39.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田妹妹？你黏人家这么紧我不好干活哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.24,0:06:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  山田…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.47,0:06:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田举目无亲  但还处在想被溺爱的年龄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马先生  请做山田的哥哥来照顾我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.30,0:06:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田绝对是举目无亲的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.59,0:06:56.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要问她本人比较好  总之…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.59,0:07:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？有个叫山田的人在找他的妹妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.79,0:07:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  他会不会在找我们这里的山田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.47,0:07:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  绝对不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.71,0:07:11.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们这里的山田  她的名字已经确认过是伪名了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.21,0:07:12.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.67,0:07:15.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们这里的山田并不是真正的山田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.56,0:07:19.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以绝对不可能是那个叫山田的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.67,0:07:20.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.00,0:07:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然感觉很复杂  原来如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.08,0:07:25.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.33,0:07:32.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  真昼  昨天如何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.73,0:07:36.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到痴汉了吗？把他乱揍一顿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.81,0:07:39.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯见到了  是个同龄人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.25,0:07:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么自然而然地就认识上了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.25,0:07:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼和男人…而且还和痴汉？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.07,0:07:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还认识上了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.60,0:07:52.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼的男人运很差吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.88,0:07:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很担心  但我不会说出口哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.66,0:08:00.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因为很有趣  因为我们是朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.96,0:08:03.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  这不是挺好的嘛  你能习惯男生了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还继续在家庭餐馆打工的吧？明明有男人在的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.18,0:08:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.44,0:08:13.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工的地方都有什么样的男人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.38,0:08:17.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…很像不良少年的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.34,0:08:20.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有对于别人的个人情报都了若指掌的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.82,0:08:24.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把12岁以上的人当作人来看待的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.03,0:08:26.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些作为人都太奇怪了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.57,0:08:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后那个男人比痴汉还要可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.15,0:08:32.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  居然尽认识些这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.10,0:08:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼你的男人运好差
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.04,0:08:38.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心  但我不会说出口哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.23,0:08:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因为很有趣  因为我们是好朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.89,0:08:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是我搞错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.68,0:08:53.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还用了招人误会的说法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.40,0:08:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再遇到的话  一定要说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.38,0:09:04.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前阵子是在这里遇到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.32,0:09:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.57,0:09:10.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.03,0:09:10.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.81,0:09:11.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.42,0:09:13.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.37,0:09:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.56,0:09:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？山…是的我叫山田  山田桐生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.45,0:09:23.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思突然出拳打你  我下意识地就…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.74,0:09:24.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.15,0:09:27.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没关系  我是空手道部的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.96,0:09:28.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空手道部…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.13,0:09:30.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主将…姑且算是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.91,0:09:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说他相当强  所以即使我揍他他也可以防御住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.88,0:09:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真靠得住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.43,0:09:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我之前误以为见过你妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.74,0:09:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前想说打工店里的女孩子会不会是你妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.86,0:09:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.96,0:09:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊啊不是…好像完全是我搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.29,0:09:56.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.66,0:09:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没这回事  伊波不需要道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.67,0:10:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹的行踪其实无所谓了  真的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.37,0:10:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不是在找你妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.77,0:10:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不…反正只是个笨蛋妹妹…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.35,0:10:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你真的很担心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.90,0:10:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹很可爱吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.47,0:10:16.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.59,0:10:20.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  你果然很为妹妹着想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.12,0:10:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.42,0:10:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.37,0:10:27.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痴汉的事听说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.15,0:10:28.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痴汉？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.98,0:10:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说痴汉在超市后面那条路出没
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.96,0:10:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个稍微有点阴暗的小道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.48,0:10:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那条路是小伊来这里的必经之路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.46,0:10:42.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点担心  去接她一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.94,0:10:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  我倒反而有点担心痴汉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.41,0:10:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌  那我自己去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.21,0:10:55.30,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}痴汉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.43,0:10:55.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊救救我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.25,0:11:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等前辈  我很担心  所以由我去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.47,0:11:01.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.82,0:11:04.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.38,0:11:06.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好  注意安全哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.21,0:11:13.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.80,0:11:16.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游对伊波越来越好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.68,0:11:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的他的话肯定会果断拒绝的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.60,0:11:22.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得也是  要是可以这样一直好下去就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.85,0:11:25.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要不被伊波揍就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.52,0:11:28.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵也这么觉得吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.49,0:11:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田还是求黏黏糊糊圈圈转转的剧情展开
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.78,0:11:34.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黏黏糊糊还要圈圈转转？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.89,0:11:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你还是放弃用这种办法找妹妹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.55,0:11:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊…伊波小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.84,0:11:43.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.94,0:11:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不是本地人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.42,0:11:51.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说是要你帮忙  还是怎么说呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.16,0:11:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能陪我一起找妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.98,0:12:01.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么办 我应付不了男人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.06,0:12:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 他似乎很困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.10,0:12:09.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我可以的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.61,0:12:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请陪我一起！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.51,0:12:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要说两次…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.40,0:12:18.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是昨天和你说过的 我打工地方的地图
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.59,0:12:22.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 伊波小姐真是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.74,0:12:26.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被男生感谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.82,0:12:29.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是这人能防住我的攻击让我比较安心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.47,0:12:30.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但能这样好好和他说话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.26,0:12:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是我的男性恐惧症好多了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.81,0:12:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这全部是小鸟游的功劳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.11,0:12:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是命运吧 伊波
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.26,0:12:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是命运什么的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.97,0:12:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是命运啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.45,0:12:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那如果有什么的话 就到那个餐厅来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.07,0:12:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.37,0:13:09.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游 欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.01,0:13:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？没和小伊一起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.73,0:13:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我中途折回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.52,0:13:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.79,0:13:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来我就没有义务要去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.59,0:13:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.71,0:13:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈真温柔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.35,0:13:28.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我也得换衣服开始工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.46,0:13:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.02,0:13:37.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游的表情好恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.41,0:14:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.94,0:14:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.18,0:14:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…羞鸟游最近好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.92,0:14:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.51,0:14:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.71,0:14:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.19,0:14:34.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游他…羞鸟游他……
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.63,0:14:36.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.86,0:14:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.62,0:14:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.56,0:14:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.56,0:14:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来不像是没事的样子…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.01,0:14:46.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.01,0:14:51.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事的 前辈好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.05,0:14:57.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前总是用手温柔地抚摸我头上最舒服的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.09,0:15:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在的抚摸却很粗鲁 很粗鲁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.23,0:15:04.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.96,0:15:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常的抚摸都是那么高水准的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.33,0:15:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 的确是很奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.43,0:15:16.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪 自从看到那一幕后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.03,0:15:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得不能平静下来 很焦躁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.09,0:15:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为这和自己辛苦训练的狗跑去亲近别人是一样的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还跑去彻夜研读关于狗的书
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.45,0:15:32.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想想伊波她根本不是狗啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.93,0:15:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不用仔细想也知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.74,0:15:39.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.22,0:15:41.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.55,0:15:46.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然应该鼓励他一下吧 作为领班
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.35,0:15:51.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如把杏子姐的照片分给他之类
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.43,0:15:57.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者让他摸一摸巨型杏子姐人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.64,0:16:00.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轰 这反而会让他更消沉的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.63,0:16:06.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那山田我就当小鸟游先生可爱的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.39,0:16:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他打气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.49,0:16:09.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免了 你给我干活去！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.24,0:16:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真困扰呢 要不要叫杏子姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.95,0:16:19.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马 你知道什么内情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.27,0:16:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知……才不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.79,0:16:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.59,0:16:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.71,0:16:27.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.03,0:16:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情变得那么有趣了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.47,0:16:36.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.10,0:16:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好工作的话 来了不就没意义了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.73,0:16:50.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就给你一个这东西 精神起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.66,0:17:07.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.70,0:17:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐 把我放上去也没用的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.21,0:17:15.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐…不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.61,0:17:16.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不想承认
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.29,0:17:18.49,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}别闹了…谁来救我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.17,0:17:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那一幕后之所以烦躁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.29,0:17:23.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.69,0:17:25.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉伊波被夺走了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.23,0:17:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挨伊波的揍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.33,0:17:31.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在照顾伊波的这段时间里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.69,0:17:33.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.83,0:17:37.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游你别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.26,0:17:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游 很危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.38,0:17:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游 你冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.68,0:17:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.10,0:17:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游 振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.77,0:17:59.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪里不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.36,0:18:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思让大家担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.02,0:18:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…今天 就今天先让我早退吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.04,0:18:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.07,0:18:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被揍太多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.19,0:18:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被揍太多变的奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.59,0:18:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被伊波揍多了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.46,0:18:26.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是我的错？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.35,0:18:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说我真的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.94,0:18:45.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…怎么会…怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.08,0:18:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.11,0:18:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.26,0:18:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工早退了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.34,0:18:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚种岛打电话过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.80,0:18:57.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说哥哥你状况不好 很担心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.18,0:18:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荠啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.12,0:18:59.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.35,0:19:02.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.60,0:19:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.34,0:19:05.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.50,0:19:08.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.63,0:19:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个M吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.61,0:19:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？！不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.49,0:19:26.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.34,0:19:28.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话先说在前头
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.13,0:19:32.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是纯粹的喜欢小东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.79,0:19:34.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是M！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.01,0:19:40.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是M 所以不会因为被揍而有快感的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.91,0:19:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…你不用说两遍我也知道哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.44,0:19:46.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我感到愉快的只有小玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.72,0:19:50.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 是平时的小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.54,0:19:52.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是M！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.93,0:19:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说第三回了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.16,0:19:57.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎变精神了  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.96,0:20:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游似乎自己得出奇怪的结论了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:23.29,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}チラリと洩れる目論見は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:23.29,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}不经意间流露出的意图
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.61,0:22:26.90,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}上目づかいなり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.61,0:22:26.90,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是暧昧的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.70,0:22:30.52,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}スキマに忍び込みたいと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.70,0:22:30.52,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}想要见缝插针
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.85,0:22:33.57,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}タギってるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.85,0:22:33.57,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}内心卻激动不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.77,0:22:37.32,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつものように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.77,0:22:37.32,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}一起来装作
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.46,0:22:40.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}きどっていしまょ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.46,0:22:40.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}和以往一样的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:44.69,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}その距離もまた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:44.69,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}这份距离也
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.81,0:22:48.05,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いけてるんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.81,0:22:48.05,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}感觉还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.17,0:22:50.12,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.17,0:22:50.12,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.16,0:22:52.16,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.16,0:22:52.16,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.32,0:22:55.81,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}飛び道具は　胸に秘め
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.32,0:22:55.81,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}把爱之矢  藏在心里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.93,0:23:00.09,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつか大事な　日を待とう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.93,0:23:00.09,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}等待着重要的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.43,0:23:02.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}夢の地図なら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.43,0:23:02.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}到达梦想的地图
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.93,0:23:06.70,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}瞳の奥に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.93,0:23:06.70,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}就在你眼中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.86,0:23:10.33,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器は　二人のため
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.86,0:23:10.33,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器是两个人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.45,0:23:14.65,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつも磨いて　備えよう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.45,0:23:14.65,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}随时打磨好  以备不时之需
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.91,0:23:17.25,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}本気の恋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.91,0:23:17.25,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}真正的爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.43,0:23:20.95,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}それは突然
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.43,0:23:20.95,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是突然之间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.09,0:23:25.90,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}花が咲く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.09,0:23:25.90,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}开花结果

Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.10,0:21:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梢姐 再来一杯啤酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.56,0:21:38.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.01,0:21:43.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有其它种类的酒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.04,0:21:46.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但酒很美味而且女孩子们也很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.86,0:21:48.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.83,0:21:49.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.07,0:21:50.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.27,0:21:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人困扰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.04,0:21:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在客人少还算没事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.51,0:22:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为领班我得说说她才行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.89,0:22:05.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个 客人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.80,0:22:08.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要独占我们的服务员
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.23,0:22:09.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.49,0:22:11.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.30,0:22:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是服务员了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.48,0:22:19.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人 随意更改服务员的服饰会让我们困扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.47,0:22:22.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是为了这间店才做的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.06,0:22:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次来制服都一样很无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.77,0:22:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点点改进各种地方对于服务行业来说是必要的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.65,0:22:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 我预备了很多衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.22,0:22:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵的是小猫对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.27,0:22:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑喵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.80,0:22:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛姐的是小狗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.58,0:22:44.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.26,0:22:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梢姐为什么会有这种衣服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.10,0:22:54.11,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}纯粹而天真的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.06,0:22:52.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人是有各种各样的需要的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.11,0:23:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.02,0:23:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不感觉挺不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.76,0:23:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一份
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.00,0:23:24.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是梢姐干的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.11,0:23:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早…早上好 小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这……个 虽然是梢姐借给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.91,0:23:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.71,0:23:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果再年轻个十年的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.31,0:23:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得知失散多年的妹妹在吉原的烟花巷
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.31,0:23:42.48,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}注：吉原的烟花巷，妓院集中的街道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.60,0:23:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 女孩子 女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.82,0:23:48.65,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(360,320)}第八道菜\N“呜呼、妹妹哟”
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.37,0:23:48.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 妹妹 妹妹
