[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,华康娃娃体W5-A,31,&H0034b1ee,&Hf0000000,&H00ffffff,&Hff0f0f0f,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPC,方正雅珠体简繁 DemiBold,31,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,15,15,6,134
Style: OPJ,A-OTF TakaHand Std B,28,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,15,15,4,128
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,33,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,10,8,134
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hf0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.39,0:00:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.57,0:00:44.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 伊波 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.50,0:00:49.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波 很遗憾地告诉你 已经没工作可以做了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.54,0:00:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家店果然要关门了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.66,0:00:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为没有客人 所以没事可做而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.42,0:01:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有客人倒是常有的事 但就算如此也还是有什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.17,0:01:03.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游一个人全部做完了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.81,0:01:04.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.66,0:01:05.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为很闲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.00,0:01:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真过分 起码也该留下我的份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.31,0:01:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏我这么辛苦地工作…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.22,0:01:14.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 伊波 这种时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.85,0:01:19.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不该偷懒 而是应该寻找自己能为店里做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.39,0:01:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力思考自行找活干啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.42,0:01:23.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓工作就是这么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.35,0:01:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得杏子今天超帅啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.57,0:01:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像店长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.91,0:01:29.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是店长！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.54,0:01:32.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是 只有嘴上说得伟大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:33.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.75,0:01:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.95,0:01:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.07,0:01:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.47,0:01:42.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安 白杨酱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.55,0:01:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.05,0:01:47.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安 今天也要加油喔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.49,0:01:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 今天也一样小巧玲珑又可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.07,0:01:53.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 佐藤 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.55,0:01:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 种岛 今天也很小巧玲珑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.50,0:01:57.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.77,0:02:02.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 来客人了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.11,0:02:18.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临 欢迎来到Wagnaria
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.08,0:02:23.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.11,0:02:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问点这些就好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.54,0:02:28.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.09,0:02:35.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 伊波
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.45,0:02:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7号桌的客人…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.61,0:02:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 全是男人呢 放心吧 尽管交给山田吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.34,0:02:46.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.90,0:03:01.82,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,300)}{\fad(500,500)}1品目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.90,0:03:01.82,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,335)}{\fad(500,500)}白杨的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.79,0:03:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(540,350)}以前的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.63,0:03:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,350)}现在的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.52,0:03:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道已经长不高了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.71,0:03:18.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算成为了大人 一辈子也都是这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.73,0:03:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.12,0:03:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么精神呢 我很担心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.92,0:03:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟 之前就一直在想了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.02,0:03:34.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸比自己年长之人的头不是很失礼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.08,0:03:36.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.11,0:03:42.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明这么小巧可爱 我可不想把前辈当做年长之人来对待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.78,0:03:43.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子都不想
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.86,0:03:44.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.92,0:03:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 一辈子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.57,0:03:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟你这个大笨蛋！ 绝交！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.46,0:03:55.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 前辈 为什么会生气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.09,0:04:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白杨 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.43,0:04:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代 小游鸟真过分啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.58,0:04:19.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 小鸟游对你做了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.83,0:04:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又笑话我个子小巧可爱 还摸我头呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.15,0:04:25.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 很过分吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.41,0:04:27.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是一直一直都是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.24,0:04:28.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎每次见面都是喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.29,0:04:30.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代你觉得如何呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.24,0:04:33.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是被摸着说可爱吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.35,0:04:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.82,0:04:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样会死啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.11,0:04:41.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会死吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.40,0:04:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.87,0:04:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.45,0:04:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.52,0:04:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.71,0:04:51.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于种岛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.05,0:04:55.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要老说她个子小比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她本人也挺在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.41,0:05:01.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？明明那么娇小可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.52,0:05:03.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说嘛…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.15,0:05:07.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有各式各样的自卑情结啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.12,0:05:09.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于女孩子来说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.66,0:05:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,个子小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.67,0:05:14.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸…胸部小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.81,0:05:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就算周围的人说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.44,0:05:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“小小的更可爱啊 大的反而不方便啊”之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.76,0:05:25.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但讨厌的东西就是讨厌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.04,0:05:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波 你就好像在说自己一样…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.92,0:05:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外地很替同事着想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.37,0:05:33.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然老是打我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.04,0:05:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.82,0:05:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 你的男性恐惧症完全没有治愈的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.48,0:05:42.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.21,0:05:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.45,0:05:46.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着忍耐一次
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.27,0:05:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.33,0:05:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.37,0:05:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算一次也好 只要能忍住揍人的冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.24,0:05:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到那个时候 伊波应该也能成长一个阶段了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.52,0:05:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.43,0:05:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会忍忍看的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.34,0:06:03.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在忍了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.95,0:06:06.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的事先放一边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.82,0:06:09.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你去和种岛道个歉比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.31,0:06:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在这里堂堂正正的吃东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.10,0:06:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 谁都不会认为在这里若无其事地吃着圣代的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.78,0:06:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会是店长
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.65,0:06:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪门子的自信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.25,0:06:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔？伊波还是老样子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.75,0:06:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然比一开始要好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.30,0:06:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最近也变得能若无其事的跟我说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.32,0:06:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然被揍这点没什么变化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.76,0:06:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.98,0:06:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 下次要搞的某活动的赠品
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.62,0:06:55.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.58,0:06:57.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那么恶心啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.67,0:06:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.43,0:06:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.52,0:07:02.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然无差别揍男人的伊波也有错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.67,0:07:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小鸟游的变态行为也是很够呛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.00,0:07:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢娇小的东西哪里变态了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.80,0:07:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说哪里？哪里都是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.61,0:07:13.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 自从在这里打工以来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.77,0:07:16.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是和家人以外的年长者扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.46,0:07:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了各式各样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.54,0:07:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心里娇小的东西已经基本…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.51,0:07:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太棒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.05,0:07:24.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你恶化的不轻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.90,0:07:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 店长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.12,0:07:28.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到学姐了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.47,0:07:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.68,0:07:32.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白杨酱刚才去办公室了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.16,0:07:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 杏子姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.80,0:07:36.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是巧克力圣代哟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.81,0:07:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是八千代
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.35,0:07:39.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大一份…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.09,0:07:43.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领班 请不要给店长喂食
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.40,0:07:45.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我难道是猴山的猴子？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.30,0:07:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系啦 这就是我的存在价值所在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.28,0:07:51.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.24,0:07:53.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么对不对的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.36,0:07:55.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是吃这么多没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.94,0:07:58.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比上周重了300克哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.91,0:08:00.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管它啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.48,0:08:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是怕胖 还吃什么甜食
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.76,0:08:06.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你连重了多少克都知道啊 相马先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.60,0:08:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田 你在干什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.76,0:08:15.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田什么都没干
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.23,0:08:17.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.02,0:08:22.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就给我看看你藏在身后的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.61,0:08:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.88,0:08:25.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是少女的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.93,0:08:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 音尾在窗外
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.43,0:08:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欺骗少女了呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.67,0:08:36.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.28,0:08:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 小鸟游你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.44,0:08:43.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田今天身体不舒服 要早退了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.23,0:08:46.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.11,0:08:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你和小鸟游绝交了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.02,0:08:59.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 你怎么知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.48,0:09:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉他的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.94,0:09:01.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.19,0:09:03.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要绝交啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.22,0:09:08.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我明明比小游鸟年纪大
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.40,0:09:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总被他当成小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.95,0:09:11.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我可爱啊 娇小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.03,0:09:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奢侈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.99,0:09:18.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我…从来没被人说过可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.84,0:09:20.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.89,0:09:23.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你也不想被人这么说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.51,0:09:26.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤你的发型很可爱喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.88,0:09:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要奇怪的夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.43,0:09:31.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛 你要更成熟一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.58,0:09:33.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.09,0:09:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被后辈说了娇小可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.91,0:09:40.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少有点不爽但也要忍着反而随便对方怎么挑衅都不动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.75,0:09:41.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是大人的应对方式啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.52,0:09:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人的应对方式…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.96,0:09:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去不错 就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.49,0:09:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去和好了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.48,0:09:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.51,0:09:53.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.01,0:09:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个小孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.03,0:09:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真善良啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.84,0:09:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你仔细想想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.65,0:10:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果放任他们这样吵下去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.42,0:10:04.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是种岛打工辞职了怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.78,0:10:05.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辞职的话？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.88,0:10:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带着连小鸟游也有可能不干了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.02,0:10:11.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话谁来照顾伊波？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.48,0:10:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望种岛接下来也要被小鸟游继续疼爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.09,0:10:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果继续被疼爱而且周围相安无事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.39,0:10:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就没有任何问题
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.84,0:10:23.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.42,0:10:26.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.43,0:10:32.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟 摸我摸我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.21,0:10:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个可爱的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.51,0:10:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.66,0:10:52.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐… 忍耐一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.76,0:10:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.66,0:10:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始变暖和了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.49,0:11:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.79,0:11:03.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然比起大冷天还是暖和点比较好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.81,0:11:04.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.37,0:11:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个冬天
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.51,0:11:11.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲在家里的小孩子小猫小狗小虫子等等都会跑到外面来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.81,0:11:14.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就是满世界都是小东西 真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.51,0:11:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 有虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.26,0:11:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫子？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.28,0:11:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害怕那种东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.36,0:11:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 普通的女孩子都害怕虫子的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.74,0:11:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的女孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.48,0:11:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 快想点办法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.27,0:11:36.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是虫子也只是潮虫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.04,0:11:38.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在本州 蟑螂…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.27,0:11:39.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.44,0:11:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐 有虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.66,0:11:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.14,0:11:49.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代 休息时间到了 和伊波交换一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.38,0:11:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.61,0:11:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真傻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.19,0:11:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去休息啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.32,0:12:07.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤啊 八千代的心又被店长俘获了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.31,0:12:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代她怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:16.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 因为她说有虫子所以我就啪的一下打了下去…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.86,0:12:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.33,0:12:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐 小游鸟是不是因为你打死了小东西所以在生气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.69,0:12:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀…杀…杀人凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.32,0:12:40.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没杀过人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.97,0:12:44.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 店长你做了跟杀死前辈一样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.91,0:12:45.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.71,0:12:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把跟前辈一样 又小又可爱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.38,0:12:53.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把虫子杀死就等于把前辈杀死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.55,0:12:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和虫子是同等级的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.39,0:12:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命是平等的 前辈的生命和虫子的生命是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.58,0:13:02.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的话虽然很伟大 不过感觉很伤人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.05,0:13:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快向前辈道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.67,0:13:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小游鸟 你稍微冷静一下 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.22,0:13:10.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.30,0:13:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要道歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.87,0:13:13.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像做了什么对不起你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.29,0:13:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我更加伤心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.73,0:13:20.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐 你还是先向小游鸟道歉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.13,0:13:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.89,0:13:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你应该没有错 但为了平息这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.45,0:13:29.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没错的话就不道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.88,0:13:36.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.77,0:13:40.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐 忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.80,0:13:46.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 在那之前 我觉得你把种岛比做虫子是很过分的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.52,0:13:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了 连虫子都不如的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.38,0:13:52.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然说我连虫子都不如 太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.59,0:13:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟 不能死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.87,0:14:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.15,0:14:05.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 感觉完全进入了忘我的境地
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.76,0:14:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.23,0:14:11.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事再说下去就变得很麻烦了 这个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.71,0:14:12.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.03,0:14:16.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 把这里收拾一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.52,0:14:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.97,0:14:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…小游鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.74,0:14:23.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再把我和虫子混为一谈了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.76,0:14:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 前辈当然比虫子要可爱多了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.00,0:14:29.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.19,0:14:33.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说别拿我跟虫子对比啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.83,0:14:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连虫子都不如
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.69,0:14:50.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.30,0:14:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到又要在那个报告表上写名字
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.19,0:14:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田我的心情就很低落
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.31,0:15:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.81,0:15:10.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还…还差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.82,0:15:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点 还差一点 还差一点喔 种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.84,0:15:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 小游鸟 是我说要帮小葵写的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.50,0:15:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样 也是接受了他人的好意而自己不去做的山田的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.81,0:15:34.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.13,0:15:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失落中的前辈比平时还要小巧可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.33,0:15:44.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 山田你也稍微学习一下如何
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.09,0:15:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田也在努力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.15,0:15:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 报告表上基本上没有种岛的名字 真是厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.17,0:15:55.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的 前辈无论何时都很努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.79,0:15:57.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为构不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.30,0:16:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 一般来说这个位置太高了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.63,0:16:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是山田我 往那上面写字都会觉得很累的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.11,0:16:06.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听你这么一说…还真是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.73,0:16:08.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩在干什么  给我工作去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.72,0:16:10.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 店长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.67,0:16:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个报告表的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.11,0:16:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是太高了点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.34,0:16:17.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛说那样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.82,0:16:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈这么说了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.26,0:16:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京子 就这么贴着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.06,0:16:25.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你构不着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.53,0:16:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想努力工作尽量不往上面写名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.30,0:16:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踮起脚的话个子也会长高一点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.18,0:16:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且总觉得有种真拿下来了我就输了的感觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.81,0:16:34.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么值得赞赏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.69,0:16:39.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 虽然因为个子小有很多不方便的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.83,0:16:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过种岛她也有在好好干活
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.44,0:16:43.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游 也帮她一把吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.65,0:16:46.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长在帮前辈说话！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.62,0:16:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就弄的再高一些
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.06,0:16:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.94,0:16:52.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田也构不着的话 不就能体现出我的可爱之处了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.17,0:16:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有小鸟游 也帮山田一把吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.91,0:17:00.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.24,0:17:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是水性笔 所以不要紧的 给我反省一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.63,0:17:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了 那两个人怎么回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.21,0:17:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.28,0:17:21.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.12,0:17:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连虫子都不如
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.47,0:17:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明下定决心今天不动用暴力的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.74,0:17:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是把人打了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.75,0:17:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是连虫子都不如的存在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.06,0:17:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊…伊波 那不是这样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.59,0:17:43.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游他很动摇 所以才说出那种奇怪的话啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.75,0:17:51.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游喜欢娇小的东西 所以虫子的死导致他内心动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.03,0:17:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那时娇小的我就正好在他的旁边…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.12,0:17:57.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我才不小呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.97,0:18:12.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.73,0:18:16.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.51,0:18:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 那要拿个垫脚椅吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.40,0:18:22.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我构得着啦 我今年可是长高了3毫米喔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.69,0:18:24.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那得长几百年啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.03,0:18:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 坦率说出来的话我会帮你拿下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.97,0:18:28.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我构得着啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:32.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京子她也是相信我所以才把这个贴在高处的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.93,0:18:45.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 种岛 你心里也明白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.30,0:18:49.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 佐藤连你也这样欺负我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.20,0:18:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啊 虽然一眼看起来我像是无理取闹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.32,0:18:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但透过踮起脚 向上延展 你的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.18,0:18:58.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能长高吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.48,0:18:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脖子会累
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.57,0:19:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛  在意身高而胡思乱想是不好的习惯喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.94,0:19:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.92,0:19:13.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就没有能让我长高的方法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.09,0:19:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天我都喝牛奶的说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.56,0:19:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我告诉你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.78,0:19:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然个子也不是很高 不过...嘛 补钙可是基础啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.54,0:19:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喝了很多牛奶喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.27,0:19:36.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真了不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.55,0:19:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有蛋白质呀锌 镁也是需要的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.52,0:19:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马真是博学多才啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 可以吃烤干的壁虎喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.56,0:19:50.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她居然信了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.00,0:19:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壁虎…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.32,0:19:53.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.24,0:19:56.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤你也吃过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.28,0:19:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.72,0:20:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西当然吃过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.79,0:20:12.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟 听我说 听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.41,0:20:16.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 看起来心情不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.34,0:20:20.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马和佐藤告诉了我能长高的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.98,0:20:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吃一堆壁虎喔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.02,0:20:31.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道是怎么一回事 前辈好像又被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.87,0:20:36.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 相马
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.99,0:20:38.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是不是向前辈灌输了奇怪的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.03,0:20:40.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.19,0:20:43.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱着希望总是好事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.02,0:20:46.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且经一事也能让种岛长一智啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.94,0:20:50.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是真的长高了那可如何是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.56,0:20:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.16,0:20:53.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太扯了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.13,0:20:55.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.91,0:20:57.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个 给我工作去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.80,0:20:59.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能偷懒喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:31.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.72,0:21:37.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤 明天我就去买壁虎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.91,0:21:41.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油的 那明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.65,0:21:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.09,0:21:50.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.56,0:21:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.14,0:21:58.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.15,0:22:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我走了 辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.96,0:22:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.76,0:22:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.07,0:22:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.72,0:22:05.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.41,0:22:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 又不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.31,0:22:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想着今天一定要目送相马回家时的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.91,0:22:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田 记得把门关好喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.50,0:22:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.63,0:22:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.79,0:22:25.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们也回去吧 伊波
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.16,0:22:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.98,0:22:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连虫子都不如…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.98,0:22:39.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.98,0:22:39.08,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.14,0:22:39.85,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.14,0:22:39.85,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.95,0:22:41.06,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.95,0:22:41.06,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:41.74,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:41.74,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.86,0:22:43.02,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.86,0:22:43.02,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:45.20,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:45.20,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しょう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.26,0:22:48.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.26,0:22:48.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.70,0:23:04.61,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.70,0:23:04.61,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心が大事です
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.71,0:23:05.65,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.71,0:23:05.65,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.69,0:23:08.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抑制住急躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.69,0:23:08.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}はやる心を抑えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.68,0:23:09.52,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.68,0:23:09.52,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモンモンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:12.52,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}做个平常人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:12.52,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}常識人になりましょう！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.62,0:23:13.47,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.62,0:23:13.47,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.57,0:23:16.83,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}难应付的人也会亲密起来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.57,0:23:16.83,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ヤバイ人ならすぐなれる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.10,0:23:21.17,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}两人蔚蓝的Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.10,0:23:21.17,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}青い二人のヘブン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.26,0:23:24.01,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}变成小狗的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.26,0:23:24.01,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}子犬になる夢は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.24,0:23:24.97,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.24,0:23:24.97,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}レア
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.03,0:23:31.95,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}愉快灿烂地投影在脑海中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.03,0:23:31.95,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ユカイ特盛りの脳トレースして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.99,0:23:34.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在天空盘旋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.99,0:23:34.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}空を　駆け回りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.72,0:23:38.96,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在摇曳思念下的果实
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.72,0:23:38.96,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}揺れる想いの下の　果肉には
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.06,0:23:42.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}充满恋爱的甜美
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.06,0:23:42.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}恋の美味しさだけ　ふくらんで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.61,0:23:46.94,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}如果有制作美味菜谱的野心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.61,0:23:46.94,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}凄いメニューを作ると　野望なら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.06,0:23:51.06,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}那就用心培育果实吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.06,0:23:51.06,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}まっとうに　フルーツ　はぐくみましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.22,0:23:52.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.22,0:23:52.43,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.55,0:23:53.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pa
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.55,0:23:53.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.30,0:23:54.44,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想紧紧咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.30,0:23:54.44,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.53,0:23:55.07,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.53,0:23:55.07,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.19,0:23:56.45,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想吓唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.19,0:23:56.45,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.57,0:23:58.46,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}现在还是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.57,0:23:58.46,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.50,0:23:59.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.50,0:23:59.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.26,0:24:00.31,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}努力修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.26,0:24:00.31,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}修行しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.41,0:24:01.10,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.41,0:24:01.10,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.16,0:24:02.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}拿出干劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.16,0:24:02.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}気合いしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.69,0:24:05.62,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.69,0:24:05.62,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…

Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.47,0:24:10.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是魔法少女 白杨
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.39,0:24:11.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全面四射爱的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.29,0:24:14.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白杨 啦啦啦 啦啦啦 啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.31,0:24:18.03,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}2品目\N“理想的家族计划”
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.76,0:24:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白杨 白杨 杨杨...
