[Script Info]
Title:未来日记
Original Script:四魂制作组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Chinese,仓耳今楷04 W04,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000040,&H80000040,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,5,5,8,1
Style: Staff,仓耳今楷04 W04,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000080,&H00000040,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,5,5,8,1
Style: Title,仓耳今楷04 W04,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,30,30,30,1
Style: note,仓耳今楷04 W04,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004F2700,&HF0804000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,4,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-Ch,仓耳今楷04 W04,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00663300,&H00C08000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,5,5,3,1
Style: OP-JP,UDDigiKyokasho StdN M,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H006441B4,&H00BCBCF5,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,5,5,3,1
Style: ED-JP,@UDDigiKyokasho StdN M,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006441B4,&HF0BCBCF5,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,1,0,5,30,30,10,1
Style: ED-Ch,@仓耳今楷04 W04,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00663300,&H00C08000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,1,0,5,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.10,0:01:51.10,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}本字幕由四魂制作组(snm.5d6d.net)制作\N仅供交流试看 如喜欢本作品请支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.10,0:01:51.10,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2\fad(130,130)}翻译：泥浆；时间/后期：铁碎牙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.97,0:00:37.80,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}The girl with the sharp thorn in her flesh
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.81,0:00:40.16,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}I meet you at your story
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.24,0:00:45.33,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Behind the hatred there lies a murderous love
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.39,0:00:50.66,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Do you kill your friends, if you can fulfill your wish?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.67,0:00:53.24,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Can you die for someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.31,0:00:56.39,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}They are synonymous words
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.40,0:01:01.42,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Life is a game It's a survival That's right! How do you start?
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.45,0:01:07.13,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Time and Space It's a crossroad through a gate! Where do yo go?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.14,0:01:09.68,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}You seek eternal breath
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.69,0:01:11.79,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Why do you need to live?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.80,0:01:16.85,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}We don't know when this world came into being
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.86,0:01:18.96,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}We are the timeleaper
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.97,0:01:22.11,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Nothing's gonna change with you in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.12,0:01:24.94,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Everything will be decided by the rules
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.95,0:01:29.83,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Oh, We are traveling the past and the future through love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.84,0:01:30.52,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Break out!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.54,0:01:35.33,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Let's dial back all the pains and we will be born again
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.34,0:01:38.07,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}I wanna see the stars with you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.10,0:01:41.19,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}Over the miracle
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.20,0:01:47.80,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}It's not a Dead END
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.97,0:00:37.80,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}浑身长刺的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.81,0:00:40.16,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}我与你在故事中相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.24,0:00:45.33,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}敌意的背后是致命的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.39,0:00:50.66,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}你是否会为达成愿望而杀害朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.67,0:00:53.24,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}你是否愿为某人而死？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.31,0:00:56.39,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}两者同义
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.40,0:01:01.42,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}人生是场生存游戏没错！你如何开场？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.45,0:01:07.13,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}穿越时空之门的十字路口！你所向何方？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.14,0:01:09.68,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}寻求永生的你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.69,0:01:11.79,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}为何要活下去？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.80,0:01:16.85,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}我们不知道这个世界诞生于何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.86,0:01:18.96,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}我们是时间穿越者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.97,0:01:22.11,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}世界不会因你而变
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.12,0:01:24.94,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}万物皆有定数
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.95,0:01:29.83,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}哦 我们的爱穿越过去与未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.84,0:01:30.52,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}爆发！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.54,0:01:35.33,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}回拨所有的痛苦 我们将重获新生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.34,0:01:38.07,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}我想和你去看星
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.10,0:01:41.19,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}超越奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.20,0:01:47.80,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)}这不是Dead END
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.71,0:20:58.02,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}あとどれくらい失えば
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.34,0:21:03.25,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}高鳴る鼓動許される？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.26,0:21:14.28,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}会いたくて涙 溢れるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.29,0:21:20.10,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}全ては未来を繋ぐ鍵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.12,0:21:27.59,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}崩れる身体に絆感じて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.60,0:21:39.80,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(30,180)}もう一度君を守ると誓う
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.71,0:20:58.02,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}还要失去多少
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.34,0:21:03.25,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}激烈的鼓动才被饶恕？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.26,0:21:14.28,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}想见面 眼泪涌出
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.29,0:21:20.10,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}一切是通往未来的钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.12,0:21:27.59,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}在崩坏的身体中感受着羁绊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.60,0:21:39.80,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(180,180)\pos(610,180)}再一次宣誓要保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.09,0:00:03.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半分之月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.04,0:00:08.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮的部分和暗的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.59,0:00:13.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.44,0:00:19.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.34,0:01:55.28,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(310,250)\fr-19\fad(600,0)}重置
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.90,0:01:59.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死9th 她果然很碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.64,0:02:03.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过嘛 没问题啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.20,0:02:06.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也有你的雪辉日记
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.83,0:02:07.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.76,0:02:12.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以每10分钟预知1st的动向 要抢先他们容易多了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.22,0:02:11.75,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(30,200)\fr10}7/28  2:30\N阿雪追到三周目来了！\N真高兴！！\N7/28  2:40\N阿雪带着三周目的我逃跑了！\N我要追上去保护阿雪！\N7/28  2:50\N阿雪在樱见中学跟9th\N还有三周目的我一起！\N我也要快点赶过去杀死9th！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.10,0:02:13.20,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(300,240)\fr10\fs30}真高兴！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.70,0:02:18.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 快点追呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.82,0:02:19.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.45,0:02:25.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不对 跟二周目世界的阿雪的关系已经完结了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.12,0:02:29.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是现在的我的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.34,0:02:33.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二周目的阿雪说不杀我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.20,0:02:37.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我不杀他的话一切就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.95,0:02:40.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪和我 一切都会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.88,0:02:47.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 阿雪如果放弃我的话 那我就不放弃阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.88,0:02:54.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟阿雪说再见 然后去三周目世界的阿雪的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.29,0:02:59.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要永远永远跟阿雪在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.59,0:03:02.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.06,0:03:06.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救护车…是阿雪叫的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.58,0:03:10.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.28,0:03:12.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.16,0:03:13.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.75,0:03:12.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吗 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.84,0:03:15.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到医院的联络回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.93,0:03:17.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤者在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.87,0:03:21.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是妈妈又做出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.47,0:03:24.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 妈妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.28,0:03:29.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…由乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.85,0:03:33.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃…你…长高了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.44,0:03:44.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么 2nd
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.13,0:03:46.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会扰乱因果律的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.23,0:03:49.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.73,0:03:53.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事怎么可能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.67,0:03:57.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃和三周目的由乃 我都要拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.51,0:04:01.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界应该还有可能性的 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.43,0:04:02.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.79,0:04:03.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 雪辉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.17,0:04:07.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最直截了当的做法 就是杀死2nd
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.13,0:04:14.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.71,0:04:17.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我就陪你玩到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.99,0:04:18.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9th
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.00,0:04:19.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.70,0:04:24.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能通过努力引发奇迹的话 我想试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.57,0:04:27.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再说一遍 雪辉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.59,0:04:31.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救不了所有人 想好你的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.43,0:04:33.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 9th
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.44,0:04:36.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账 随你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.34,0:04:43.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然好重…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.77,0:04:50.31,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(160,100)\fr15}7/28  3:52 [樱见中学]\N由乃用雪辉日记追着我来了。\N7/28  3:55 [樱见中学]\N三周目的由乃醒不来。\N7/28  4:06 [樱见中学]\N由乃追上我了。\N…由乃活动身体。
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.28,0:04:50.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来改变了 这样下去会被由乃追上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.92,0:04:55.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:57.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.83,0:04:59.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我爱着你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.30,0:05:08.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 为什么我会喜欢上由乃的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.49,0:05:14.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1年B班 一开始是在这间教室…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.16,0:05:18.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是一切的开始
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.80,0:05:25.47,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(160,100)\fr10}7/28  3:59 [樱见中学]\N由乃在埋伏。\N7/28  4:00 [樱见中学]\N三周目的由乃还不醒来。\N7/28  4:01 [樱见中学]\N由乃向我袭来。\N7/28  4:02 [樱见中学]\N黑色球体在校舍出现。
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.14,0:05:31.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里等着 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.27,0:05:33.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上了断这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.16,0:05:39.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来做个了断吧 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.56,0:05:46.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受死吧 阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.66,0:05:50.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.86,0:05:50.36,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,70)\fr-18}7/28  3:59 [樱见中学]\N由乃在埋伏。\N7/28  4:00 [樱见中学]\N三周目的由乃还不醒来。\N7/28  4:01 [樱见中学]\N由乃挥起小刀。从右边挥下。\N7/28  4:02 [樱见中学]\N由乃用雪辉日记预知我逃跑的地方。
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.44,0:05:51.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从右边来
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.08,0:05:57.82,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(160,100)\fr10}7/28  4:00\N阿雪逃向右边的消火栓了！\N我要保护阿雪！\N7/28  4:10\N阿雪被姆鲁姆鲁攻击了。\N我要保护阿雪！\N7/28  4:20\N阿雪还在被姆鲁姆鲁攻击。\N阿雪加油！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.31,0:05:59.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆鲁姆鲁 在消火栓那里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.81,0:06:05.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 雪辉这家伙 到处乱躲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.55,0:06:07.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你能躲到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.01,0:06:09.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.57,0:06:11.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.46,0:06:12.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 我这边的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.29,0:06:15.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之你听好了 来须圭悟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.49,0:06:19.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的儿子心脏有病 这样下去就剩下两年命
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.82,0:06:21.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在接受诊断说不定还能救
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.42,0:06:24.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 快去看医生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.31,0:06:25.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.25,0:06:35.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的儿子…我守约了 4th
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.55,0:06:44.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.69,0:06:45.80,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(100,270)\fr17}7/28  4:03 [樱见中学]\N姆鲁姆鲁攻击过来。\N7/28  4:04 [樱见中学]\N姆鲁姆鲁的球体接二连三地爆炸。\N7/28  4:05 [樱见中学]\N由乃追着我过来。\N7/28  4:07 [樱见中学]\N姆鲁姆鲁的球体再次包围我…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.34,0:06:47.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化灰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.59,0:07:09.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆鲁姆鲁 接下来是游廊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.88,0:07:15.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要由乃手中有未来日记…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.63,0:07:18.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边的位置就了如指掌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.69,0:07:21.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 这样就好
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.65,0:07:25.79,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(80,90)\fr13}7/28  4:10\N阿雪受伤了。怎么办啊！\N真担心！！\N7/28  4:20\N阿雪被球体追着。不好了！\N我要救他！！\N7/28  4:10\N…很拼命地跑
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.80,0:07:26.99,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,140)\fr17\fs30}怎么办啊！\N真担心！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.02,0:07:26.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪受伤了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.73,0:07:28.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.79,0:07:29.32,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(430,190)\fr-13}7/28  4:10\N阿雪受伤了。怎么办啊！\N真担心！！\N7/28  4:20\N阿雪被球体追着。\N不好了！\N我要救他！！\N7/28  4:30\N阿雪很拼命地跑！ \N我要保护他！！\N7/28  4:40\N我也要快点去阿雪…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.33,0:07:29.83,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,140)\fr-15\fs30}不好了！\N我要救他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.54,0:07:31.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.45,0:07:31.95,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,150)}阿雪受伤了。怎么办啊！\N真担心！！\N7/28  4:20\N阿雪被球体追着。\N不好了！\N我要救他！！\N7/28  4:30\N阿雪很拼命地跑！ \N我要保护他！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.08,0:07:32.58,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,180)\fs30}保护他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.91,0:07:33.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.02,0:07:36.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.53,0:07:43.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样应该拖远一点了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.49,0:07:46.63,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,280)\fr19}7/28  4:11 [樱见中学]\N1st天野雪辉被2nd我妻由乃用小刀刺死。\NDEAD END
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.98,0:07:46.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被由乃的小刀刺死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.66,0:07:50.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 离DEAD END还有时间
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.98,0:07:53.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到我这么乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.11,0:07:56.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪9th会对我失望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.29,0:08:00.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我要任性到底
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.85,0:08:03.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让由乃留在三周目世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.59,0:08:05.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何 也要说服她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.10,0:08:10.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我死了让由乃成为二周目世界的神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.39,0:08:13.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一切应该就可以顺利了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.70,0:08:16.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的方法只有这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.71,0:08:18.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.22,0:08:25.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃 不要再追我…再追天野雪辉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.09,0:08:26.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.08,0:08:29.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交涉手段只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.46,0:08:34.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要夺走由乃的未来日记 由乃就无法改变未来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.84,0:08:37.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺走…然后说服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.95,0:08:42.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是蠢材 就这样压扁你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.70,0:08:51.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.00,0:08:55.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DEAD END显示的是小刀 我不会在这里死的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.50,0:08:56.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.89,0:08:59.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪 为什么要妨碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.48,0:09:01.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.76,0:09:05.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 没想到她投过来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.60,0:09:15.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投歪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.23,0:09:17.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心被阿雪的话迷惑…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.74,0:09:20.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心？怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.86,0:09:22.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.18,0:09:23.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才别想
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.35,0:09:31.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就避开DEAD END了 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.88,0:09:36.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.56,0:09:38.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃你要回到二周目世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.76,0:09:39.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要成为神…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.76,0:09:41.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.62,0:09:46.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.47,0:09:48.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.83,0:09:55.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵 活该
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.58,0:10:12.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 这当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.12,0:10:15.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我没有察觉呢
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.92,0:10:16.42,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(280,300)\fr25}7/28  4:10\N阿雪说爱我了！\N太高兴不小心投歪了。\N7/28  4:20\N阿雪被我控制的球体杀死了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.16,0:10:18.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:29.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个日记就是我的心情
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.44,0:10:29.04,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,200)\fr7\fs30}太高兴不小心投歪了。
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.94,0:10:33.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Deus之核的力量啊 把球体的控制权交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.53,0:10:39.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱你 阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.47,0:10:42.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪辉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.88,0:10:57.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公和女儿失踪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.55,0:11:01.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 救护车的人说我丈夫受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.75,0:11:04.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.64,0:11:06.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我是来须
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.75,0:11:09.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.26,0:11:10.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.18,0:11:12.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 我这边的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.92,0:11:14.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之你听好了 来须圭悟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.20,0:11:19.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的儿子心脏有病 这样下去就剩下两年命
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.55,0:11:21.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在接受诊断说不定还能救
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.12,0:11:23.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 快去看医生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.89,0:11:24.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.33,0:11:28.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这电话怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.07,0:11:30.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿曜有心脏病？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.80,0:11:34.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课长 樱见中学发生爆炸事件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.17,0:11:34.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.41,0:11:38.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那电话 好像听到爆炸的声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.75,0:11:42.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出动了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.66,0:11:43.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课…课长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.71,0:11:44.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了 新人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.96,0:11:51.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.38,0:11:54.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.73,0:11:58.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好闪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.41,0:12:06.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,椿小姐 船津一行即将带老爷和夫人出发
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.55,0:12:07.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们等着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.07,0:12:09.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城镇的情况有异样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.78,0:12:20.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些爆炸是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.00,0:12:23.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,院长 不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.94,0:12:25.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有位大人物打电话来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.38,0:12:32.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现可疑人物
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.19,0:12:33.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才可疑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.42,0:12:50.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 雪君
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.09,0:12:54.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}坐下吧 不是要做好看星的计划吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.84,0:12:52.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 妈妈
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.80,0:12:57.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}今天是雪君最喜欢的汉堡牛肉饼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.16,0:12:56.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.78,0:13:07.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我想要的夹克…为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.40,0:13:10.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这个飞镖盘…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.29,0:13:13.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直想买鹩哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.43,0:13:15.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这些都是你想要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.76,0:13:20.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是我用Deus之核的力量制造出来的幻觉空间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.19,0:13:24.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪想要的东西 什么都能得到的梦想国度
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.04,0:13:28.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫不出由乃的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.24,0:13:30.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.38,0:13:37.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是那边的世界不存在我和我的名字而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.21,0:13:42.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪 我们分手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.67,0:13:45.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.83,0:13:49.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要杀死二周目的你 一切都完结
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.43,0:13:53.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又可以在三周目世界继续正常生活…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.36,0:13:54.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.15,0:13:56.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 看来不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.98,0:13:59.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脑子里面乱成一团了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.41,0:14:02.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 要跟你说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:10.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 但我不会去二周目世界
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.72,0:14:11.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.74,0:14:15.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要{\s1\i1}由乃{\s0\i0}成为神 一切都可以圆满解决呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.11,0:14:19.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 那样我就会失去阿雪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.09,0:14:24.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是决定不出神 二周目世界就会灭亡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.98,0:14:28.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人不决定出神就一起回去是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.68,0:14:32.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样 我就把你困在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.48,0:14:35.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后去见三周目的新的阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.57,0:14:42.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要阿雪支撑我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.40,0:14:46.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 这样就要抛弃我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.65,0:14:51.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后又疯狂地杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.63,0:14:54.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后又赌上自己的性命了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.95,0:14:57.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 不要让我说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:07.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雪 只要是我可以依靠的人 是谁都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.88,0:15:15.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是 只要是可以保护自己的人 是谁都无所谓的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.61,0:15:18.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天野君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.40,0:15:20.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若叶同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.52,0:15:26.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天野君 我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.02,0:15:30.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 若叶同学不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.21,0:15:33.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.07,0:15:36.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.13,0:15:42.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天野君 我喜欢你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.63,0:15:43.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.29,0:15:48.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.30,0:15:49.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非{\s1\i1}由乃{\s0\i0}不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.12,0:15:52.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要{\s1\i1}由乃{\s0\i0}…是{\s1\i1}由乃{\s0\i0}…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.53,0:15:54.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.66,0:15:56.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.39,0:16:03.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 我为了活下去而利用了由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.70,0:16:06.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能是扭曲的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.54,0:16:08.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 即便这样 我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:16.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.11,0:16:21.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 2nd
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.60,0:16:24.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副失恋的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.91,0:16:30.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想问 你为什么要帮阿雪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.31,0:16:35.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐呀 你认为鸟是一边考虑着飞的理由一边在飞的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.76,0:16:41.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有考虑吧 我也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.94,0:16:45.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很可怜你 你不能坦率地爱他人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.76,0:16:52.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么上吧 不打你一顿我的气不消
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.08,0:16:53.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆鲁姆鲁 我解开封印
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.02,0:17:02.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙…还有这样的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.26,0:17:52.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真期待啊 雪君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.79,0:17:54.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,望远镜我也准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.97,0:17:55.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.16,0:17:58.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊 雪君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.51,0:18:01.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天跑到离星最近的地方去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.52,0:18:02.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.44,0:18:04.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪君你想看什么星呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.04,0:18:07.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗？我想…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.92,0:18:12.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 来了来了 看上去很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.82,0:18:18.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 趁热吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.77,0:18:19.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.37,0:18:21.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.68,0:18:26.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很好吃啊 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.93,0:18:30.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 你吃那么多 那我不用做便当了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.47,0:18:44.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好今天的天气这么好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.45,0:18:47.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逛一下樱见岭 然后去天文台吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.45,0:18:49.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边可以很清楚地看到星
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.22,0:18:54.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便当也会花足心思做多一些呢 还有炸鸡腿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.61,0:18:56.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.92,0:18:58.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 再来一碗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.88,0:18:59.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的好的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.16,0:19:01.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 雪君？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.11,0:19:04.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了呀 突然哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.45,0:19:09.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…我想起今天做的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.96,0:19:10.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.00,0:19:13.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很奇怪的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.79,0:19:17.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着可以预知未来的日记 参加生存游戏的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.61,0:19:20.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这梦好像很有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.10,0:19:25.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在梦中 我喜欢一个有点奇怪的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.65,0:19:29.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的女孩啊 我还以为雪君会喜欢普通的孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.96,0:19:32.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会喜欢那女孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.94,0:19:39.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…跟我喜欢爸爸妈妈的理由一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.97,0:19:45.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…因为她一直在我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.61,0:21:52.66,note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}姆鲁姆鲁老师的「里」未来日记\N2年的岁月\N我妻潮篇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.02,0:21:58.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃 你是…由乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.35,0:22:04.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥 一段时间没见 长大了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.76,0:22:05.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…各种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.18,0:22:08.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…你在说什么啊 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.59,0:22:09.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.97,0:22:12.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}不…不过 我太感动了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.93,0:22:14.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}讨厌讨厌讨厌讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.93,0:22:14.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 这时候就要蒙混过关
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.71,0:22:18.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Deus之核 把2nd变小
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.11,0:22:22.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变小了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.35,0:22:24.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.02,0:22:29.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃 你是…由乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.35,0:22:35.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥 一段时间没见 长大了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.76,0:22:36.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…各种地方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.18,0:22:39.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}喂…你在说什么啊 爸爸
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.59,0:22:40.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}抱…抱歉
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.97,0:22:43.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}不…不过 我太感动了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.93,0:22:45.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}讨厌讨厌讨厌讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.94,0:22:40.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 顺利把时间倒回了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.61,0:22:45.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要搞妥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.79,0:22:50.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Deus之核 把2nd变小
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.08,0:22:53.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变…变婴儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:23:01.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃 你是…由乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.65,0:23:06.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥 一段时间没见 长大了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.06,0:23:07.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…各种地方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.48,0:23:10.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}喂…你在说什么啊 爸爸
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.89,0:23:12.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}抱…抱歉
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.27,0:23:15.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}不…不过 我太感动了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.23,0:23:16.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}讨厌讨厌讨厌讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.05,0:23:11.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒回来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.88,0:23:16.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.07,0:23:21.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Deus之核 把2nd变小
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.99,0:23:28.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由乃 你…的胸…变小了？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.68,0:23:30.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 由乃
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.91,0:23:32.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要杀了老爸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.07,0:23:45.42,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,250)\fad(600,0)}初始化
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
