[Script Info]
Title: 攻殻機動隊 S.A.C. 2nd GIG 第20話 「北端の混迷 FABRICATE FOG」
Original Script:POPGO FANSUB
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,25,1
Style: OP,Nadejda,56,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1
Style: ED,Amaze,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- OP --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.59,0:00:09.53,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I'm a soldier  значит я
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.68,0:00:12.84,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}И ответчик и судья
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.07,0:00:18.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я стою на двух концах огня
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.80,0:00:26.10,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Огибая виражи обгоняя смерть и жизнь
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.33,0:00:31.86,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я бегу сразиться с тенью лжи
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.03,0:00:38.58,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Сколько б нитей не плёл обман
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.68,0:00:46.34,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Покажет лик света истина
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.78,0:00:49.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your tears for the day
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.96,0:00:53.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}when our pain is far behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.23,0:00:54.79,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}on your feet
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.82,0:00:56.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}come with me
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.48,0:00:59.85,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we are soldiers stand or die
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.89,0:01:01.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your fears
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.49,0:01:02.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}take your place
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.06,0:01:06.29,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}save them for the judgement day
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.40,0:01:08.00,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}fast and free
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.02,0:01:09.56,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}follow me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.62,0:01:14.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}time to make the sacrifice
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.51,0:01:20.71,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we rise or fall
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- 第20話 「北端の混迷 FABRICATE FOG」 --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.46,0:01:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs50\an8\fad(1000,1000)}中文字幕由漫游字幕组制作 供交流学习使用 禁止用于商业用途\N请在下载后24小时内删除
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.72,0:01:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像你的作风啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.65,0:01:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情形…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.93,0:01:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无话可说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.64,0:01:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在实战中培养新人还是太勉强了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.87,0:01:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把记忆改写进电子脑会怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.92,0:01:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再生矢野君吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.90,0:02:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像Ghost无法复制一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.90,0:02:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使复制了记忆 Ghost也不会宿于其中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.23,0:02:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅考虑维持九课的话 可能并不需要新的人才
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.80,0:02:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但考虑到今后的形势时
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.66,0:02:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是我们必须跨越的一个课题
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.56,0:02:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.92,0:02:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但把东从这次作战中撤出吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.09,0:02:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.06,0:02:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请妥善处置 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1500,0)\fn方正小标宋_GBK\1c&H0E1011&\bord0\be1\shad0\fs80}北端的混乱 FABRICATE FOG
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.60,0:02:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的老朋友带来的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.16,0:03:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原俄罗斯军官 现已改投黑手党的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.62,0:03:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波利斯·加布罗夫及其数名部下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.45,0:03:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被确认从本国带出了钚 进入择捉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.33,0:03:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 久世是打算买他们的钚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.30,0:03:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算拥有核武装后宣称成为独立国家吗 再大胆也要有个限度吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.06,0:03:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直执行秘密侦察任务的谍报人员被其同伙的义体人杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.44,0:03:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶手目前行踪不明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.36,0:03:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谍报人员被杀是在两小时前吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.25,0:03:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 说是这么说 我们已经没有选择的余地了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.44,0:03:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.60,0:03:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 如何确定位置
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.55,0:03:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分青红皂白地跑去择捉也解决不了问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.84,0:04:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公安部给出的情报里似乎有些线索
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.84,0:04:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}贝尔塔尔贝：择捉岛南端都市 巨大的旧型电脑都市
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.84,0:04:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,择捉支厅的佐川电子公司
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.17,0:04:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎正在无照扩建贝尔塔尔贝区的地下工厂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.04,0:04:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝尔塔尔贝 原俄国潜艇基地的所在地吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 听说在俄军撤退时爆破掩埋掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.31,0:04:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 如果其后佐川的扩建工程进展顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.22,0:04:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就应该到达基地了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.86,0:04:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 很可疑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.70,0:04:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潜艇基地用来藏伪造船再合适不过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.65,0:04:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没有确凿证据
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.84,0:04:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有计划进行这种程度的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.98,0:04:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当地的情报贩子也应该知道些风声
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.85,0:04:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课长 我们直接进入择捉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.62,0:04:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了以防万一 请向海上保安厅申请封锁出岛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.06,0:04:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果难民弄到了核 就等于解开了所有的枷锁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.98,0:04:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以 但我相信你们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.34,0:05:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不能在此阻止久世
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.63,0:05:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内阁情报厅的行为将消匿于黑暗中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.73,0:05:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军队就会介入
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.11,0:05:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让出岛变成战场
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.87,0:05:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.38,0:05:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 似乎没做什么手脚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.94,0:05:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离交易还有一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.26,0:05:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们轮流休息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.05,0:05:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.50,0:05:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 吃点这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.92,0:05:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.61,0:05:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难吃 味道真差
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.29,0:05:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得向课长抗议才行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.57,0:06:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有不少时间 要不要检查一下电子脑活性
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.45,0:06:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 我只是有点困惑于久世的妄想之大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.99,0:06:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞不懂 那家伙到底抱着怎样的妄想
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.03,0:06:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单来说就是「征服世界」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.50,0:06:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.08,0:06:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是了不得的妄想狂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.18,0:06:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会着这种道可不像是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.46,0:06:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直像是思春期的小鬼遇到了真命天子的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.79,0:06:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.27,0:06:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这下清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.33,0:06:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「个别的11人」病毒虽然曾在他身上发作过一次
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.29,0:06:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他现在的行动是由其原本的资质和思想产生的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.76,0:06:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这妄想本身确实是很老套
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但无法一笑带过的是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.49,0:06:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是真心认为当上独裁者能给世界带来和平
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.33,0:06:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.33,0:07:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他的肾上腺素分泌已达到了常人的致死量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.30,0:07:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以认为久世已经进入「圣域」了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.49,0:07:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你说的「圣域」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.49,0:07:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说他已经超乎常理了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.26,0:07:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从历史来上看 这种人会发挥令人难以置信的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如切·格瓦拉和马尔科姆·X
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}Malcolm X：美国黑人民族主义者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.71,0:07:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯瑟斯·克莱等就是典型
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.71,0:07:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}Cassius Clay：拳王阿里(Muhammad Ali)的原名，黑人民权运动者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.47,0:07:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和希特勒不同吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.43,0:07:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从某种意义上来说是同类
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.15,0:07:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在思想上比较接近甘地和马丁·路德·金
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.46,0:07:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时常与他连网的难民们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.73,0:07:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经由设立了分区制和过滤程序的网络
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.84,0:07:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉浸在与久世行动的实时连接中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.26,0:07:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但通过设置偏压{\fs50}（bias）{\r}来避免意识共享
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.88,0:07:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,则是因为知道他的Ghost障壁之后是危险区域
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.11,0:07:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是千钧一发
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.63,0:07:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没意思的话题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.74,0:08:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川 帕兹 博马就此待机
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.74,0:08:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防交易地点有变
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.16,0:08:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.72,0:09:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧 军国主义者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.98,0:09:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个是非之地啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.36,0:09:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说已经归还了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.18,0:09:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但俄裔和日裔之间的摩擦不可能马上消失
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.64,0:09:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦 这就是建设中的地下都市吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.58,0:09:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿着这向基地前进的话 就有可能会碰到久世吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.76,0:09:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们还有运气的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.22,0:09:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有运气呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.09,0:09:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候就只会和佐川的建筑工人相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.39,0:09:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没工夫等少佐的联络了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.71,0:10:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.25,0:10:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是听说要买武器才上船的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.03,0:10:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果知道是你在指挥 我就不会来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.70,0:10:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.98,0:10:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也不勉强你跟着我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.18,0:10:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么回去也好 消失在择捉市里也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.88,0:10:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会强制你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.31,0:10:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也赞成革命
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.47,0:10:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最初教我们革命的 就是「传说」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.62,0:10:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在出岛上几乎所有人都知道同志久世
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.67,0:10:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但几乎没人知道你的真正面目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.19,0:10:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不能接受
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.72,0:10:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我至今仍遵循「传说」的教导 有自爆的觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.14,0:10:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊 那种东西只能让人自我满足
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.08,0:10:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,革命是有Ghost才会有的产物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.53,0:10:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想知道你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.60,0:10:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿出让我也能相信你的证据来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.65,0:11:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.53,0:11:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.64,0:11:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我们打算拿到的武器是钚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.06,0:11:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算以此让日本政府承认出岛为独立国家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.75,0:11:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有借有还 这是最基本的规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.01,0:11:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.87,0:11:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混得不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.98,0:11:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么可借人的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.34,0:11:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是大姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.48,0:11:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.40,0:11:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说克罗尔登还在这里面做 是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.51,0:11:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 这边请
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.36,0:12:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这么小心翼翼的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.39,0:12:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 请
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.10,0:12:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陀古萨 你在这里等着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.58,0:12:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.12,0:12:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.25,0:12:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这世上 太缠人是会遭人厌的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.24,0:12:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做大姐的搭档很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.85,0:12:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不和大姐搞好关系 是会后悔死的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.37,0:12:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克罗尔登 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.47,0:12:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根室登陆作战时蒙你照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.04,0:13:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻性防壁…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.54,0:13:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚刚被烧掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.09,0:13:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是潜到哪里去被烧掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.35,0:13:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 能烧掉克罗尔登这种程度的黑客
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.49,0:13:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当有本事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.51,0:13:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻性防壁的作动方式
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.48,0:13:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是不被机密保持法认可的对应方法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.03,0:13:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.57,0:13:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软盘？居然用这种老式媒体做外部记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.58,0:14:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那家伙就是为了清除这个才多费了功夫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.24,0:14:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐川的秘密帐簿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.18,0:14:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卖出 柠檬蛋糕 20公斤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.38,0:14:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柠檬蛋糕？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.87,0:14:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每公斤50万美金
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.45,0:14:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由MAU交易中撤出
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.87,0:14:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中介人佐川「K」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.94,0:14:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B.J. 柠檬蛋糕20公斤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.64,0:14:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给「K」交易额40％退职金
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.09,0:14:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买家B.P.商会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.50,0:14:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如我所料 钚的交易情报被人偷窥了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.64,0:14:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐川的「K」 「K」是指北端特务课长加贺崎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.26,0:14:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他作为中介商 以每公斤50万美金交易
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.85,0:14:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卖方是波利斯·加布罗夫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.48,0:14:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买方是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚洲的B.P.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.74,0:14:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指亚洲难民？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.69,0:14:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么刚才的黑客是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.43,0:15:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加贺崎的交易部分是以日元进行的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.49,0:15:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定金已经汇给了佐川
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.27,0:15:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两亿四千万日元？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.91,0:15:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难民哪来的这么多钱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.60,0:15:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是久世准备的？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.20,0:15:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是怎么弄到的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.56,0:15:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你帮了大忙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.00,0:15:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得佐川电子是你最讨厌的本州企业
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（内阁情报厅调查 非官方白皮书）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.14,0:15:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.67,0:15:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真不该辞去报道厅的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.92,0:15:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来 内阁情报厅说不定还能变成比现在正经点的机关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.90,0:15:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川 交易地点在原潜艇基地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.24,0:15:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事可能也与内阁情报厅有关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.93,0:15:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.06,0:15:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没时间了 巴特他们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.91,0:15:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在地下深处
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.56,0:15:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通信被遮断了 我们马上过去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.13,0:16:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到时间了 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.19,0:16:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有件事要问
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.18,0:16:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经听说要买钚 至少需要25万美金
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.02,0:16:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱要怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.05,0:16:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要骗俄国人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.13,0:16:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 正当地付钱买货
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.18,0:16:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱是为了让其理解我们的痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.84,0:16:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设法从不断消费难民的国民那里 一点点募集过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.42,0:16:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说你也不明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.14,0:16:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伎俩是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.34,0:16:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现今对丰衣足食毫无自觉的国民的总储蓄额 是900兆日元多一点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.90,0:16:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于这个数额本身 他们也毫无自觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.48,0:16:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在这些储蓄的利息中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.22,0:17:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存在着表面上不存在的金额 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.34,0:17:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表面上不存在？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.11,0:17:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一日元以下的金额
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.53,0:17:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终端的数据通常不会显示出来的 小数点以后的数字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.97,0:17:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}钱：元以下的日元单位 1日元 = 100钱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.97,0:17:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是从网上的户头里征收这些只有几钱的微小金额
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.00,0:17:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天就会有数千万单位的金额
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.30,0:17:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我设置了程序 自动将这些钱汇进我的虚拟银行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.02,0:17:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱就是这样准备起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.11,0:17:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般人根本不知道自己的户头里 存在小数点以后的存款
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.49,0:17:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银行现在也把户头管理都交给了AI
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.22,0:17:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要难民在本土工作 就要被征收预扣税
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.22,0:17:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}预扣税（源泉課税）：在支付薪金、红利、版税时 预先扣除税款
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.23,0:17:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却绝不可能承认他们的归化（入籍）
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国民也是 对系统的庞大榨取毫无察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.17,0:17:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只摄取动听的 容易接受的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.99,0:18:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等虚伪的社会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.54,0:18:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想启蒙大家认识这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.56,0:18:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些钱 现在到底有多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.46,0:18:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多是107亿6000万
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.61,0:18:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些将成为我们革命可用的军费
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.86,0:18:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 你究竟…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.99,0:18:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是个恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.54,0:18:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 现在稍稍有点沉迷于英雄主义
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.88,0:18:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你留下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.22,0:18:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好准备 随时可以出船
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.43,0:18:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.49,0:18:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是有问题的扩建区吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.48,0:19:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 今天到底有什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.85,0:19:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有得到许可吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.92,0:19:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是现场的负责人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.32,0:19:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你刚才说「又」了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.56,0:19:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.77,0:19:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久前是两台总公司的武装机甲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.54,0:19:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再之前是一个奇怪的俄国义体人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.23,0:19:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提着两个大箱子 吊着绳索下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.00,0:19:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜中了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.82,0:19:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.88,0:19:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是为什么陆上自卫军…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.67,0:19:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么只有你一个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.60,0:19:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加布罗夫和加贺崎都被公安盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.08,0:19:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我一个人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.68,0:19:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快完成交易吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.64,0:20:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.54,0:20:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有汇款到指定户头的记录
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.21,0:20:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确认一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.64,0:20:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走一步 你们随后跟来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.26,0:20:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交易成立
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能确认内容 双方都是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.60,0:21:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下武器出来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.38,0:21:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以违反武器管制法和不正当交易核物质的嫌疑逮捕你～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.50,0:21:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快现形吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.57,0:22:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,齐藤 有些不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.54,0:22:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管这里了 去抓寇尔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.54,0:22:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}寇尔·克拉斯诺夫：俄国战斗型义体人 钛制义手支架延伸至肩胛骨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.25,0:22:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.85,0:22:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.88,0:22:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出去 一定要宰了他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.69,0:22:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住 久世
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.54,0:22:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把东西放下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.41,0:22:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不立即开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.27,0:22:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为知道这是什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.17,0:22:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西是什么都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.10,0:22:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的是你的脑袋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.62,0:22:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这似乎不大可能
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.80,0:22:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拿着箱子到船上去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.98,0:22:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.71,0:22:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.56,0:22:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小看我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- ED --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.21,0:23:14.68,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Finding out a galaxy of planets and stars within me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.17,0:23:21.20,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}listening to each of them singing the same silent melody
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.50,0:23:28.45,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I've never seen such beauty in possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:32.64,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}no speck of doubt or fear
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.98,0:23:37.04,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.36,0:23:40.10,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.57,0:23:43.65,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.90,0:23:46.85,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.37,0:23:49.01,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.02,0:23:54.10,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.65,0:23:59.09,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}the beauty within the shell
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.53,0:24:03.70,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.98,0:24:06.85,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.33,0:24:10.40,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.59,0:24:13.60,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.84,0:24:15.52,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.61,0:24:21.49,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.49,0:24:26.40,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}right here within this shell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- Section 9 Science File --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.56,0:24:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}塔奇克马式的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.01,0:24:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方现在都还能站着 就已经近似于奇迹了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.00,0:24:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是否能清楚地看到对方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.80,0:24:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 塔奇克马跳到了ARM SUITS的头顶！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.55,0:24:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了 漂亮的大招 TACHI·Spin·Driver！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.84,0:24:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ARM SUITS可以说已经无法反抗了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.84,0:24:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是终于耗尽力量了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.72,0:25:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 居然会这样！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.95,0:25:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在即将迎来高潮的时候 双方同时不像样地瘫到了台上！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.08,0:25:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方都没能站起！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.28,0:25:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很不像样 但是节目时间已经快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.63,0:25:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个被各种不像样的气氛包裹的电脑空间中
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.83,0:25:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的实况转播依然由塔奇克马为各位带来！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.58,0:25:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太不像样了 实在抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.84,0:25:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…



