[Script Info]
Title:攻殻機動隊 S.A.C. 2nd GIG 第06話 「潜在熱源 EXCAVATION」
Original Script:POPGO FANSUB
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,25,1
Style: OP,Nadejda,56,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1
Style: ED,Amaze,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- OP --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.59,0:00:11.53,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I'm a soldier  значит я
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.68,0:00:14.84,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}И ответчик и судья
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.07,0:00:20.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я стою на двух концах огня
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.80,0:00:28.10,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Огибая виражи обгоняя смерть и жизнь
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.33,0:00:33.86,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я бегу сразиться с тенью лжи
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.03,0:00:40.58,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Сколько б нитей не плёл обман
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.68,0:00:48.34,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Покажет лик света истина
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.78,0:00:51.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your tears for the day
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.96,0:00:55.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}when our pain is far behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.23,0:00:56.79,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}on your feet
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.82,0:00:58.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}come with me
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.48,0:01:01.85,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we are soldiers stand or die
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.89,0:01:03.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your fears
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.49,0:01:04.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}take your place
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.06,0:01:08.29,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}save them for the judgement day
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.40,0:01:10.00,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}fast and free
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.02,0:01:11.56,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}follow me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.62,0:01:16.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}time to make the sacrifice
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.51,0:01:22.71,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we rise or fall
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- 第06話 「潜在熱源 EXCAVATION」--------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.48,0:01:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs50\an8\fad(1000,1000)}中文字幕由漫游字幕组制作 供交流学习使用 禁止用于商业用途\N请在下载后24小时内删除
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.30,0:01:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伪装成意外事故的他杀吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.19,0:01:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据调查人员说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.83,0:01:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有可能在碾压时故意对脑壳造成了伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.50,0:01:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卡车司机因为开车打瞌睡 完全没有记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为慎重起见 正在检查司机的电子脑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.96,0:01:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概不会有任何发现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.35,0:01:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐吓能源省的犯人这条线索就此断了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.86,0:02:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个男人是独自犯罪的话 那的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.22,0:02:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被害者的义体是丰田化工制的2902式
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.07,0:02:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑壳是Derumo制2706式改良型
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.34,0:02:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然型号落伍 但都是新出厂的国产机种
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.46,0:02:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外表也是市售的标准型式 没有附加功能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.81,0:02:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有脸部是定制品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.84,0:02:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 从细胞劣化的程度来看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.82,0:02:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是从义体化开始就使用到现在的老部品了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.99,0:02:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以犯罪者来说 换装方式真不高明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.72,0:02:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且恐吓手段似乎也很拙劣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.28,0:02:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能源省丑闻本身可能就是故弄玄虚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.87,0:02:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却在逮捕前突然死于有暗杀嫌疑的事故
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.92,0:02:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个印记是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.51,0:02:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是旧首都内新宿区的标志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.78,0:02:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大战时沉到水底的那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.97,0:02:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个脑壳不知为何镀了一层玻璃和铅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.44,0:02:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像就是在那时刻的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.04,0:03:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的随身物品
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.09,0:03:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面写了记者的联络方式
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.40,0:03:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该可以当做身份调查的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.64,0:03:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会不会是结婚戒指呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.92,0:03:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1500,0)\fn方正小标宋_GBK\1c&H0E1011&\bord0\be1\shad0\fs80}潜在热源 EXCAVATION
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.65,0:03:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们事务所的确接到了希望见面的联络电话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.44,0:03:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.33,0:03:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然密告内容十分可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.08,0:03:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是因为联络用的是东京的公用终端…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.70,0:03:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东京？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.62,0:03:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么密告的内容是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.40,0:03:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能源省内部的丑闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.84,0:03:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种密告要是挨个调查还怎么工作
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.73,0:03:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很少直接碰面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.98,0:03:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他说要寄给我能当证据的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.11,0:03:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问是两位吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.66,0:03:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问抽不抽烟？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.08,0:04:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请这边走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.29,0:04:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一片黑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.76,0:04:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是什么可以当证据的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.84,0:04:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但完全曝光了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.89,0:04:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他大概认为用电子数据没说服力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.25,0:04:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在很少有人会使用胶卷了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.41,0:04:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个可不可以先给我保管？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.89,0:04:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以是可以
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.65,0:04:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过真的什么都没拍到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.65,0:04:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课长
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.11,0:04:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来那个男人在被杀害的几天前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.12,0:04:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在东京都内呆过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.07,0:04:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在那里把感光过度的底片寄给了记者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.92,0:04:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 你到东京走一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.16,0:04:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间我们会查出他使用的终端器
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.57,0:04:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.58,0:04:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人还在继续负责保护总理
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.86,0:04:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派给你一台塔奇克马
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.35,0:04:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辐射已经没问题了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.62,0:04:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为大战结束几年了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.58,0:05:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从 「日本的奇迹」散播之后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.58,0:05:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}日本的奇迹：一种能消除核污染的微型机械
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.26,0:05:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没查到过有残留辐射了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.66,0:05:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.59,0:05:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新东京 新东京
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.24,0:05:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在到站的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.60,0:06:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心残留辐射的话 建议你去改成义体
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.64,0:06:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.64,0:06:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是感觉上…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.42,0:06:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不舒服？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.20,0:06:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我可以让你坐进来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.87,0:06:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样会晕车
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.33,0:06:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少啰唆 闭上嘴跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.75,0:06:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.97,0:06:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里打的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.81,0:06:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有见过这个男的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.10,0:06:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.43,0:07:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该是在这附近更新义体的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.00,0:07:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.60,0:07:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近都是些忍耐着靠最低限机能过活的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.60,0:07:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也给我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.15,0:07:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近常有人来找人 说不定我认识
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.35,0:07:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.70,0:07:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.92,0:07:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.65,0:07:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.06,0:07:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不认识这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.77,0:07:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在四五天前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.23,0:07:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也被一位在这种大热天还穿着黑西装的男人问过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.49,0:07:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长着一副可怕的脸孔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.03,0:07:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且刚刚在人群聚集处有个年轻小姐也在找这个人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.58,0:07:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个帅哥到底干了什么好事？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.82,0:07:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大事 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.84,0:07:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.62,0:07:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问认不认识小段完治这个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.73,0:07:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认识啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.13,0:07:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.61,0:07:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.44,0:08:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不是到处都能淘到那种好货的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.15,0:08:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？陀古萨？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.96,0:08:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,线…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.25,0:08:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,断了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.81,0:08:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想受苦的话就快滚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.45,0:09:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.56,0:09:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次联络时提到的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.61,0:09:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已确认在关东难民居住区
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.67,0:09:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确曾有过一个叫做小段完治的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.40,0:09:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.42,0:09:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把死者的照片和戒指给搭救的女性看了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.40,0:09:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说是小段的东西没错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.40,0:09:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女性是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.04,0:09:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅木琉璃子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.54,0:09:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说两年前参加支持难民的NGO
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.54,0:09:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}NGO：非政府组织
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.39,0:09:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那时结识了小段
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.14,0:09:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来彼此仍继续联络
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.78,0:09:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至约好总有一天要在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.12,0:09:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是三个月前 小段失去联络
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.13,0:10:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在一周前 她突然接到分手的信件
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.29,0:10:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了寻找小段 她从秋田来到新东京
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.44,0:10:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.37,0:10:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续从女人那里打听详情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.94,0:10:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.28,0:10:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段死了 对不对…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.84,0:10:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是小段送给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.47,0:10:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说很快就能离开难民街了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.54,0:10:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是到领取ID时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.78,0:10:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段的义体却没有通过审查
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.19,0:10:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为没有具备最低所需的机能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.12,0:11:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道这件事之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.89,0:11:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段开始逃避我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.72,0:11:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是认为我隐瞒了规格的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.72,0:11:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没办法跟他取得联络吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.33,0:11:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联络过好几次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.05,0:11:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我也来帮他想办法弄到新义体
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.64,0:11:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是他拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.98,0:11:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在新滨市被发现的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.45,0:11:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段已经换了国产的新义体
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.02,0:11:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听他说过这件事？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.24,0:11:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没听说过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.76,0:11:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.72,0:11:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 他在死前…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.46,0:11:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涉嫌恐吓某国家机关 勒索金钱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.53,0:11:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听你说的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.22,0:11:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为小段是为了得到义体 才想到去恐吓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.35,0:11:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是他的义体已经换好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.08,0:11:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么得到义体之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.70,0:12:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还要去恐吓呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.15,0:12:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段虽然被迫过着怀才不遇的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.39,0:12:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但绝不是会去犯罪的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.42,0:12:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.04,0:12:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是小段的死并不是意外
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.91,0:12:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能是被某人杀害的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.62,0:12:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与你失去联络的三个月当中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.47,0:12:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的身上可能发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.97,0:12:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天去人多的地方打听看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.28,0:12:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是一个月前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.11,0:12:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛传有个家伙在大量雇用全身义体化的劳工
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.67,0:12:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说只要愿意到「内环七」去 就免费赠送义体
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.00,0:12:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.51,0:12:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个「内环七」是指哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.08,0:12:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指淹到水里的那一带
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.62,0:13:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是没听说有人拿到过义体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.16,0:13:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概只是谣传吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.02,0:13:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人好像拿到了新义体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.11,0:13:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有人知道以前那个可以拿到义体的谣言？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.06,0:13:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说这个男人真的拿到全身义体了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.23,0:13:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.50,0:13:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏老师我才能活到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.03,0:13:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.90,0:13:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在「内环七」教了我很多事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.03,0:13:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里发生了什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.35,0:13:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不太清楚 只是按照指示工作而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.67,0:14:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得雇主是谁吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.10,0:14:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是叫「黑松电设」什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.04,0:14:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是要挖掘战争时被掩埋的设施
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.34,0:14:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为要进入很深的地底 要我们换成全身义体再集合
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.90,0:14:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于要求义体化比率98% 我一度想放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.61,0:14:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过黑市医生帮我谎报了义体化比率 我才混了进去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.45,0:14:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,义体上有这个记号吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.28,0:14:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.54,0:14:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师对能换上新义体非常高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.04,0:14:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己又无法看到自己的脑壳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.00,0:14:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道是不是真的拿到了新品
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.23,0:14:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 聚集了40名左右的劳工
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.28,0:14:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入了很深的地底
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.00,0:15:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我之外 好像也有其它人谎报了义体化比率
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.36,0:15:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我和老师一组开始工作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.88,0:15:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是个叫热交换管道的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.41,0:15:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然戴着防尘面具 但鼻子里面都一片黑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.91,0:15:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师说只要切断感觉器官就没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.27,0:15:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我不是全身义体 没办法切断
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.92,0:15:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果老师的表情变得非常可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.02,0:15:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我要是不马上离开这里 一定会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.54,0:15:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我无论如何都需要钱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.84,0:15:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没听老师的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.26,0:15:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后老师说 如果这个变黑了就赶快逃出去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.52,0:15:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了我这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.94,0:15:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始工作的第四天 发生了大事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.76,0:15:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然响起警报声
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.42,0:15:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在想发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.61,0:15:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面的工作现场有许多像是技术人员的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.53,0:15:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺在担架上被抬了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.35,0:16:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我终于明白这个工作非常危险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.72,0:16:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以逃了出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.82,0:16:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来 发现进来了一群穿黑衣的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.16,0:16:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟老师虽然顺利逃了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.99,0:16:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但逃的时候回头看了一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.02,0:16:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起工作的同伴都被关在巨大的铁门后面了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.68,0:16:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来小段怎么样了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.71,0:16:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说必须把自己在隧道中看到的事公诸于世
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.86,0:16:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.04,0:16:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以带我们到内环七那边去？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.25,0:16:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.44,0:16:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算给钱我也不回那种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.33,0:16:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只到中途也行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.06,0:16:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.40,0:16:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想知道小段在那里看到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.10,0:17:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有陆上自卫队在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.22,0:17:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逃出来的时候还没有那种铁丝网
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.70,0:17:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里进去就能走到同样的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.90,0:17:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我就带你们到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.40,0:17:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.86,0:18:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\an1}前方禁止进入。\N进入时不要忘记穿着规定的辐射防护服\N以及别上film badge。\N如果检测出规定以上的数值，\N请立刻离开。\N负责单位：东京核电
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.86,0:18:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}film badge：测量辐射的胶片襟章剂量计
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.30,0:18:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.37,0:18:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武装机甲？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.75,0:18:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.22,0:18:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳过来 快
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.76,0:19:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.98,0:20:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陀古萨 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.15,0:20:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔奇克马
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.70,0:21:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到站列车开往新福冈 未来52号
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.29,0:21:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段为了跟你在一起 明知有危险还是去了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.68,0:21:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为正好具有了解那里是什么设施的知识
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.29,0:21:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才被杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.98,0:21:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回家后马上就去接小段
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.44,0:21:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事马上跟我联系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.94,0:21:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.18,0:21:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小段在隐藏于深层地底的核电厂中遇到事故
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.21,0:21:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此威胁能源省
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.25,0:22:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能是想把这个丑闻公诸于世
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.33,0:22:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.30,0:22:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推测是工程中发生了临界事故
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以急忙找人来埋掉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.03,0:22:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过军方似乎还没有掌握实际状况
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.81,0:22:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题在于挖掘大战前遗物的是哪个机关 目的又是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.38,0:22:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个黑西装…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.33,0:22:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还有内幕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.69,0:22:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来之后立刻汇整报告书
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.14,0:22:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.24,0:22:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}黑松电设社长自杀\N不法劳动者被现场解体
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- ED --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.30,0:23:16.89,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Finding out a galaxy of planets and stars within me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.00,0:23:23.27,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}listening to each of them singing the same silent melody
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.60,0:23:30.56,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I've never seen such beauty in possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.88,0:23:34.79,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}no speck of doubt or fear
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.00,0:23:39.22,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.48,0:23:42.14,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.75,0:23:45.85,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.04,0:23:48.73,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.43,0:23:50.90,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.30,0:23:56.22,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.59,0:24:00.82,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}the beauty within the shell
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.73,0:24:05.94,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.14,0:24:09.03,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.36,0:24:12.59,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.76,0:24:15.44,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.25,0:24:17.57,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.91,0:24:23.34,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.50,0:24:27.18,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}right here within this shell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- Section 9 Science File --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.40,0:24:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}塔奇克马式的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.45,0:24:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人围殴才干掉的对手我怎么可能打赢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.57,0:24:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二局开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.77,0:24:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.50,0:24:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪 好像眼泪流出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.81,0:25:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快救命
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.44,0:25:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙好像不动耶
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.81,0:25:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.70,0:25:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 动起来了


