[Script Info]
;
;此字幕是由RP、琵琶行等字幕组字幕文件以及外文字幕文件重新整理修改而成，在此感谢各字幕组的无私奉献。
;
;F005
;

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Hellsing,微软雅黑,75,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00040409,&HF0FDFDFD,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,20,1
Style: Notes,微软雅黑,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00322D62,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,20,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:17.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是我的新家
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.60,0:00:23.09,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,老师　为什么我要来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.95,0:00:27.43,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么父亲母亲都不来接我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.51,0:00:30.36,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是侧室的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.23,0:00:39.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.17,0:00:41.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不需要伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.25,0:00:43.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,也不需要父母
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.68,0:00:45.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为大人物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.41,0:00:48.54,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要成为大人物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.55,0:00:52.36,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,成为不论是谁都得仰视的大人物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.19,0:00:57.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,局长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.01,0:01:00.71,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,局长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.11,0:01:04.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,请醒醒 局长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.87,0:01:07.59,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,马克斯威尔局长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.81,0:01:15.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,先遣的安德鲁森神父武装部队
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.32,0:01:17.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,逮捕了因特古拉·赫尔辛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.68,0:01:21.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,并与最后的大队发生交战
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.72,0:01:23.93,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那个战斗狂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.66,0:01:27.21,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,明明交代他只要监视就好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.48,0:01:45.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,真是壮观啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.59,0:01:49.22,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像是炼狱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.78,0:01:51.82,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,帝都伦敦已处于毁灭状态
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.48,0:01:55.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,伦敦大空袭后火灾持续蔓延着
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.65,0:01:57.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,死者不计其数
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.55,0:02:01.71,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 不知有多少人成了食尸鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.29,0:02:04.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是神罚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.32,0:02:09.42,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是白痴们妄开异端之门还自鸣得意的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.09,0:02:11.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,活该啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.36,0:02:13.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,正是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.50,0:02:21.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,美国呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:23.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,一片混乱中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.78,0:02:25.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,白宫仍处于失火状态
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.26,0:02:31.96,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,因为在会议中白宫办公厅主任突然变成吸血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.60,0:02:36.46,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,除了总统 将其他13名会议成员都杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.33,0:02:38.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不出所料呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.40,0:02:41.39,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,美支部部队已部署完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.36,0:02:44.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,等事态再度恶化我们再行动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,静观其变
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.25,0:02:51.40,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那边的混乱对我们来说是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.60,0:02:54.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,先让那边乐上一阵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.85,0:03:01.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 目前他们的行动也仅限于此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.02,0:03:02.74,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是为何
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.49,0:03:04.47,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我没兴趣知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.64,0:03:07.85,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,只要不妨碍我就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.33,0:03:11.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我感兴趣的只有英国 HELLSING 阿卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.43,0:03:14.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那个呆肥 呆肥少校
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.35,0:03:17.38,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,根本没把我们放在眼里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.57,0:03:23.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.41,0:03:25.64,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,就看我这个局外人冲进去横扫一切吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.32,0:03:27.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.42,0:03:33.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,让我们把英国从那些异教徒和怪物们的手中夺回来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.97,0:03:39.03,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,异教徒和怪物们杀了最好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.97,0:03:41.70,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,老师就是这么教我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.39,0:03:49.10,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,库尔兰提 剑之友修道骑士会 全军340名
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.30,0:03:50.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,参阵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.97,0:03:54.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,卡拉托拉巴·努埃巴骑士团 全军118名
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.12,0:03:55.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,参阵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:04:01.90,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,圣斯特法诺骑士团 托斯卡纳军团 全军257名
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.00,0:04:02.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,参阵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.65,0:04:07.05,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,马耳他骑士团 全军2457名
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.45,0:04:07.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,参阵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.98,0:04:39.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,吾等奉教皇陛下之命前来效力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.16,0:04:42.53,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,同时传令 马克斯威尔司教晋升为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.96,0:04:44.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,大主教
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.09,0:04:49.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,吾等军团 在此结成第九次十字军
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.92,0:04:55.02,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,总指挥权尽归马克斯威尔大主教猊下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.79,0:05:08.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,Amen
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.73,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,粉身碎骨在所不辞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.66,0:05:15.01,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,目标大英帝国 死都伦敦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:21.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,再次狂热的征服  RECONQUISTA开始
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:21.56,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,RECONQUISTA ：收复失地运动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.35,0:05:37.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,Amen...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.36,0:05:54.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,第十三课出身的我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.40,0:05:57.85,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,被嫌弃的恶魔之子 连生存都难以如愿的我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.85,0:06:02.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然成了大主教 竟然成了军团指挥者
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.93,0:06:08.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,局长
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.68,0:06:12.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.50,0:06:14.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.18,0:06:19.92,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,大西洋上的英国航母
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.29,0:06:21.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,在移动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.11,0:06:25.93,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,难道正在航行 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.24,0:06:29.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,经过那样的火灾后 怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.04,0:06:33.72,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然时速只有几海里 但确实在移动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.31,0:06:35.15,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,向着伦敦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.97,0:06:37.77,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,阿卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.92,0:06:38.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.49,0:06:44.14,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.69,0:06:48.92,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,HELLSING也好 Millennium也好 阿卡特也好 都将被抹杀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.32,0:06:53.08,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,最后站在擂台上高举双拳的将是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.60,0:06:54.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,全军进击
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.34,0:06:58.91,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,执行神罚的时刻到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.52,0:07:35.38,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都欢欣雀跃地向地狱突击而去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.71,0:07:40.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,到底谁能从地狱中 从那片杀戮之地中生还
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.69,0:07:44.86,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,想必每个人都会面带着喜色迎来死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.53,0:07:46.58,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,在那黄昏中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.12,0:08:12.79,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\fad(1000,1000)}赫尔墨斯之鸟乃吾之名  噬己翼以驭己心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.62,0:08:40.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,传来了令人怀念的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.45,0:08:51.41,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,被刺杀的男人的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.28,0:08:54.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,被砍杀的女人的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.64,0:08:57.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,被烧杀的婴儿的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.83,0:09:00.86,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,被射杀的老人的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.00,0:09:07.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡的气味 战争的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.66,0:09:11.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我来了 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.56,0:09:19.71,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,佐林 出击吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.70,0:09:21.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.74,0:09:24.73,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,齐柏林Ⅱ引擎启动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.08,0:09:27.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,佐林·布里兹支队 出击
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.99,0:09:34.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,目标 HELLSING本部
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.26,0:09:57.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,还剩多少人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.38,0:10:01.73,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,还剩一半了 他们比预期的强啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.06,0:10:06.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,准备铝热剂 把纳粹的尸体全部烧光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.06,0:10:06.98,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs34} 铝热剂: 是把铝粉和氧化铁粉末按一定比例配成的混合物 当用引燃剂点燃时 会发生猛烈反应 得到氧化铝和单质铁并放出大量的热 温度可到3000℃ 能使生成的铁熔化
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.00,0:10:09.05,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不留任何渣滓
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.67,0:10:13.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.08,0:10:16.93,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.11,0:10:19.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,当然是回家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.63,0:10:25.10,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我有我的任务 作为指挥官的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.42,0:10:27.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我必须回去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.60,0:10:32.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行 你现在可是我们的人质
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.24,0:10:35.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,火
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.34,0:10:40.24,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,给我点烟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.27,0:10:44.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不机灵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.08,0:10:49.60,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,火
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.90,0:10:54.64,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,火
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.27,0:11:00.75,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 你明白自己的处境吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.36,0:11:02.91,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,火
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.15,0:11:25.01,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,恐吓我是没用的 我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.26,0:11:26.60,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,想开枪的就开枪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.57,0:11:32.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,算了由美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.44,0:11:36.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是对付不了这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.99,0:11:37.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.34,0:11:41.85,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,大…大家一起上 把…把她绑起来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.42,0:11:43.08,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,开枪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.28,0:11:44.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,全都听到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.49,0:11:50.18,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那样好吗 十三课
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.64,0:11:53.51,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那样做好吗 安德鲁森
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.76,0:11:55.78,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,愚蠢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.10,0:12:00.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,对一个手无寸铁的女性 以多欺少使其就范
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.99,0:12:02.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,简直是强奸魔的行径
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.18,0:12:06.51,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.13,0:12:10.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,一个女人走夜路可不安全 送我一程
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.01,0:12:13.71,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 那就送你一程
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.58,0:12:17.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我赶时间 快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.78,0:12:20.17,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.80,0:12:34.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这算啥啊 事态向着奇怪的方向发展了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.96,0:12:38.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么办 局长知道了又要发火了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:43.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这…这也算是监视啦 不会生气的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.44,0:12:45.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是狡辩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.38,0:12:46.94,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.17,0:12:51.82,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,海因克尔 去找车子来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.40,0:12:54.77,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去 简直像是去猎鸭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.58,0:12:58.75,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗 安德鲁森神父
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.89,0:13:01.96,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好会被追究责任的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.49,0:13:05.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 就这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.76,0:13:09.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,马克斯威尔的行事方法有些精明过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.84,0:13:17.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,即将抵达HELLSING本部上空
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.91,0:13:20.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 全员做好战斗准备
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.57,0:13:24.75,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,旗舰的支援射击要到了 是V1改飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.21,0:13:30.83,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,Deus Ex Machina准备的开胃菜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.82,0:13:34.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那就让HELLSING好好吃个够吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.00,0:13:43.78,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.70,0:13:48.36,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.23,0:13:53.53,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.78,0:13:55.51,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,V1改正被狙击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.43,0:13:58.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是HELLSING本部发出的射击
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.11,0:14:01.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.92,0:14:08.83,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,V1改 全弹尽毁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:13.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 这可是24发飞弹同时攻击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.73,0:14:19.38,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,打开探照灯 照亮HELLSING本部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.13,0:14:22.86,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,请三思 我们会成为狙击目标的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.44,0:14:26.22,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓 那女人早就看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.64,0:15:00.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,全弹击毁啊 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.46,0:15:05.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,新装备很顺手嘛 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.04,0:15:12.39,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,HALLCONNENⅡ 30mm半自动加农炮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.07,0:15:18.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,最远射程4000m 总重量345kg
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.62,0:15:23.53,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这种武器可真是搞笑啊 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.19,0:15:27.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,贝尔纳德队长 可以不要叫我小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.78,0:15:30.57,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.41,0:15:33.67,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那真是不好意思了 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.55,0:15:41.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,伦敦看得到吗 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.01,0:15:44.78,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.99,0:15:51.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,皮卡迪利广场 soho区
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.43,0:15:54.40,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,柯芬园 全都成了灰烬
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.34,0:16:00.05,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这个伦敦 现在就如同地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.03,0:16:03.86,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌伦敦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.61,0:16:06.77,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是个老朽的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.50,0:16:10.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是个完全不适合我的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.22,0:16:11.91,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.37,0:16:17.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们周末常去的那家酒馆的啤酒够冰爽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.99,0:16:22.36,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,酒保小哥是个喜欢讲低级笑话的傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.13,0:16:27.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然妓女们要价又狠丑女又多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.28,0:16:29.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.24,0:16:34.29,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很善良 都有着一双悲哀的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.08,0:16:41.90,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,巴比路上小吃店的阿婆每次都把我没点的炸鱼薯条硬塞给我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.31,0:16:48.22,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么外国人一定得尝尝 说什么这是英国名菜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.57,0:16:52.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我明明说过那东西太油腻我不爱吃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.06,0:16:56.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,可为了不伤阿婆的心只好每次都辛苦的吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.06,0:17:02.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌伦敦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.13,0:17:05.53,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.48,0:17:08.24,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,酒保 妓女 阿婆
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.24,0:17:10.92,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,和这场战争都毫无关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.67,0:17:14.78,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,战争 纳粹 吸血鬼 都与他们无关
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.28,0:17:18.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,少校 十三课
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.02,0:17:21.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,最后的大队 我们HELLSING
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.50,0:17:22.66,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,都不关他们的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.27,0:17:29.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 他们现在却都成了吞噬死尸的行尸走肉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.01,0:17:32.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这个我无法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.23,0:17:36.66,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯 让我们报仇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.64,0:17:43.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 把他们通通干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.03,0:17:46.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.04,0:17:48.26,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我都明白 队长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.59,0:17:50.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我都明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.55,0:18:03.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,目标 敌空中战舰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.44,0:18:05.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,炮击战 准备
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.95,0:18:11.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,放
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.66,0:18:26.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,多处中弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.59,0:18:29.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.93,0:18:34.51,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,把他们通通干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.51,0:18:49.75,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,第7、第3、第4区域中弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.16,0:18:55.05,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,第2兵员准备室爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.38,0:19:04.54,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,尾部第4、第5引擎崩坏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.12,0:19:21.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,飞行能力减损32%
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.07,0:19:25.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,中尉 战舰 战舰再不后撤的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.11,0:19:27.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,已经晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.88,0:19:36.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,在那种火力面前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.00,0:19:39.07,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这种轻合金装甲飞艇简直就像纸气球一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.68,0:19:41.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,体积又这么大 根本逃不掉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.51,0:19:45.11,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,下降 想办法着陆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.21,0:19:46.64,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,强行着陆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.06,0:19:48.87,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,撞向HELLSING本部 不
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.35,0:19:50.79,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,撞向那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.76,0:19:56.65,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯·维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.08,0:20:19.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,快跑 快跑啊塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.86,0:20:35.17,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,广域立体压制用爆炸燃烧迫击炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.90,0:20:37.58,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,VLadimir
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.57,0:21:03.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,无法控制 无法控制
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.66,0:21:06.12,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要 要坠毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.74,0:21:45.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了 成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.67,0:21:48.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,Tally-ho...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.67,0:21:48.62,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,Tally-ho ：空军航空术语  空战时 不借助雷达 而是直接使用肉眼确认到情况时使用的词
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.46,0:21:50.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,还没结束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.80,0:21:52.62,Hellsing,215,0000,0000,0000,,没错 还没结束呢Ladies
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.80,0:21:52.62,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,Ladys ：女士们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.18,0:21:55.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,睁大眼睛 要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.36,0:22:03.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,在即将坠毁前逃出来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.57,0:22:05.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能 身上什么装备都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.39,0:22:09.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 他们可不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.12,0:22:11.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.21,0:22:21.74,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.50,0:22:25.18,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐先退下来补给吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.41,0:22:27.16,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.35,0:22:40.42,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,看好哦 小姐 我们Geese的战斗方式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.35,0:22:40.42,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,Geese ：野鹅军团
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.32,0:22:47.97,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,好 前戏结束 他们要来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.56,0:22:52.58,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,开工吧  Rock'n'Roll
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.33,0:23:00.69,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,残存兵员42名 对方的弹头并非普通货色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.49,0:23:05.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们损失了半数以上的兵员和所有重武器
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.02,0:23:08.91,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但我等依然斗志昂扬
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.21,0:23:11.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,请下令 佐林·布里兹中尉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.09,0:23:17.24,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,足够了 足够杀光他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.60,0:23:20.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,杀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.20,0:23:25.96,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,全部击杀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.20,0:23:33.19,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 吸血鬼都是那样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:37.29,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有远超人类的反射神经和运动能力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.14,0:23:42.41,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,野兽般的杀气 以及可怕的蛮力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.20,0:23:46.43,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,能感受到人类的杀气 预测对方的动作
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.30,0:23:49.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,能窥测人心且应变迅速
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.68,0:23:53.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,无论枪击剑砍都能轻易闪躲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.35,0:23:55.86,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,打败对手之后还要食其血液
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.03,0:23:59.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这样又如何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.36,0:24:09.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,地雷区 是地雷区
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.40,0:24:14.96,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,他们停下了 杀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.53,0:24:37.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,Bingo
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.38,0:24:40.47,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是小看人类的下场
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.76,0:24:43.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这 这种机关
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.08,0:24:45.12,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,机关?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.79,0:24:49.47,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是那群蠢货想都没想 就从正前方冲过来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.80,0:24:53.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,即没杀气又没心灵更没动作的发动装置
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.17,0:24:56.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,再加上不是点而是面攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.76,0:25:01.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,面对60个同时引爆的祝福过的钢珠Claymore
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.87,0:25:02.01,Notes,,0000,0000,0000,,Claymore : 定向杀伤地雷
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.24,0:25:04.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,有本事闪的话就闪给我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.88,0:25:07.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们太弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.77,0:25:14.15,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,所以不敢与你们面对面交锋 军人先生们
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.76,0:25:19.74,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,3楼 燃烧榴弹齐射 连续发射张开火线
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.42,0:25:21.94,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,别给他们喘息的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.01,0:25:28.38,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,面攻击 要构成彻底的面攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.66,0:25:38.19,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,步枪分队把全部火力收拢到单一目标的周边
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.70,0:25:40.09,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,集中扫射
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.68,0:25:44.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长 他们停止前进了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.16,0:25:48.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,伏在小丘斜坡上 一动不动
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.12,0:25:51.78,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,肯定在打什么鬼主意
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.43,0:25:53.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不过这样也好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.13,0:25:57.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,只要不让对方靠近 我们就赢定了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.41,0:26:00.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我们第一次看家
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.01,0:26:02.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要好好努力
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.72,0:26:06.29,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要是让可怕的怪叔叔们进了家门我们可就输了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.26,0:26:10.26,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们太弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.88,0:26:22.70,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙会撤退吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.30,0:26:24.95,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是人都会
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.42,0:26:37.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要是人类的话 肯定会撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.07,0:26:40.87,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,可是他们不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.48,0:26:44.40,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.91,0:27:16.75,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,什 什
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.44,0:27:38.44,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.13,0:27:40.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.41,0:27:53.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.48,0:27:56.95,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我们不是在做梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.90,0:28:00.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你们在干什么 继续射击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.16,0:28:04.92,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不开火了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.42,0:28:08.07,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.76,0:28:16.31,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪门子玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.85,0:28:47.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么会有这种蠢事
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.04,0:29:11.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊                    怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.68,0:29:13.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,腿…我的腿
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.18,0:29:17.12,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,手…我的…我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.04,0:29:20.03,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.26,0:29:21.30,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,动不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.98,0:29:45.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的 这一定是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.69,0:29:49.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.77,0:29:55.58,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但我的体内有某样东西这样告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.19,0:30:02.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是你额头上的另一只眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.56,0:30:04.71,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是它告诉你的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.47,0:30:06.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,第三只眼
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.01,0:30:14.41,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,舍弃人类的眼睛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.55,0:30:17.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,人类遇到这种情况就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.00,0:30:21.09,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你已经不是人类了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.03,0:30:23.70,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.63,0:30:31.79,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.11,0:30:35.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.41,0:30:39.87,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,腿…我的腿                    怪物 救命
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.82,0:30:42.08,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,手…我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.16,0:30:43.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,振作 请振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.99,0:30:44.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.48,0:30:46.47,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.67,0:30:47.73,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,动不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.49,0:30:50.22,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是幻觉 都是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.05,0:30:55.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 这种事 怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.10,0:30:58.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长 那是幻觉 都是幻觉 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.16,0:31:00.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.25,0:31:54.90,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.65,0:31:58.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,手 还在
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.17,0:32:00.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.78,0:32:01.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.32,0:32:04.42,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.36,0:32:07.43,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,请振作些 那是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.98,0:32:09.24,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是幻术之类的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.75,0:32:11.72,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,幻术
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.30,0:32:14.56,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那些 是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.72,0:32:15.18,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.47,0:32:17.46,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,没错正是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.64,0:32:21.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,破得好 塞拉斯·维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.21,0:32:24.42,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 可是已经迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.73,0:33:12.08,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这下糟了 正面被突破了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.12,0:33:17.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是正门 敌兵已杀到玄关前
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.39,0:33:18.18,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要攻进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.32,0:33:32.77,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,集合分队
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.00,0:33:36.60,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,分散的队员也要叫他们想办法退回来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.17,0:33:39.17,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的队员都到这里集合
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.32,0:33:42.79,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,把能带的弹药和手榴弹都带过来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.15,0:33:45.79,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.62,0:33:47.07,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.61,0:33:50.53,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们死守这栋大宅
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.22,0:33:52.64,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们负责防御
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.45,0:33:54.68,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐负责进攻
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.14,0:33:57.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我们守住这里
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.82,0:34:01.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐要趁机干掉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.78,0:34:03.70,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.59,0:34:07.72,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐是我们的王牌
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.10,0:34:12.22,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要在我们没被碎尸万段前干掉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.41,0:34:17.44,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.98,0:34:28.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.38,0:34:31.28,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,忘了件很重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.91,0:34:32.74,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.84,0:34:33.92,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.52,0:34:35.60,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛闭上
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.80,0:34:49.41,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,你 你 你想干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.77,0:34:51.63,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长好奸诈
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.96,0:34:52.82,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,奸诈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.57,0:34:55.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 该出发了 快走
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.75,0:34:57.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是要事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.29,0:34:59.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 那么的话
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.00,0:35:02.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要 我也要...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.37,0:35:04.74,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.19,0:35:08.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,让我亲一口嘛… 我也要啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.36,0:35:11.98,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.80,0:35:17.40,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,可别死哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.21,0:35:19.21,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,不准死
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.08,0:35:25.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长和大家也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.20,0:35:35.27,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,好 出发
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.68,0:35:37.45,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,我出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.30,0:35:45.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.99,0:35:49.88,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋一样的好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.88,0:35:56.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,要是让这样的女孩死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.45,0:35:59.96,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那可就颜面扫地 该下地狱了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.39,0:36:01.19,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.59,0:36:03.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.17,0:36:06.46,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.46,0:36:07.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,正是正是
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.67,0:36:12.46,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那不好意思了 把你们的性命交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.72,0:36:15.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是你们的舍身之地
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.28,0:36:18.54,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,把此处当成坟墓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.16,0:36:23.49,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,队长 我说啊 这时的台词应该是
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.78,0:36:25.65,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,想逃的就趁现在快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.10,0:36:30.41,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,或者让部下都逃走 自己留下来 这样才对嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.15,0:36:32.67,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.03,0:36:39.55,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不都是为了钱 自愿沦落为佣兵的不孝子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.99,0:36:41.73,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊      没错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.09,0:36:43.76,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,也对
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.90,0:36:51.48,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 赴死吧恶犬们
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.94,0:36:54.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,一边喊着Fuck、Fuck赴死
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.44,0:36:58.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,一边吃着子弹 痛苦的挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.10,0:37:02.00,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.58,0:37:03.52,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.10,0:37:06.59,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.53,0:37:32.29,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,还早呢 战争才刚刚开始而已
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.59,0:37:38.13,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,会更加 更加的精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.57,0:37:45.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,若不是那样的话 会很失望的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.30,0:38:01.99,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,饶不了你们
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.15,0:38:05.16,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,谁也救不了你们
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.50,0:38:39.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(1550,100)}你怎么会射偏? \N 只有400-500米的距离!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.21,0:38:39.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(900,100)}白痴!!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.00,0:38:39.04,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,100)}妈的!!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.75,0:38:44.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(1550,120)}标准的小型武器不可能击中 \N 距离500米的目标!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.00,0:38:44.34,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(350,170)}但60D的怪物就可以击中!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.30,0:39:00.90,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(600,500)}满\N意\N了\N吗\N?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.06,0:39:03.23,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(600,170)}仔细看看,白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.95,0:39:06.94,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,500)}死\N吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.74,0:39:10.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(200,100)}射的好!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.74,0:39:10.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(1200,300)}杀了你!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.74,0:39:10.20,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(1250,500)}救我!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.29,0:39:19.08,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,啊!                啊!                啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.12,0:39:22.83,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(120,400)}瓦\N尔\N特\N先\N生
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.21,0:39:25.84,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(270,100)}我说,\N今天的训练结束了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.84,0:39:28.26,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(1350,470)}那是性,\N\N\N\N那是性,\N\N\N\N那是性骚扰!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.21,0:39:29.06,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(750,620)}他们边跑边吼着下流的歌!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.26,0:39:33.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(480,700)}爱\N斯\N基\N摩\N女\N人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.26,0:39:33.89,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(380,700)}的\N“猫”\N真\N冷\N!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.39,0:39:35.60,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1650,100)}真棒!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.50,0:39:36.62,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(500,100)}真棒!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.22,0:39:37.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1300,800)}对你有益
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.98,0:39:38.80,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(450,100)}对你有益
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.00,0:39:39.50,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1300,800)}对我有益
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.73,0:39:40.10,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(450,100)}对我有益
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.19,0:39:42.35,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,下流!                下流!                下流!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.61,0:39:46.61,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(1500,100)}我们可以开始了吗,\N佐林中尉?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.78,0:39:49.11,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(650,550)}你们要\N一起分享
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.86,0:39:53.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1400,200)}给我一部分躯干
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.37,0:39:55.87,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1500,200)}我也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.87,0:39:57.12,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1500,200)}不,那是我的...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.12,0:39:59.33,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(1600,300)}不对,那是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.33,0:39:59.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\pos(430,400)}安静点
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.37,0:40:02.37,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(1600,70)}我的! ...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.37,0:40:04.88,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(1000,70)}那是我的!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.62,0:40:04.88,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(920,770)}是我要的!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.00,0:40:04.88,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs68\pos(1600,720)}我的!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.42,0:40:04.88,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(430,400)}安静点...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.09,0:40:19.81,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1250,200)}不要在晚餐时间\N吵吵闹闹的!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.89,0:40:21.39,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1300,120)}是,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.10,0:41:01.18,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1550,470)}主要打击对象
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.71,0:41:43.69,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,冲进去
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.09,0:41:48.69,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,猛攻...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.09,0:41:48.69,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34}Sturm...（德语）
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.62,0:41:53.32,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那群混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.36,0:42:02.64,Hellsing,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 快点受死吧 杂碎们


