[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H0034a3d1,&Hff00ffff,&H12000000,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,15,15,11,134
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,38,&H00ffffff,&H004080ff,&Hff1fb5f5,&H403f98c2,-1,0,0,0,92,100,3,0.00,1,0,4,2,15,15,12,134
Style: OPJ,A-OTF TakaHand Std B,30,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,15,15,4,128
Style: EDJ,DFMaruGothic-Md,23,&H0034a3d1,&Hff00ffff,&H12000000,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,15,15,13,128
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,33,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,10,10,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00ffffff,&H005955fd,&H00000000,&H00ffffff,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: OPC,方正雅珠体简繁 DemiBold,34,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,15,15,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.76,0:00:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.06,0:00:22.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位客人 请问你们要坐在吸烟区还是禁烟区呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.12,0:00:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸烟区
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.82,0:00:26.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.39,0:00:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  请往这边走
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.71,0:00:33.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.11,0:00:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.39,0:00:37.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8号桌的客人  我这就端过去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.18,0:00:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5号的牛肉饼套餐可以上菜了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.49,0:00:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我把这些送过去以后确认一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.04,0:00:48.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得今天好忙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.89,0:00:49.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.05,0:00:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近偶尔会有出现人手不足的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.26,0:00:56.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐说要增加新的打工员
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.85,0:00:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的打工员啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.61,0:01:02.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤觉得新的打工员是男的好呢还是女的好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.54,0:01:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能干活  是男是女都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  其实我也觉得无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.77,0:01:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能来个有趣的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.64,0:01:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样都好  快点去做下一份菜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.71,0:01:13.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.10,0:01:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有17秒油炸套餐就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.19,0:01:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.59,0:01:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是感冒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.75,0:01:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.39,0:01:27.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.43,0:01:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧  种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.46,0:01:33.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被店长拜托去招打工员
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.80,0:01:38.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  总之先去问问学校的朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.85,0:01:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有就是到街上去试试劝诱路人什么的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.46,0:01:44.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波要帮我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.93,0:01:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去问问朋友的话倒是没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.84,0:01:50.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在街上劝…劝诱路人  我大概做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.28,0:01:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊  去街上的话就会有很多男人的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.73,0:01:57.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.92,0:01:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.16,0:02:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让您久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.39,0:02:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.85,0:02:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.97,0:03:10.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工…你要打工吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.43,0:03:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.25,0:03:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  你父母呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.63,0:03:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.09,0:03:21.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  爸爸和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.82,0:03:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  被来历不明的人劝诱打工自然会起疑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.64,0:03:31.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我爸爸是公务员  我妈妈是专职主妇
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.41,0:03:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不是这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.96,0:03:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.57,0:03:38.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就去那边的派出所吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.74,0:03:40.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非他以为我迷路了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.85,0:03:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.36,0:03:44.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来找家庭餐厅的打工者的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.40,0:03:46.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起打工
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.40,0:03:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  啊…怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.69,0:03:50.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过家家么  这实在是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.76,0:03:51.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.14,0:03:54.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  话说不通
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.66,0:03:57.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也抓不到其他人了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.31,0:03:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且感觉这人是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.07,0:04:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我叫种岛白杨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.05,0:04:06.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,17岁  是高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.31,0:04:08.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？高中生？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:10.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然…然后…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.86,0:04:12.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在找打工的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.76,0:04:15.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这本学生证和这套校服
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:17.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的高中前辈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.81,0:04:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅外表居然比我年龄大？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.72,0:04:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  12岁以上竟然如此可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.66,0:04:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上还真有这种事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.19,0:04:29.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是有的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要打工
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.32,0:04:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.98,0:04:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.36,0:04:40.99,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}北海道某处\N家庭餐厅“瓦古娜利亚”
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.42,0:04:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  从今天开始我来这里工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.44,0:04:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小鸟游宗太  16岁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.62,0:04:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然被人叫成“SHO CHO YU”或者“KO TORI ASOBI”过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.62,0:04:50.21,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注：“小鸟游”三个字的音读和训读  都不是正确的读法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.62,0:04:50.21,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注2：“小鸟游”读法的典故是“没有鹰  小鸟就能玩耍”\N因此与“鹰无（TA KA NA SHI）”谐音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.32,0:04:51.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我是“TA KA NA SHI”
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.09,0:04:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫种岛白杨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.01,0:04:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人希望我可以长得像白杨树一样高大所以取了这个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.08,0:04:58.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白杨树…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.37,0:05:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比你大一岁  有不懂的事情要和我说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.19,0:05:04.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.47,0:05:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都有奇怪的名字  都不要叫错了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.98,0:05:08.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.22,0:05:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就叫错了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.63,0:05:12.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是店长白藤杏子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.14,0:05:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他成员就让种岛来介绍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.88,0:05:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.29,0:05:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得店长是个可怕的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.01,0:05:22.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游也好羞鸟游也好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.40,0:05:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于工作我是不会给你任何建议的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.15,0:05:25.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要做好准备
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.22,0:05:29.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说工作要自己边看边学是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.73,0:05:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不大工作所以都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.84,0:05:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  工作的事就问我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.78,0:05:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.37,0:05:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.80,0:05:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.63,0:05:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害的店长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.44,0:05:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.40,0:05:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你真的帮了我大忙啦  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.31,0:05:49.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.06,0:05:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招募了也没人来  朋友也不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.28,0:05:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被店长拜托要我去找人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.36,0:05:58.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要打工吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.13,0:06:01.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.37,0:06:06.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候可以相遇也算是缘分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:09.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始一起加油吧  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.54,0:06:11.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.44,0:06:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我不叫羞鸟游  我叫小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.63,0:06:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.69,0:06:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…小…羞…小…羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.18,0:06:23.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞…羞…羞鸟…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.04,0:06:25.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.88,0:06:31.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那首先先把杯子的摆放方法告诉你  要认真看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.09,0:06:33.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.35,0:06:36.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个杯子呢  要放回这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.09,0:06:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.89,0:06:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我够不到  所以要找别人来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.67,0:06:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是把这个要洗的东西搬到洗碗池那里…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.68,0:07:09.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太重了我搬不动  这个也要请别人帮一下忙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.15,0:07:11.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.63,0:07:14.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也很努力想要教我工作的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.32,0:07:15.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.91,0:07:17.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.19,0:07:20.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙就是今天来的新人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.51,0:07:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.13,0:07:24.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小鸟游宗太  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.90,0:07:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是佐藤润  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.65,0:07:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人也和店长一样  是个看上去有点可怕的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.42,0:07:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤你现在有空吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.97,0:07:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  平常那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.11,0:07:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太高了我够不着  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.84,0:07:39.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.25,0:07:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太重了我搬不动  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.93,0:07:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.78,0:07:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  明白了吗  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.89,0:07:52.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.96,0:07:55.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己会干的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.91,0:07:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到佐藤是个好人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.38,0:08:05.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的头发好厚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.04,0:08:07.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.51,0:08:08.58,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是今天来的小鸟游吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.43,0:08:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.42,0:08:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫相马博臣  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:14.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.21,0:08:18.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是和种岛同一所高中的后辈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.30,0:08:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你还真清楚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.29,0:08:23.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是前辈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.78,0:08:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  和种岛前辈同一所高中的事有和谁说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.40,0:08:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛正在进行教育吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.69,0:08:33.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  现在在非常严格地教育他哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.66,0:08:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伟大呢  种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.35,0:08:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.12,0:08:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.54,0:08:38.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备做完了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.69,0:08:42.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.85,0:08:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点去准备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.80,0:08:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么两位要加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.13,0:08:51.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相马是个喜欢聊天的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.58,0:08:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  他看起来人也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.81,0:08:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.60,0:08:57.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我教你下一个工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.33,0:08:58.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.78,0:09:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢光临
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.16,0:09:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接客就是这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.50,0:09:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我明白了  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.92,0:09:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小白杨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.08,0:09:11.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.40,0:09:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天来的小鸟游？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.73,0:09:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.54,0:09:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.80,0:09:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和你打个招呼  正找你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.24,0:09:18.12,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个漂亮的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.14,0:09:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小鸟游宗太  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.40,0:09:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是领班  轰八千代
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:29.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游  请不要客气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.18,0:09:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不懂的请尽管问我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.33,0:09:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢…谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.24,0:09:39.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8号桌的客人好像在叫人  我过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.26,0:09:40.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.38,0:09:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  我想问下关于那个腰间挂着的危险物品的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.28,0:09:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种工作在家也经常干  一点都不会紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.49,0:09:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得虽然是不知不觉就接下的打工
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.95,0:09:59.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家人都挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.60,0:10:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时加加油好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.09,0:10:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.22,0:10:05.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我说啊  刚才啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.14,0:10:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我端菜过去的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.43,0:10:11.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人说“你是初中生吗”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.18,0:10:13.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分啊  人家明明是高中生来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.62,0:10:16.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了  前辈才不是初中生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.46,0:10:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.20,0:10:19.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小学生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.49,0:10:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对哦  我是高中生…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.74,0:10:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中生的话  不再长大点是不行的哦  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.13,0:10:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游  人家才不小呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.44,0:10:33.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游  我过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.69,0:10:34.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.16,0:10:39.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.73,0:10:42.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  怎么了  店长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.74,0:10:44.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我事先说一句
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.26,0:10:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和种岛关系好没事  可不要恋爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.28,0:10:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在写排班表的时候会很麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.33,0:10:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会有那回事  我们根本不可能恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.24,0:10:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.72,0:10:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤  请不要突然插进来说话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.98,0:11:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚好听到而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.72,0:11:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的话那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.44,0:11:07.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说我想成为前辈的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.19,0:11:11.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.03,0:11:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  那也不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.53,0:11:15.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.59,0:11:19.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话  我不想特别过问你的兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.55,0:11:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不要在店里动歪脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.48,0:11:25.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等等  莫非你们把我当萝莉控了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.81,0:11:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.75,0:11:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.89,0:11:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢的是小小的  可爱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.19,0:11:32.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.46,0:11:33.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.52,0:11:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.59,0:11:35.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仓鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.40,0:11:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.92,0:11:38.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水蚤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.35,0:11:42.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水蚤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.98,0:11:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呢  想保护不能独自活下去的弱小生物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.59,0:11:49.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.62,0:11:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我对前辈的感觉不是店长所想的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.78,0:11:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  虽然她比我大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.77,0:11:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她和小孩啊小狗一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.35,0:12:03.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛前辈对我来说和水蚤是一个等级的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.16,0:12:06.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再怎么样也不会和水蚤交往的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.73,0:12:10.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛和水蚤一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.43,0:12:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个过分的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.99,0:12:19.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  店长芳龄多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.09,0:12:21.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,28
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.33,0:12:23.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  年纪相当大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.43,0:12:29.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排班表变成一周上7天班了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.97,0:12:31.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.75,0:12:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.82,0:12:42.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.71,0:12:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也要上班？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.08,0:12:46.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这几周每天都有排班
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.68,0:12:48.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是累坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.91,0:12:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和杏子姐商量下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.67,0:12:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.69,0:12:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.86,0:12:56.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.68,0:12:58.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作已经习惯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.39,0:13:02.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领班  工作已经完全习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.60,0:13:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长  那个  我的排班表…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.28,0:13:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  想排得更满吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.38,0:13:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要试试看当领班啊  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.84,0:13:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…做错什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.96,0:13:18.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  年轻人嘛  拼命工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.99,0:13:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作加油哦  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.79,0:13:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长在生什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:28.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游你该不会对杏子姐说错什么话了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.55,0:13:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因为上年纪了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.86,0:13:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说上年纪了荷尔蒙会分泌失调变得有点歇斯底里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.56,0:13:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是更年期综合症
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.50,0:13:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是说错什么话了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.40,0:13:40.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？有说错什么话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.82,0:13:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长的态度转变  是从问过店长年龄的那天开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.84,0:13:49.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  店长芳龄多少
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.80,0:13:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,28
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.07,0:13:53.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  年纪相当大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.80,0:13:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游  就是那个啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.08,0:13:56.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？哪个？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.43,0:14:00.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对女孩子说“年纪相当大了呢”什么的是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.65,0:14:03.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是过了12岁的不都是老女人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.62,0:14:04.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太小了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.84,0:14:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不不  前辈你完全不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.63,0:14:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不算老女人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.29,0:14:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个  到了那个年龄段的人会变得很敏感的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.26,0:14:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不能说那种话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.54,0:14:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊  必须去道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.01,0:14:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.27,0:14:23.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老女人就是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.70,0:14:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.52,0:14:29.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  羞鸟游  快去向杏子姐道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.68,0:14:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  明白了  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.66,0:14:33.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.43,0:14:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店里的暖气温度太高了  快想点办法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.66,0:14:40.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就滚出店  把那丑陋的脂肪燃烧殆尽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.43,0:14:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.19,0:14:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.83,0:14:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能对客人口出狂言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.52,0:14:50.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说把暖气关小点就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.02,0:14:52.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.29,0:14:54.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长要有店长的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.36,0:14:57.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说  请你以一个普通成年人的礼仪待客
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.16,0:15:01.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好做的话  店的口碑会变差的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.76,0:15:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传出去的话的确会很麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.03,0:15:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不如…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.82,0:15:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.56,0:15:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她关进冰箱里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.43,0:15:10.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿点冷饮做赔礼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.29,0:15:15.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.36,0:15:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是做赔礼的饮料
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.52,0:15:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暖气也会关小一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.47,0:15:22.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果还有不满意的地方  请随时指教
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.17,0:15:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  其实也没有不满意啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.11,0:15:28.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.77,0:15:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…  是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.36,0:15:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实感觉比刚才凉快点了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.56,0:15:35.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.52,0:15:37.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果还有什么要求的话  请随时吩咐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.28,0:15:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.78,0:15:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后就不要再指望那个店长了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.60,0:15:45.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.97,0:15:50.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…  店长她总是那样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:53.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  店长一直都是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.42,0:15:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.34,0:15:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.23,0:15:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小矮子是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.95,0:16:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这店里让小学生打工的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.97,0:16:03.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小妹妹  上几年级啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.89,0:16:07.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要这样  我是高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.65,0:16:08.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.35,0:16:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.09,0:16:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.93,0:16:10.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.09,0:16:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给那家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.59,0:16:14.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？交给谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.53,0:16:15.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  好好看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.04,0:16:19.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位客人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.28,0:16:24.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.43,0:16:26.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.15,0:16:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位客人  暴力是不对的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.74,0:16:35.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有踢飞客人的店员  叫店长出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.95,0:16:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.55,0:16:40.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有踢飞客人的店长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.63,0:16:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后再也不会来这店了  臭老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.83,0:16:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种店快给我倒闭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.94,0:16:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  还没结帐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.71,0:16:49.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种岛  没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.04,0:16:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长做出那种事了哦  这样可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.05,0:16:54.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.48,0:16:55.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说这个了  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.09,0:16:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.22,0:16:59.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  店长的手机  给她送过去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.81,0:17:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？这是店长的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.97,0:17:04.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在相马手里…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.24,0:17:05.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.48,0:17:11.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长  相马让我把这个拿给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.19,0:17:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要报警吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.37,0:17:16.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要把事情闹大比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.39,0:17:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  刚才出门的客人  把他们身上的钱全拿来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.81,0:17:24.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  我有很靠得住的后辈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.06,0:17:26.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这店长是何等人物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.04,0:17:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游  今后也会很辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.65,0:17:31.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.93,0:17:35.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会尽量用不被立案的方法解决的  不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.55,0:17:36.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立案？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.51,0:17:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐  其实不用这么夸张
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.49,0:17:41.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说努力工作的种岛是小矮子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人多少也有保护店里工作人员的心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.21,0:17:49.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  还骂我是臭老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.85,0:17:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.15,0:17:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还骂我是臭老太婆…  臭老太婆…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.82,0:17:54.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.82,0:17:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主要原因是那个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.27,0:17:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.12,0:17:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.16,0:18:01.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的事  真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.42,0:18:03.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…年龄的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.39,0:18:06.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现店长比实际年龄要年轻得多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.59,0:18:06.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.16,0:18:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  深刻体会到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.18,0:18:10.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长  就是一小鬼头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.73,0:18:14.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.53,0:18:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  下周的排班表  有一天休息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.13,0:18:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟 今天会继续严厉指导你工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.44,0:18:27.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许你哭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.95,0:18:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长 我可以抱一下她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.40,0:18:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.47,0:18:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小游鸟学东西很快 但偶尔会把我的话当耳边风
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.95,0:18:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.02,0:18:42.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于小游鸟如此在意我的身高
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.57,0:18:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是今天我带来了秘密武器
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.01,0:18:47.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 现在反倒更在意你刚才的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.46,0:18:49.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的秘密武器到底是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.63,0:18:52.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踏台
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.98,0:18:58.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话小游鸟就不会在意了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.38,0:19:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说 现在我们都一样高了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.31,0:19:02.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.91,0:19:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这东西携带不方便 还是用不着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.48,0:19:10.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.62,0:19:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是想抱一下 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.37,0:19:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.22,0:19:25.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经完全习惯这边的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.25,0:19:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经习惯这里的自己也有点恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.28,0:19:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.64,0:19:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了  羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.50,0:19:38.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  我上班也有一段时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.30,0:19:41.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个叫伊波的人我还没见过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.35,0:19:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个么…  小伊是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.07,0:19:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  种岛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.59,0:19:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.49,0:19:47.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.87,0:19:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.13,0:19:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  羞鸟游  我先去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.01,0:19:55.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  过段时间就能见到的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.16,0:20:12.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让您久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.11,0:20:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后台还有存货  能帮我拿一箱来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.45,0:20:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.67,0:20:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  放在相当高的地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.05,0:20:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊  不好意思  还麻烦你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.34,0:20:33.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.76,0:20:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  今天是第一次和伊波小姐同班次
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.24,0:20:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.29,0:20:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是伊波小姐吗  你好…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.28,0:20:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.18,0:20:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似又来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.71,0:21:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.26,0:21:05.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然之间搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.50,0:21:06.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.21,0:21:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.22,0:21:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.23,0:21:11.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且算是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.48,0:21:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伊  小伊冷静一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.77,0:21:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.59,0:21:17.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.53,0:21:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怕的是你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.18,0:21:21.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀  小昼你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.73,0:21:24.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代姐  有男人  有男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.26,0:21:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最近新来的打工员  小鸟游
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.56,0:21:29.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有男人啊  很危险的  八千代姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.20,0:21:30.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好还带着武器
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.75,0:21:33.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小昼真的很怕男生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.25,0:21:35.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然说武器…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.66,0:21:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游  介绍一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.94,0:21:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是有男性恐惧症的伊波真昼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.20,0:21:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会因为太害怕而袭击男性  请当心别被杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.09,0:21:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…当心别被杀掉？！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.35,0:21:53.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子可是很猛的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.23,0:21:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有点怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.83,0:21:57.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为事关性命
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.27,0:22:00.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐说过不会和小鸟游排到同一班次的…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.65,0:22:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  今天伊波有排班吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:07.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排错了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.63,0:22:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.83,0:22:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.86,0:22:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被娇小可爱的前辈介绍来打工的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.77,0:22:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是家聚集着一堆怪人的餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.33,0:22:20.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正当我以为自己渐渐习惯这里的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:23.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于男性恐惧症的伊波小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.25,0:22:26.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我也不得不感到有生命危险
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.30,0:22:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.14,0:22:30.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个普通人  能够适应这环境吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.19,0:22:34.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  能和娇小可爱的前辈一起的工作  我不想辞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.61,0:22:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  你果然是萝莉控吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.51,0:22:38.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不是萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.53,0:22:41.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  硬要说的话  我是喜欢小东西的迷你控
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.28,0:22:44.41,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}第1道菜\N欢迎来到瓦古娜利亚～小鸟游、工作。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.06,0:22:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鸟游也是个十足的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.20,0:22:47.03,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone(one one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.20,0:22:47.03,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone(one one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.15,0:22:49.14,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone one else
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.15,0:22:49.14,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone one else
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.20,0:22:51.09,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone(one one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.20,0:22:51.09,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone(one one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.19,0:22:53.55,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone one else
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.19,0:22:53.55,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}someone(one one)　someone one else
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.77,0:22:55.43,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.77,0:22:55.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.59,0:22:57.45,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.59,0:22:57.45,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.61,0:22:59.52,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.61,0:22:59.52,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:01.30,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(Yheay!)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:01.30,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(Yheay!)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.54,0:23:03.38,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}だれかが好きだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.54,0:23:03.38,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}喜欢某个人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.58,0:23:05.42,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}あなたも好きだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.58,0:23:05.42,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}也好喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.63,0:23:07.48,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}もっときゅっと距離を
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.63,0:23:07.48,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}再缩短一些距离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.69,0:23:09.53,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}埋めてみようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.69,0:23:09.53,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}紧紧拥抱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.75,0:23:11.57,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}働くのが好きだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.75,0:23:11.57,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}工作是喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.77,0:23:13.72,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}サボルのは　恋だ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.77,0:23:13.72,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}可翘班也是为了恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.91,0:23:15.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}えっとポっと　ここで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.91,0:23:15.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}还想迷迷糊糊地
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.97,0:23:17.77,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}過ごしていたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.97,0:23:17.77,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在这里生活
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.02,0:23:26.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}はるか遠くに　ユート{\rOPC}·{\r}ピアが　見えるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.02,0:23:26.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那遥远的地方　可以看到乌托邦哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.24,0:23:34.00,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}君の瞳の　温泉{\rOPC}·{\r}に　入ろぉ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.24,0:23:34.00,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}跳进你眼中的温泉！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.36,0:23:40.64,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}たましいゴーンと　鐘を　打たれたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.36,0:23:40.64,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果连灵魂都小鹿乱撞的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.88,0:23:42.53,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}（打たれちゃったら）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.88,0:23:42.53,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}（小鹿乱撞的话）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.74,0:23:48.50,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}産毛フワフワ　夢なでられたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.74,0:23:48.50,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}像胎毛一样软绵绵　触感如梦如幻的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.89,0:23:50.61,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}すすめ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.89,0:23:50.61,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}前进吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.75,0:23:57.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}切なさホロリの真ん中　射抜かれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.75,0:23:57.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}苦闷落泪之时正中红心的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.39,0:23:59.06,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}（射抜かれちゃったら）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.39,0:23:59.06,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}（正中红心的话）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.18,0:24:05.08,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}くるぶしグリグリ　骨が　感じてるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.18,0:24:05.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}转一转脚踝　骨头嘎吱嘎吱响的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.34,0:24:09.60,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}汗をかきましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.34,0:24:09.60,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}去流一身汗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.70,0:24:09.64,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.70,0:24:09.64,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}(one one someone one)
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.61,0:24:12.83,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}(Yheay!)
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.61,0:24:12.83,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}(Yheay!)

Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.25,0:24:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集预告
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.71,0:24:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…遭到了很残酷的对待
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.64,0:24:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.75,0:24:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  还好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.05,0:24:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说伊波小姐是个什么样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.67,0:24:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个非常乖的孩子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.07,0:24:26.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里乖了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.84,0:24:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.45,0:24:30.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“伊波、男性恐惧症。因为很可怕呀…”
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.23,0:24:31.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  因为你个头啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.52,0:24:33.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…啊…敬请期待！
