[Script Info]
Title:Asoiku BD 02 gb
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00335ADA,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H1E001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DCPHoLeiSho-W3,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H003759D5,&H960304FE,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,8,1
Style: EDCN,方正隶变_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H003759D5,&H960304FE,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,8,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H1E001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DCPHoLeiSho-W3,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H003759D5,&H960304FE,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,8,1
Style: OPCN,方正隶变_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H003759D5,&H960304FE,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.96,0:21:56.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}未体験なの
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.80,0:22:02.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}目の前に　答えは色々あるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.50,0:22:08.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}ひとつの大空を何等分できる？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.73,0:22:11.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}楽しいから全てをください
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.52,0:22:13.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}あたしってば独占したい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.42,0:22:16.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}本音がこぼれるよ　{\fn方正隶变_GBK\fs20}Blue Sky
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.77,0:22:17.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}もうっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.00,0:22:21.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}名前を書いておこう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.74,0:22:24.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}消えないように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.42,0:22:26.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}真剣になったら？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.28,0:22:31.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}そ～ゆ～のヤダなんて言わせない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.58,0:22:38.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}純愛装置{\fn方正隶变_GBK\fs20}/Set Up Now/{\r}動きだせ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.33,0:22:42.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}焦りと夢の滑走路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}シートベルトはもっとぎゅっと致して
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.39,0:22:52.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}最新装置{\fn方正隶变_GBK\fs20}/Back Up Now/{\r}動きだす
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.06,0:22:57.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}あなたの心だけは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.25,0:23:04.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}オリジナルが欲しくて　作戦立てましたよ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.96,0:21:56.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}还未体验过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.80,0:22:02.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}就在眼前的  答案却有很多很多
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.50,0:22:08.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}将这一个广阔天空能分成几等分？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.73,0:22:11.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}因为很开心  所以把全部都给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.52,0:22:13.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}我想要将一切都独占
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.42,0:22:16.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}真心话要说漏了  Blue Sky
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.77,0:22:17.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.00,0:22:21.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}把名字写在这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.74,0:22:24.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}希望它不会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.42,0:22:26.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}要是认真起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.28,0:22:31.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}不会让你说「这种事我不干」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.58,0:22:38.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}纯爱装置/Set Up Now/动起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.33,0:22:42.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}焦急和梦想的跑道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}安全带要更紧更贴地系起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.39,0:22:52.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}最新装置/Back Up Now/动起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.06,0:22:57.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}只有你的心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.25,0:23:04.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be1}想要原版的  作战方案已拟定好了哦
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.04,0:01:23.05,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(280,275)}我来找你玩了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.14,0:00:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自彼方的访问者  终于遇见了不错的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.76,0:00:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.25,0:00:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  那一副cosplay一样的装扮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.23,0:00:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不长成超乎人类想像的外形呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.68,0:00:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起外星人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.74,0:00:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是精神生命体啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着生态加速装置的硅生物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.64,0:00:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机械化智慧生物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.86,0:00:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是像有着放射状对称的外骨骼的生物一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.96,0:00:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「啊  这才是来自广阔宇宙的使者」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.10,0:00:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要这副样子才能让人接受嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.30,0:00:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为「星际旅行」的影迷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.48,0:00:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎会容忍如此偷工减料的外星人存在
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.45,0:00:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了美好的接触
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.95,0:00:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了美好的接触
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.27,0:00:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会让长成那样的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.56,0:00:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为人类的第一次接触的对象
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.12,0:00:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.08,0:00:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.64,0:00:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这道菜叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.80,0:01:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们叫它「烤肉」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.67,0:01:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑色部分的香甜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.17,0:01:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配上紧绷的肉的口感
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.81,0:01:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上被米饭的热量融化的油脂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.72,0:01:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  太棒了  真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.61,0:01:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来到地球真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.65,0:01:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝你们为什么会进行宇宙旅行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.93,0:01:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主要的目的是观光和扩展交流范围
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.39,0:01:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们凯提亚星人不管在文化上还是在基因上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.04,0:01:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都感觉已经走到了尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.08,0:01:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走到尽头？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.09,0:01:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社会安定已经持续了七万年
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.12,0:01:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做的基本都做完了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.69,0:01:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们才前往宇宙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.63,0:01:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与外族人展开交流  接受刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.82,0:01:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么一回事    嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.43,0:01:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福的青鸟居然离你这么近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.84,0:02:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  JACK
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲绳本来就是不方便展开工作的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.23,0:02:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要研究作战计划  所以支援工作就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.01,0:02:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇宙探险吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人羡慕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.72,0:02:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羡慕什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.43,0:02:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是充满梦想的工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.09,0:02:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没找到  自己想从事的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.25,0:02:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奈美已经决定做基地内的员工了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.93,0:02:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我还不太清楚这个星球的社会制度
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.44,0:02:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得只要不放弃就好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.84,0:02:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不放弃？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.87,0:02:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  不放弃寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.41,0:02:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.50,0:02:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.23,0:02:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于报酬的问题…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.56,0:02:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报酬？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.84,0:02:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙你如此费心的关照
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.48,0:02:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照这里的社会状态
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.57,0:02:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,支付报酬也是理所当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.80,0:02:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.98,0:03:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  在交流尚未正式化之时
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.60,0:03:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不能使用货币
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.68,0:03:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是用其他东西支付的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.76,0:03:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根…根据我读到的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.53,0:03:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候要…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.80,0:03:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要以身相许…什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.68,0:03:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.01,0:03:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方的生殖系统也很相似
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.91,0:03:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概能够进行这种行为什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.58,0:03:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给…给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.02,0:03:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底看了什么资料
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.52,0:03:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央床下的书上是这么写的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.70,0:03:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.38,0:03:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是虚构的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.06,0:03:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.34,0:03:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我只有十六周年期
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.59,0:03:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对生殖行为完全没有经验
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.47,0:03:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.16,0:03:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太…太好了  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.94,0:03:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.54,0:03:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肮脏！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.73,0:03:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  拿好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.26,0:04:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.82,0:04:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  是梦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.90,0:04:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是处在不同世界里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.08,0:04:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.03,0:04:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在种什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.50,0:04:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝说要给我介绍…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.74,0:04:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介绍？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.37,0:04:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全员列队
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.08,0:04:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指定动作  跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.92,0:04:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自傲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.45,0:04:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反省
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.42,0:04:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唱歌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.11,0:04:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我判断机能正常
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.93,0:04:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这些是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.06,0:05:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小帮手机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.57,0:05:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要把这个纳米机械胶囊撒在地上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能重建土壤的成分而生长出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让他们帮忙调查
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.10,0:05:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要在我家里也种一些呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.97,0:05:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  今天也好热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.62,0:05:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝很怕热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.69,0:05:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你等一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.55,0:05:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  这样就能稍微消消暑了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.43,0:05:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.45,0:05:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.79,0:05:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉快又甜又滑溜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.35,0:05:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.38,0:05:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.65,0:05:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什么口味的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.38,0:05:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红芋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.31,0:05:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以吃一口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.41,0:05:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.47,0:05:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  赶快给我解决掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.42,0:05:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在人太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.29,0:06:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太着急可不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.06,0:06:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查了这么多  大概一周内就能整理出重要的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.87,0:06:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.19,0:06:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这么热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.42,0:06:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得已经凉快多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.29,0:06:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还吃冰淇淋吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.38,0:06:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.42,0:06:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.52,0:06:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时候差不多了  红叶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.78,0:07:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七式  启动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.84,0:07:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  怎么没人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停电？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.53,0:07:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.83,0:07:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.51,0:07:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是秘密组织「Beautiful Contact」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.51,0:07:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个外星人！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.60,0:07:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.95,0:07:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为了人类的发展
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.74,0:07:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝与你们的种族进行接触
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.12,0:07:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即给我离开这个星球！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.50,0:07:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况变了  紧急待机
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.22,0:07:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JACK
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.19,0:07:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先看看情况再说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.04,0:07:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  不好意思  请问您是哪位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.49,0:07:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是人类的代表
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.15,0:07:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  具体地说是哪些人的代表呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.20,0:07:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有知道的必要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.53,0:07:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来调查地球的状况的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.39,0:07:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然承蒙您赐教
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.42,0:08:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我必须了解你们组织的详细情况
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.96,0:08:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此  请告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.74,0:08:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不能说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.78,0:08:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.91,0:08:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是秘密组织
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.02,0:08:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.69,0:08:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没注意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在耍我们玩吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.53,0:08:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.62,0:08:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.87,0:08:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.19,0:08:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.23,0:08:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.74,0:08:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.27,0:08:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,S1  装备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.59,0:08:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,优先解决目标
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.55,0:08:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.00,0:09:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好轻…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.71,0:09:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.29,0:09:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.00,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.48,0:09:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘉和君…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.87,0:09:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央  快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.91,0:09:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝什么坏事也没做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.34,0:09:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要杀她
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.68,0:09:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢…谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.53,0:09:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.40,0:09:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  爱丽丝也没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.23,0:09:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  继续进行任务
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.00,0:09:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据现场判断  作战中止
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.35,0:09:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么任性  红叶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.43,0:09:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘉和君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.09,0:09:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.29,0:09:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必连骑央也…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.23,0:10:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.26,0:10:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了吗  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雄一叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.88,0:10:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.83,0:10:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是为捡你回来就费好大劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.40,0:10:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须去救她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.79,0:10:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是积极啊  我的侄子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.47,0:10:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.05,0:10:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝明明什么都没做…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.10,0:10:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是因为这件事爱丽丝讨厌地球了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.60,0:10:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家要怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.29,0:10:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要去救她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.53,0:10:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要告诉她  至少还有一个人站在她这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.39,0:10:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奈美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.75,0:10:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央？  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.41,0:10:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道爱丽丝在哪里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.56,0:10:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.26,0:10:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.32,0:10:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.93,0:10:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.44,0:10:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才  我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.87,0:10:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同一个地方带着同一道伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.96,0:11:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和真奈美的手表一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.91,0:11:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是真奈美吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.48,0:11:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.86,0:11:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做出这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.07,0:11:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要立功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.12,0:11:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我准备成为基地内的员工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.78,0:11:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.56,0:11:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准确的说  是基地内CIA的本地协助员
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.17,0:11:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.96,0:11:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.37,0:11:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  已经过去的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.34,0:11:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请告诉我爱丽丝在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.70,0:11:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是在嘉手纳基地的F号格纳库
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.28,0:11:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想进入基地可没那么容易
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.45,0:11:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就找人带路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.74,0:11:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.11,0:11:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,S&W的M686
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.82,0:11:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装的是麻醉弹  所以放心开枪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.63,0:11:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…叔叔到底是做什么工作的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.23,0:11:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没你的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.78,0:12:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面就由我们来处理了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.12,0:12:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令CIA？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.14,0:12:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DIA也变得了不起了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.30,0:12:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊  我们不都是人民公仆嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.73,0:12:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  上世纪的臭遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.49,0:12:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\i1}你好  是副官大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.00,0:12:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\i1}啊  确认下情况
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.97,0:12:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我是双叶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.81,0:12:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好  我是嘉和
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.95,0:12:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.03,0:12:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊  关于明天的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.30,0:12:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.31,0:12:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.07,0:12:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然有急事  说不定暂时回不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.42,0:12:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.72,0:12:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  发生了很多事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.54,0:12:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一回来我就会打电话给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.22,0:12:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.24,0:12:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么再见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.62,0:12:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真失败呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.03,0:12:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来政府没有和他们建交的打算
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和我们的目的正好…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.59,0:13:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.82,0:13:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  请不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.00,0:13:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.20,0:13:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糸嘉州老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.80,0:13:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  茄子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.79,0:13:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.35,0:13:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把这张照片散布在网络上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.93,0:13:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「硬派SF秘密组织Beautiful Contact的成员们」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.27,0:13:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不想这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.53,0:13:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是被讨厌了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.30,0:13:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.78,0:13:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是Y字车牌
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.45,0:13:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是时间刚好的关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.30,0:13:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基地里的人全都是星际迷航迷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.02,0:13:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在播放那个的时候  能力都会低于三成
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.67,0:14:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.68,0:14:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.26,0:14:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真头疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.93,0:14:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,You look confused (你看上去很迷茫)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.65,0:14:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,What you…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.30,0:14:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.49,0:14:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会被怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.28,0:14:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要请你去死
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.63,0:14:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们存在着就是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.90,0:14:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会损害到我们的国家利益
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.31,0:14:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不正式地拒绝和我们交流呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.94,0:14:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有先约了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.54,0:14:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有必要回答你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.38,0:14:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.10,0:14:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.35,0:14:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有狗的气味哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.28,0:14:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.37,0:14:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据宇宙的法规  和狗的交流可是属于「走私贸易」的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.21,0:14:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这种生物应该要尽快处理掉才对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.17,0:14:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.88,0:14:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放烟花喽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.29,0:14:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  再来一发
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.88,0:15:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们打算干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.55,0:15:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去救爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.05,0:15:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以  太危险了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.67,0:15:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝现在更危险
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.58,0:15:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  这之后请步行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.96,0:15:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我来吸引敌人的注意力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.43,0:15:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  这样就不可能成为CIA的成员了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.27,0:15:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是会就此被日本政府通缉的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.62,0:15:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  会用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.86,0:15:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和MGC一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.33,0:15:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.12,0:15:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伎俩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.29,0:16:00.11,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(0,500)}(请不要捡走)
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.97,0:16:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这里吗  F号格纳库
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.72,0:16:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  外面到底发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.80,0:16:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  差不多该让我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.07,0:16:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.55,0:16:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件衣服  是简易型的强化服
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.36,0:16:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对擅自跟犬人进行走私行为的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不用手下留情的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.08,0:16:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.51,0:16:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.24,0:16:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.90,0:16:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.03,0:16:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.52,0:17:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么为什么  当然是来救你的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.08,0:17:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那外面的混乱是骑央你？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.01,0:17:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看这样或许不来也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.72,0:17:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.58,0:17:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常的高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.31,0:17:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.26,0:17:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以了啦  可以了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.73,0:17:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  到此为止了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.48,0:17:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雄一叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.98,0:17:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.96,0:17:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.04,0:17:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救出爱丽丝了  现在正坐在糸嘉州老师的车上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.40,0:17:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在飞行跑道汇合吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.83,0:17:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  真奈美和双叶？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.13,0:18:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  你还挺受欢迎的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.92,0:18:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之后要怎么逃脱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.70,0:18:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是请直升机来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.02,0:18:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们能好好开过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.61,0:18:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.89,0:18:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.84,0:18:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.49,0:18:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样停到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.79,0:18:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦克
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  万事休矣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.09,0:18:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  双叶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.13,0:18:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要把那些战斗机械除掉就可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.01,0:18:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.96,0:18:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  全体准备解除武装
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.27,0:18:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对准目标  开始突击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.29,0:18:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太乱来了  爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.95,0:18:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  我也会上的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.72,0:19:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.16,0:19:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拟似反物质槌  准备
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.26,0:19:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  都变成光之尘埃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.27,0:19:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一事件  被作为收容装置的爆炸事故公布
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.69,0:19:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真相从此不为世人所知
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.03,0:19:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就像什么事都没有发生一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.54,0:20:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暑假像往常一样一天天地过去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.94,0:20:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是全部的数据吧  还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.37,0:20:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  今天不去图书馆了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.75,0:20:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  绝大部分的数据都已经复制完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.20,0:20:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报告书我也送回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.03,0:20:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  要回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.31,0:20:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  受您照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.68,0:20:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊  是工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.66,0:20:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.53,0:20:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候你来救我让我非常高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.72,0:20:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会到那么危险的地方  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.09,0:20:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  啊  那个  我们是朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.90,0:20:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.90,0:20:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再过一阵子就要进入第一次的发情期了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.29,0:20:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发情…期？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.58,0:20:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  如果可以的话  骑央
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.85,0:20:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能做我的交配对象
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.18,0:20:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交配对象
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.10,0:20:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.77,0:20:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑央  不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.40,0:21:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘉和  那个  看电视
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.16,0:21:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  为什么母舰会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.73,0:21:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝  爱丽丝在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.26,0:21:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主任  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.34,0:21:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是再多看看情况的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.91,0:21:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不  报告上不是有「烤肉」这个料理的味觉记忆数据吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.13,0:21:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个在母舰里引起了很强的热潮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.70,0:21:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都说「一定要吃一吃烤肉」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.69,0:21:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就打算快点正式缔结友好条约
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.19,0:21:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为先遣队派到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.34,0:21:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.57,0:21:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊  有点突然
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.32,0:21:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.22,0:23:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就失败了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.47,0:23:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  这星球上的全是废物
Comment: 0,0:00:00.45,0:00:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生送上门来的留宿会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.65,0:23:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既高兴又害羞的共浴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.45,0:23:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生禁止的睡衣聚会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.95,0:23:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥特女仆的突发事件
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.30,0:23:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.07,0:23:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来借住了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.69,0:23:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到你这来  找你玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.40,0:23:41.40,NEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(300,275)}次回  我来借住了


