[Script Info]
Title:Sankarea 14 sc
Original Script:澄空学园
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00838383,&H00620062,&H00480048,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,1
Style: Staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H141F1F1F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: EDTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00141414,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPCN,方正中等线_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,8,134
Style: OPJP,DFGGothicP-W5,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,8,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFGHSMincho-W3,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,10,10,128
Style: Note1,方正稚艺_GBK,18,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,134
Style: Note2,方正中等线_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000F0F0F,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,5,134
Style: Movie1,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00C2BEBC,&HF0000000,&H001B1B1B,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Note3,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.97,0:05:29.02,OPTitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\be3}{\pos(493,294)}「身为僵尸…心为…」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.73,0:03:37.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠れない夜に聞いた物語が　
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.05,0:03:41.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}絵空事だとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.37,0:03:58.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永遠を知るより快楽を求めて　
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.61,0:04:02.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.79,0:04:08.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ココロの深くに棲みついた影から　
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.98,0:04:12.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.29,0:04:18.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それでもあたしはあたしを　
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.57,0:04:22.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.14,0:04:28.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分に割れた太陽が朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.41,0:04:33.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}闇に慣れた神経をじわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.63,0:04:38.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}置き忘れた脳内はあえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.99,0:04:43.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シナリオの消えた物語だ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.55,0:04:48.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由に自由に舵を取って
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.93,0:04:55.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと高くへ舞い上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.73,0:03:37.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在无法入眠的夜晚  所听到的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.05,0:03:41.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}假若只是子虚乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.37,0:03:58.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}与其知晓永恒  不如追求快乐 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.61,0:04:02.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}懊恼着如今
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.79,0:04:12.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}是为了逃避  在心灵深处隐藏的阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.29,0:04:22.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使如此  我还是能够深爱着自己
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.14,0:04:28.41,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分为两半的太阳为我带来晨光
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.41,0:04:33.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}刺激着适应了黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.63,0:04:38.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遗忘了的记忆尽管就让它遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.99,0:04:43.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如同失去了剧本的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.55,0:04:48.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由地  自由地  把握住方向
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.93,0:04:55.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}向着更高的地方飞舞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.64,0:22:29.19,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.64,0:22:41.08,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君の手の中　揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.48,0:22:47.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:55.70,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君ともしはぐれたとしても　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.21,0:23:06.30,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.65,0:23:24.30,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:31.96,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.64,0:22:29.19,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只有一个愿望  能够实现的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.64,0:22:41.08,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}希望能变成  在你手中摇曳着的小小花朵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.48,0:22:47.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}第一次看到  这个耀眼的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:55.70,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果和你走散了　也一定能
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.21,0:23:06.30,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.65,0:23:24.30,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}醒来睁开眼  就在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:31.96,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明天也是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.20,0:00:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人  饭菜已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.89,0:00:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.28,0:00:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.67,0:01:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  作为班级的代表参加辩论大会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.88,0:01:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.26,0:01:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为学习和运动都很优秀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.36,0:01:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个完美无瑕的大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.47,0:01:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.93,0:01:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说完美无瑕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.46,0:01:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.75,0:01:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让其他学校的男生送到校门口的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.68,0:01:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是完美无瑕？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.73,0:01:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟也是理事长您的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.23,0:01:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么点事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.58,0:01:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给予一些处分的话无法警示众人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.20,0:01:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不要对大小姐的私生活进行干涉的指示…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.04,0:01:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是我们家的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.84,0:01:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就特别对待的话  这可不是我丈夫所希望的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.84,0:01:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:01:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不至于说什么停学退学
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.77,0:02:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,训诫  警告什么的  能有很多做法的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.54,0:02:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那么就以口头严重警告…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.95,0:02:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给予相当的处罚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.12,0:02:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是命令
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.35,0:02:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.25,0:02:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五月
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.30,0:02:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.63,0:02:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也喝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.29,0:02:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我还在执勤中  所以还是不必了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.36,0:02:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管那么多了  喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.94,0:02:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.95,0:02:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都是这样当我是傻瓜  我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.87,0:02:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人  您再喝下去会伤身体的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.40,0:02:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.17,0:02:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人  您还是先休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.52,0:02:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不管怎么都要把我当傻瓜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.16,0:03:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  每个人都是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.53,0:03:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都当我是傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.70,0:05:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.45,0:05:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊  明明正是高潮的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.73,0:05:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  那个拍得不怎么样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.88,0:05:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不看这个  这个「恶魔的轻声低语」可是杰作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.94,0:05:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是看到最后吧  不是让人很在意嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.60,0:05:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之后也不会有什么让人在意的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.69,0:05:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.83,0:05:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.49,0:05:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥  听我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.31,0:05:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在走廊的下面…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.75,0:05:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是个谜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.95,0:05:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这身装扮是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.99,0:05:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是特别啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.39,0:06:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她多大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.94,0:06:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12、3岁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.79,0:06:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.83,0:06:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.54,0:06:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有这方面的兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.39,0:06:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？  兴趣？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.24,0:06:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥  对于礼弥殿下来说你这话的细微差别可传达不了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.24,0:06:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么到底该怎么说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.08,0:06:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  你们就不能安静点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.35,0:06:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.56,0:06:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,江户川巡警很快就会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.55,0:06:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是迷路之类的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.89,0:06:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒还好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.18,0:06:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是被父母遗弃了的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.72,0:06:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少能告诉我名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.08,0:06:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里地址以及你读几年级了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.69,0:06:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.79,0:06:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是说是要带她去医院就突然间…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.15,0:07:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.25,0:07:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  不可怕的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.59,0:07:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事的啦  冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.19,0:07:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话要带她去医院看来是不可能了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.47,0:07:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  还是请医生来这里看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们和她的年纪比较接近
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.60,0:07:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会跟你们说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.72,0:07:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能不能试一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.38,0:07:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.14,0:07:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.88,0:07:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不想说？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.06,0:07:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么看不惯的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.37,0:07:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是头疼啊  这可没什么办法了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.90,0:07:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥  你在恶搞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.67,0:07:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  我想这样会不会就对我们敞开心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.79,0:08:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.60,0:08:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  一起看电影吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.47,0:08:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸电影非常有趣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.00,0:08:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥殿下  这还是免了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.47,0:08:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  我想一定会很中意的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.65,0:08:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会中意的人恐怕万里都没法挑一吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.59,0:08:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我明明很喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.41,0:08:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连我也不可能有这种想法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.45,0:08:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是被礼弥殿下的天然给治愈了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.96,0:08:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.10,0:08:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.33,0:08:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.66,0:08:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.88,0:08:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就暂时安置在我们这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.23,0:08:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥殿下也是  这下会变得热闹了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  有什么我能帮忙的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.42,0:08:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么能帮我把晚饭带给那个女孩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.68,0:09:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把晚饭带来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.31,0:09:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.64,0:09:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.41,0:09:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.24,0:09:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.64,0:09:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥殿下  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.99,0:09:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  降谷君  小萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.79,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我稍微脚滑了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.88,0:09:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.02,0:09:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.01,0:09:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.44,0:09:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.77,0:10:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.44,0:10:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.39,0:10:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥殿下  你的身体怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.26,0:10:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经完全没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.99,0:10:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个  发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.35,0:10:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥你用的紫阳花的叶子找不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.49,0:10:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得的确是放在这个保鲜盒里的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.55,0:10:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦  我会去后院自己摘的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是过分啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.96,0:10:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是动物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.33,0:10:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  还是当心点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.39,0:10:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会去后山摘叶子回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.59,0:10:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.95,0:10:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要添饭的话  要多少都尽管说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.33,0:10:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿…阿夜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.33,0:11:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿夜…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然都这样了  那就不用介意啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.58,0:11:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是个普通的女孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.60,0:11:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是多敲几下爷爷  她会不会就稍微敞开心扉一点呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.24,0:11:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  就算是开玩笑也别说这种啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.08,0:11:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不介意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.63,0:11:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.60,0:11:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  但是这会不会是礼弥你考虑太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.66,0:11:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.63,0:11:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟昨天才来的  应该不可能有什么怨恨的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.71,0:11:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.08,0:11:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是错觉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.80,0:11:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是那样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.33,0:11:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那孩子应该是对礼弥你没啥恶意的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.09,0:11:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是在害怕礼弥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.95,0:11:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕我？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.43,0:11:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是孩子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.29,0:11:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没法老实地说出害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.97,0:11:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会变成这么冷漠的态度
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.90,0:12:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.58,0:12:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.08,0:12:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥先去接近她试试如何
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.56,0:12:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样那孩子的态度肯定会有所变化的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.89,0:12:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.17,0:12:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以进来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.98,0:12:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.91,0:12:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体好点了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.09,0:12:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道情况  但能早点找到家人就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.95,0:12:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讨厌我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.52,0:12:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说我做了什么让你不开心的事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.71,0:12:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这样的话请告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.33,0:12:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对这种事相当迟钝的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.94,0:12:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉在你休息的时候打扰你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.09,0:12:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么过会儿见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.78,0:13:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.47,0:13:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.82,0:13:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.04,0:13:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个孩子啊  你怎么看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.80,0:13:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.26,0:13:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君是怎么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.24,0:13:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.02,0:13:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她挺可怜的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.35,0:13:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.13,0:13:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.46,0:13:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.73,0:13:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.63,0:13:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的只是有点怕我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.56,0:14:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.44,0:14:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.22,0:14:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然对降谷君做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.61,0:14:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破坏紫阳花和推我的人都是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.19,0:14:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讨厌我没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.43,0:14:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请不要对降谷君出手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.59,0:14:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是就此停手的话  我就不再追究这些事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.82,0:15:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.28,0:15:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.81,0:15:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.22,0:15:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那个昨晚睡得还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.85,0:15:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.37,0:15:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.69,0:15:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.63,0:15:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.02,0:15:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥  你能来一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.93,0:15:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.03,0:15:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不能亲口说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.50,0:15:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是通过摇头点头还是能够稍微交流一下的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.73,0:15:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再问一遍刚才的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.66,0:16:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是被人打的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.08,0:16:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被谁打的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.81,0:16:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥  也不是说我就相信了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.74,0:16:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那孩子确实就这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.33,0:16:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.87,0:16:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想不会没理由就这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.54,0:16:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道有什么原因吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.41,0:16:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.53,0:16:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.14,0:16:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.14,0:17:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.16,0:17:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想和降谷君接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.10,0:17:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.11,0:17:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥殿下  是不是看错了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.29,0:17:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.86,0:17:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥不要用那么吓人的表情  她都在发抖了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.54,0:17:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.95,0:17:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要擅自认定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.94,0:17:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.25,0:17:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚才打算亲我的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.81,0:17:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.26,0:17:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥说的都是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.79,0:17:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.70,0:17:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都不是普通的小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.27,0:17:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.79,0:17:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你  是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.00,0:17:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.61,0:17:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.72,0:17:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.34,0:17:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.14,0:18:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.14,0:18:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.53,0:18:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会觉得这小丫头好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.75,0:18:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.62,0:18:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真迟钝啊  还不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.42,0:18:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.95,0:18:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来打算把你的全部都夺走的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.22,0:18:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果你周围全是笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.61,0:18:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明老老实实按我说的做就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.95,0:18:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果大家全是礼弥  礼弥  礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.76,0:18:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个全都是只注意礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.51,0:18:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没有人肯看我一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.95,0:18:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  你是礼弥的老妈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.22,0:18:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这忽视人类只想着僵尸的臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.87,0:18:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该成熟点了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.87,0:18:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又说这种话了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.20,0:18:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没成长的是你才对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.59,0:18:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.79,0:18:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样尽做些讨人厌又阴险的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.70,0:18:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然会被人讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.06,0:18:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该有点自觉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.69,0:19:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才如此孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.06,0:19:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这么寂寞的话就抱你了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.61,0:19:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呸  谁会做啊  这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.37,0:19:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是身体变成僵尸  心灵变得纯洁了倒会考虑一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.94,0:19:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  难道打算开始超能力大战了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.02,0:19:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛  真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.56,0:19:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.95,0:20:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.27,0:20:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.91,0:20:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.14,0:20:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  今天也不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.66,0:20:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明…明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.57,0:20:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于对大小姐的惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.87,0:20:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为处分  做两周的义务劳动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.17,0:20:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时取消出席辩论大会的资格  这样如何
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.00,0:20:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于此次的处分  教师里面也有人不满
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.63,0:20:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐在学生里面也很有人气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.05,0:20:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.51,0:20:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想开了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.18,0:21:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得没有违背丈夫的意思还要处罚女儿的必要了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.48,0:21:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.69,0:21:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.10,0:21:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那个  因为看到母亲大人的车了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.42,0:21:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天被说了什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.12,0:21:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不  今天什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.48,0:21:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.87,0:21:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是我的训斥起作用了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.26,0:21:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  你说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.72,0:21:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  昨晚做了个梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.98,0:21:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个女孩子倒在寺里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.83,0:21:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子不知怎么回事居然是你老妈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.23,0:21:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后啊  因为和平常一样老是捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.47,0:21:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就「像你这种性格」地训…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.83,0:21:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.69,0:21:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.89,0:21:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.52,0:22:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不客气
