[Script Info]
Title:Sankarea 07
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00838383,&H00620062,&H00480048,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,1
Style: Staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H141F1F1F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: EDTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00141414,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPCN,方正中等线_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,8,134
Style: OPJP,DFGGothicP-W5,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,8,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFGHSMincho-W3,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,10,10,128
Style: Note1,方正稚艺_GBK,18,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,134
Style: Note2,方正中等线_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H002F2F2F,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: Movie1,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00C2BEBC,&HF0000000,&H001B1B1B,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Note3,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.78,0:00:59.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠れない夜に聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.10,0:01:03.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}絵空事だとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:20.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永遠を知るより快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.66,0:01:24.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.84,0:01:31.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ココロの深くに棲みついた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.03,0:01:35.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.34,0:01:40.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それでもあたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.62,0:01:44.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.19,0:01:50.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分に割れた太陽が朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.46,0:01:55.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}闇に慣れた神経をじわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:02:00.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}置き忘れた脳内はあえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.04,0:02:05.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シナリオの消えた物語だ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.60,0:02:10.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由に自由に舵を取って
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.98,0:02:17.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと高くへ舞い上がって
Comment: 0,0:00:21.80,0:00:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.78,0:00:59.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在无法入眠的夜晚  所听到的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.10,0:01:03.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}假若只是子虚乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:20.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}与其知晓永恒  不如追求快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.66,0:01:24.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}懊恼着如今
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.84,0:01:35.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}是为了逃避  在心灵深处隐藏的阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.34,0:01:44.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使如此  我还是能够深爱着自己
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.19,0:01:50.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分为两半的太阳为我带来晨光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.46,0:01:55.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}刺激着适应了黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:02:00.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遗忘了的记忆尽管就让它遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.04,0:02:05.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如同失去了剧本的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.60,0:02:10.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由地  自由地  把握住方向
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.98,0:02:17.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}向着更高的地方飞舞
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.54,0:22:29.09,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.98,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君の手の中　揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:47.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:55.60,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君ともしはぐれたとしても　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.11,0:23:06.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.55,0:23:24.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明日も
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.54,0:22:29.09,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只有一个愿望  能够实现的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.98,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}希望能变成  在你手中摇曳着的小小花朵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:47.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}第一次看到  这个耀眼的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:55.60,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果和你走散了　也一定能
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.11,0:23:06.20,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.55,0:23:24.20,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}醒来睁开眼  就在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明天也是
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.75,0:02:35.93,OPTitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\be3}{\pos(502,294)}「青梅…竹马…」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.36,0:24:09.71,EDTitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be7}{\pos(330,250)}「虚伪的…自由…」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  千纮那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.71,0:00:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要拜托我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.15,0:00:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.75,0:00:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.32,0:00:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  丢下你不管咯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.30,0:00:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.56,0:02:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.55,0:02:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好像很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.38,0:02:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.65,0:02:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.14,0:02:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫左王子兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.21,0:02:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私立散华女子学园二年生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.38,0:02:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲是这里京怀石左王子的女老板
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.55,0:02:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲是主厨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.16,0:02:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说我生来就是旅店的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.85,0:02:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在年幼的时候就经常帮忙打点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.70,0:02:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时人手不够  就会像这样让我来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.89,0:02:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.40,0:03:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  手脚麻利点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了  别突然来搭话啊  会切到手指的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.76,0:03:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且为什么我非要来帮你们店里干活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.32,0:03:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的周日啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.37,0:03:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说得这么无情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.02,0:03:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们交情都那么久了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.83,0:03:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你又停下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.45,0:03:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你让我停下来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.94,0:03:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是因为你干得那么慢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.44,0:03:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  这样看着  真像是对般配的年轻夫妇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.87,0:03:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.29,0:03:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的哦  千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.29,0:03:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是你们结婚了  也不会强迫你来继承这家店的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.38,0:03:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用介意  只要有机会的话就尽情地推倒她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.61,0:03:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  老公
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.43,0:03:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.50,0:03:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.20,0:03:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.95,0:03:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.89,0:04:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  你们还真是亲热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.18,0:04:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没必要那么急着放开手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.96,0:04:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.35,0:04:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.42,0:04:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次与千纮邂逅是在我还在上幼儿园的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.69,0:04:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋爱肥皂剧里也很常见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.55,0:04:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邂逅糟糕透了  一开始就是最讨厌的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.18,0:04:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后通过一步一步的了解逐渐喜欢上之类的桥段
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.49,0:04:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和千纮的邂逅却是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.56,0:04:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不害怕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.54,0:05:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.51,0:05:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是王子殿下降临了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.11,0:05:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这王子殿下的真实身份
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.23,0:05:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天  呶恩叔叔告诉了我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.38,0:05:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子  这孩子是我们家的千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.31,0:05:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然比你小一岁  但你们要好好相处哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.18,0:05:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.34,0:05:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.11,0:05:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.29,0:05:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想着一定要和他搞好关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.76,0:05:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看电影吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.13,0:05:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  很有趣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.64,0:05:57.62,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  爱德莉阿娜？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.41,0:06:00.62,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么噩梦了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.62,0:06:02.70,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德莉阿娜？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.99,0:06:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.91,0:06:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.00,0:06:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.11,0:06:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到外面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.91,0:06:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.15,0:06:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到外面去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.66,0:06:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.52,0:06:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到外面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.15,0:06:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君平时玩些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.93,0:06:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看僵尸电影
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.59,0:07:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了僵尸电影之外呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.58,0:07:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看僵尸的书
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.93,0:07:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了僵尸以外呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.11,0:07:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.99,0:07:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.05,0:07:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.97,0:07:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君  用这个玩过家家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.11,0:07:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.91,0:07:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说在樱花树下有埋藏着尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.61,0:07:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能埋着僵尸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.81,0:07:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不要挖啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.86,0:07:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事  好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.03,0:07:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  这不是寺里的千纮吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.72,0:07:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.37,0:07:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  在和女生玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.97,0:07:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太没用了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.44,0:07:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们不跟你玩  就去和女生玩了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.01,0:07:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.40,0:08:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.12,0:08:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和女生玩哪里不对了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.13,0:08:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.86,0:08:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.72,0:08:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.73,0:08:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙真是爱哭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.08,0:08:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是以为哭了就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.79,0:08:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看中的王子殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.02,0:08:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实只是个喜欢僵尸的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.79,0:08:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万事嫌麻烦  没有协调性
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.47,0:08:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窝囊的爱哭鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.04,0:08:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕墓地是因为在僵尸电影里已经看惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.34,0:08:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有因为是自己家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.91,0:08:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是这样  回去的时候我的这份爱恋也完全降温了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.96,0:08:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没能做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.92,0:08:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里的话  每次来这里都玩得那么疯  真是抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:09:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果方便的话  即使不是盂兰节也请经常来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.84,0:09:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太感谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.72,0:09:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  柚菜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.00,0:09:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她啊  萌路发烧了  陪她去医院了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.41,0:09:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.11,0:09:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不用特意给我们送行了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.63,0:09:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用啦  不是很严重啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.67,0:09:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么哥哥  下次见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.16,0:09:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.60,0:09:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子  不跟千纮君说拜拜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.88,0:09:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.68,0:09:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  我被叫来给厨房帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.71,0:09:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连送货都要做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.37,0:09:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是因为你在厨房起不到什么作用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.35,0:09:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.77,0:09:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜刀什么的  基本上没怎么用过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.80,0:09:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  这倒是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.06,0:09:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  为什么丸子你也跟来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.60,0:09:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是千纮的话  都没法好好跟客人打招呼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.93,0:10:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是和我们店里的信用挂钩的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没这么不懂常识啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.84,0:10:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得到的啦  打招呼什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.57,0:10:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.28,0:10:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那么多废话  好好干啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.61,0:10:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子  今天也谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.93,0:10:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  没什么大不了的啦  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮的话  随便你怎么使唤都可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.15,0:10:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一直都在受你的照顾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.77,0:10:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.20,0:10:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有拒绝的权利吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.11,0:10:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.53,0:10:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.03,0:10:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有几家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.88,0:10:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.28,0:10:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  这么不想来帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.58,0:10:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是这样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.18,0:10:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  礼弥的事也很在意啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.99,0:10:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  礼弥同学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.32,0:10:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  所以都说了不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.64,0:10:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有好多不知道的事啦  不太稳定什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.85,0:10:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.59,0:10:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.21,0:11:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很让人在意呢  礼弥同学很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.35,0:11:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这不是完全没有了解吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.84,0:11:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这难道是在约会吗  是约会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.60,0:11:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  约…约会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.64,0:11:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你傻吗  这种事怎么可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.07,0:11:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  你不用这么直接的否定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.71,0:11:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这本来就不是约会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.55,0:11:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  被他这么说一下  你就那么不愿意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.25,0:11:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么不愿意啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.85,0:11:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.19,0:11:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难道说是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.08,0:11:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情侣之间经常发生的让人向往的打情骂俏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.40,0:11:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.47,0:11:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  礼弥同学也好  兰子同学也好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.57,0:11:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你总是那么受欢迎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.11,0:11:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你还口口声声说只对僵尸感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.10,0:11:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游刃吗  有余吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.40,0:11:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我当白痴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.43,0:11:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吧  混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.29,0:11:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康孝君  冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.50,0:12:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫我如何冷静啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.81,0:12:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难沟通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.62,0:12:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子同学  这小子哪点好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.81,0:12:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子既不是大帅哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.44,0:12:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是个僵尸宅  性格扭曲  懒惰怕事  顽固的无能家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.67,0:12:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.54,0:12:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不否定的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.52,0:12:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来你也是美少女宅的变态吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.47,0:12:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有错  而且我还以此为荣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.60,0:12:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果你也不受欢迎的话我就没意见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.23,0:12:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说了我没受欢迎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.27,0:12:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在说啊  这是晒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.75,0:12:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位都冷静一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.62,0:12:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很冷静的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.61,0:12:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}僵尸  啃咬直至尸骨无形  一起腐烂的时候来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.53,0:12:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和千纮的重逢是初次相遇的二年后
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.70,0:12:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我六岁时  在我父亲强烈的意愿下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.88,0:12:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把千叶的店搬到了这里  紫阳町
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.46,0:12:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我家就和千纮家的寺庙变成邻居了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.45,0:12:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后不久就在母亲的邀请下  千纮来我家玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.37,0:12:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说这份爱恋在两年前就熄灭了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.50,0:13:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是作为表姐弟  我决定要好好陪他玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.97,0:13:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.49,0:13:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩吧  游戏什么的玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.24,0:13:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.20,0:13:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么去外面玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.53,0:13:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.64,0:13:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.80,0:13:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我带零食来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.20,0:13:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君  难得成为邻居了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.33,0:13:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和兰子做好朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.46,0:13:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}真是的  太爱害羞了啦  真可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.71,0:13:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从以前开始  不知为什么妈妈就很喜欢千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.41,0:13:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要让我和千纮成为好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.84,0:13:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也让我的兴致骤降了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.27,0:13:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  真的太可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.30,0:13:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.32,0:13:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.10,0:13:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.59,0:13:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在楼上看书
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.84,0:13:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不和他一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.66,0:14:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君说他不想玩  游戏也不玩外面也不去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.84,0:14:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就去附近的影像出租店吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.46,0:14:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  之前不是说有想看的动画吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.18,0:14:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把那个借来一起看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.26,0:14:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  兰子难道是会把难得来的表弟丢在一边的孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.40,0:14:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.28,0:14:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.51,0:14:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.23,0:14:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.09,0:14:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐  千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.02,0:14:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.14,0:14:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来借动画吧  有很好看的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.08,0:14:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个才好看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.93,0:14:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}僵尸学园  惨剧之学园祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.37,0:15:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸学园  惨剧之学园祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.33,0:15:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  不愧是千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个的话是最新作  从美国买来的就在里面  要看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.06,0:15:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.74,0:15:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  千纮君真厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.03,0:15:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明才五岁  恐怖电影倒是已经可以看原声的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.48,0:15:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.73,0:15:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点过激  要跟你爸爸妈妈保密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.12,0:15:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.79,0:15:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  过激是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.04,0:15:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僵尸的「爆浆」很厉害的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.99,0:15:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「爆浆」是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.20,0:15:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会是怎样的感觉呢  「爆浆」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.27,0:15:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么擅自决定要看的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.25,0:15:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  这个肯定很好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.40,0:15:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个系列铁定好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.37,0:16:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不喜欢恐怖电影
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.05,0:16:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看了就会喜欢上的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.22,0:16:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这是英语的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.70,0:16:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算听不懂也很好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.85,0:16:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不好看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.18,0:16:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要看动画
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.61,0:16:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  绝对要比动画好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.95,0:16:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比起恐怖电影更想看动画
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.28,0:16:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西我要拿去还掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.92,0:16:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.42,0:16:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.70,0:16:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哇  走开啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.81,0:17:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.92,0:17:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮君  谢谢你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.27,0:17:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在回想起来  果然从墓地相遇那刻开始
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.30,0:17:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已经一见钟情了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.39,0:17:33.68,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,282)}{\1c&HD2D2D2&}你会保护我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.68,0:17:34.85,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,282)}{\1c&HD2D2D2&}当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.98,0:17:37.73,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,282)}{\1c&HD2D2D2&}这个事件结束之后我们就在一起吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.27,0:17:39.02,Movie1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,282)}{\1c&HD2D2D2&}嗯  好的  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.21,0:17:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我啊  在十岁的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.09,0:17:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就毫无疑问地喜欢上了千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.27,0:17:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊  千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.42,0:17:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮啊  你觉得怎么样的初吻比较好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.86,0:17:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？  怎么样的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.71,0:17:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  不是有很多种的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.38,0:18:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以夕阳下的大海为背景
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.75,0:18:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即将踏上旅途的情侣的分别之时  什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.60,0:18:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.56,0:18:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是想和这样的僵尸妹亲亲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.81,0:18:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又…又是僵尸妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.10,0:18:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真以为会有这样的女孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.52,0:18:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.45,0:18:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再好好想一想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.08,0:18:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻可是很重要的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.68,0:18:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.55,0:18:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.56,0:18:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷  总有一天你会遭天谴的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.46,0:18:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者给我介绍女孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.52,0:18:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  真烦人的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.13,0:18:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  去剩下的两家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.86,0:18:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.04,0:18:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来牵手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.14,0:19:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.66,0:19:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啦  快牵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.34,0:19:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛痛  知道了  知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.20,0:19:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.68,0:19:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.08,0:19:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.34,0:19:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.39,0:19:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得我们第一次牵手是在什么时候吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.21,0:19:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那个是第一次见面的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.14,0:19:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你在墓地里哭着  我没办法就拉着你的手出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.64,0:19:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.07,0:19:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确的是什么时候的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.12,0:19:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了  都这么久了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.69,0:19:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.05,0:19:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不懂你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.11,0:19:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送货结束
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.08,0:19:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会送到这种宅邸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.23,0:20:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这里的老奶奶在前年法事的时候吃过我家便当后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.50,0:20:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就迷上我们家的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.10,0:20:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时常会定些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.17,0:20:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮到此就下班了  可以回去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.07,0:20:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.51,0:20:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多高峰时段也过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.62,0:20:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不回去继续帮忙  我们自己也能解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.38,0:20:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  真幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.84,0:20:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.83,0:20:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  哇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.86,0:20:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.93,0:21:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别顺着气氛就被吻了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.29,0:21:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多考虑考虑清楚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.86,0:21:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻可是很重要的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.22,0:21:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  不想输
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.54,0:21:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对！  绝对！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.29,0:21:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会输的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.11,0:23:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗  让我来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.12,0:23:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小萌路事先说好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.39,0:23:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就没什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.11,0:23:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回  散华礼弥  第八话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.22,0:23:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「虚伪的…自由…」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.86,0:23:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？  
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.51,0:24:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小萌路？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.38,0:24:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作人  制作人在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.34,0:24:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小萌路  这个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.73,0:24:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作人  请解释一下这是怎么回事吧
