[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:Kokoro Connect #5 chs
Original Script:A.I.R.nesSub(翻：伊藤誠/校+轴：cunhan/繁：小翊)
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,仓耳今楷04 W04,52,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,60,60,20,1
Style: Note,仓耳今楷04 W04,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,60,60,15,1
Style: Title_Hito_Random,KaiTi,46,&H009E70CE,&HF0000000,&H14FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,5,0,1,0,0,3,90,90,100,1
Style: Title_Kizu_Random,KaiTi,46,&H0040CA98,&HF0000000,&H14FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,5,0,1,0,0,3,90,90,100,1
Style: Staff,仓耳今楷04 W04,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H00001319,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: OP1,仓耳今楷04 W04,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00B134DB,&H0AB857DA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,60,60,20,134
Style: ED1,仓耳今楷04 W04,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0017325F,&H6417325F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,60,60,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能你会纳闷我怎么又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.04,0:00:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是要重新说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.46,0:00:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.40,0:00:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐山唯 我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.92,0:00:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话请和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.95,0:00:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.71,0:00:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前不是拒绝了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.72,0:00:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我的心意也没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.51,0:00:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯的心境也差不多…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.94,0:00:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.44,0:00:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.23,0:00:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.82,0:00:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前就在想了 为什么是我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.25,0:00:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明伊织比起我更可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.97,0:00:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稻叶也是个美女
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯也有很多优点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.52,0:00:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最大的原因是感觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.46,0:00:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到的瞬间我就知道自己会喜欢上唯的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.91,0:00:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际也喜欢上了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.91,0:00:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直喜欢着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.39,0:02:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么选现在来说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.28,0:02:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯对太一怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.06,0:02:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.30,0:02:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是喜欢太一的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.48,0:02:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.46,0:02:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那么再问下 我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.43,0:02:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为朋友很讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.82,0:02:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.58,0:02:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是骗人了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.23,0:02:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说的话还是喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.16,0:02:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是作为朋友 作为朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.23,0:03:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我只能说到这个地步
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.23,0:03:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 不是因为你不好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.48,0:03:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我现在做不到跟谁交往
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.50,0:03:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之明白有戏我就安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.56,0:03:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以了吧 回教室吃午饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.13,0:03:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一起吃的意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.42,0:03:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是 朋友在等着我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.26,0:03:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.63,0:03:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说在前头 男性朋友好感度排名里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.28,0:03:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}你落后太一很多哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.11,0:03:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么知道会有这种事的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.64,0:03:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}什么 果然超不过太一吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.33,0:03:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天和唯互换的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.48,0:03:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然看到了青木的短信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.15,0:03:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是故意的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.91,0:03:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想给你们来点刺激多少有些好处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.20,0:03:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.33,0:03:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 剩下随便你们了 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.36,0:03:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.34,0:03:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.22,0:01:18.77,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}青空見上げた 今日もまた会えるね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.27,0:01:24.49,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}風をきって すべりこんだ電車
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.21,0:01:30.81,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}シャボン色のにおい 陽だまりの歩道に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.24,0:01:36.55,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}ココロを早めてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.42,0:01:42.80,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}放学後廊下に響くシグナル
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:46.34,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6\fs18\pos(700,715)}セカイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:46.34,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}ありふれた部室が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.46,0:01:50.85,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}キラめいてゆくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.02,0:01:57.35,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}走り出した君へのキモチは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.01,0:02:03.45,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}胸の奥をきゅんと締めつける
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.08,0:02:09.15,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}止められないドキドキ溢れる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.05,0:02:15.33,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}君のこと ねぇもっと教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.26,0:02:21.21,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}届きそう？届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.38,0:02:25.44,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}そっと君にコネクト
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.22,0:01:18.77,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}仰望头上的青空 今天又能见面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.27,0:01:24.49,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}踏上破风入站的电车
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.21,0:01:30.81,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}嗅着肥皂泡色的味道 走在暖阳下的人行道上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.24,0:01:36.55,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}心中的期待不由地加快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.42,0:01:42.80,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}放学后回响走廊的铃声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:46.34,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}那个熟悉的活动室
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:46.34,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6\fs18\pos(714,624)}世　　界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.46,0:01:50.85,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}正闪亮着迎接我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.02,0:01:57.35,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}心中爆发的那份对你的向往
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.01,0:02:03.45,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}实在地收在胸口里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.08,0:02:09.15,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}却止不住不断外溢的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.05,0:02:15.33,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}再告诉我 更多你的事情 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.26,0:02:21.21,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}你感受得到吗？多想你感受得到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.38,0:02:25.44,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6}暗暗地牵上你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.38,0:02:25.44,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur6\fs18\pos(683,624)}c  o  n  n  e  c  t
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.48,0:04:04.47,Title_Hito_Random,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告白、随之而来的死……
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.18,0:04:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有太一吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 难道是稻叶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.42,0:04:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我跟伊织互换了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.92,0:04:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 午休时青木和唯的情况如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.58,0:04:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊 感觉像是个不同的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.98,0:04:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是稻叶 为什么要让我看到那场景啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.68,0:04:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…你不会真的不明白…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.20,0:04:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 那直截了当地问你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.02,0:04:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一对伊织究竟是怎么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.09,0:04:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这么直接啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.96,0:04:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且用永濑的样子问就更有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.82,0:04:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反过来算是好机会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.97,0:04:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.73,0:05:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢 我觉得现在的关系很好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.40,0:05:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点不想去破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.62,0:05:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.65,0:05:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 还只有你们两个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.24,0:05:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稻叶太快了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.01,0:05:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.87,0:05:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上当了都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.71,0:05:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.02,0:05:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一 你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.64,0:05:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.97,0:05:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑装成跟稻叶互换了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.40,0:05:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装成我是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.91,0:05:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不明…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.26,0:05:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生什么 不管变成什么样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.27,0:05:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都知道永濑就是永濑的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.22,0:05:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你想到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.64,0:05:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道自己是最差劲的了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.69,0:05:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她明明想相信我的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.93,0:05:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我揍你一下么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.69,0:06:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 揍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.80,0:06:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快追上去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.56,0:06:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次不是我可以搞定的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.63,0:06:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤岛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.37,0:06:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八重樫君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.80,0:06:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到永濑了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.47,0:06:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然男女成对才是世间常理吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.62,0:06:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.89,0:06:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没空跟你聊这些
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.57,0:06:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要先找到永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.12,0:06:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开藤…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.03,0:06:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑同学从正门跑出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.32,0:06:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我是不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.93,0:06:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概永濑同学需要的人是你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.67,0:06:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤岛 真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.67,0:06:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是现在的永濑同学需要的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.05,0:06:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理所当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.91,0:06:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.47,0:06:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.97,0:07:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.45,0:07:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.96,0:07:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.84,0:07:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没注意到真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.18,0:07:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明约好了的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.46,0:07:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对一个人来说 自我是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.07,0:07:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要外表一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.23,0:07:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内在变了后谁都注意不到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.26,0:07:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这不是在责备太一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.54,0:07:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才完全是我的不对
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.19,0:07:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.29,0:07:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那也是永濑以自己的方式前进的结果吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.61,0:07:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.92,0:07:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.39,0:07:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.07,0:08:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么说呢 我非常憧憬永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.45,0:08:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憧憬？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.17,0:08:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能像永濑那样用各种表情欢笑生气悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.08,0:08:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以很憧憬像那样很开心地渡过人生的永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.57,0:08:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是因为我演绎着各种各样的角色而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.64,0:08:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前也这么说了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.86,0:08:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到底真的是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.72,0:08:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思 你想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.44,0:08:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你误解什么了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.89,0:08:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑 装傻 娇羞 糟糕捏他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.54,0:08:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着性子什么都会做 其实很有心计
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.17,0:08:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不去想 但有时也会想得太多
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在说严肃话题之前大概因为难为情故意装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.98,0:08:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔会露出冷淡的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.98,0:08:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.73,0:09:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个都是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.44,0:09:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.21,0:09:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些全都是永濑伊织吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.04,0:09:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种人不存在吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.59,0:09:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种拥有好几张脸的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.14,0:09:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实很普通吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.96,0:09:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人有很多张脸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.07,0:09:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是少的那种
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.69,0:09:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑是多的那种
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.46,0:09:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不就是这么回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.49,0:09:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是看人才…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.99,0:09:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事 谁都会看气氛说话的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.11,0:09:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我自认为必须要摆出这样的角色…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.23,0:09:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不顾周围我行我素
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.30,0:09:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能和别人好好相处的人是不存在的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.16,0:09:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我就算是喜欢的东西也会因为气氛…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.31,0:09:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社团都不能自己决定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.21,0:09:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为喜欢的东西太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.67,0:09:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而社团 跟那些选择轻松社团的家伙没多大差别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽是歪理啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中途开始完全是了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.31,0:10:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才憧憬着太一你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.24,0:10:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论什么时候都能保持着自我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.06,0:10:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我是如何的我 太一都不会改变的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.99,0:10:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我憧憬着那样能带来安心感的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.12,0:10:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.23,0:10:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.47,0:10:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢永濑伊织 跟我交往吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.09,0:10:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.69,0:10:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.77,0:10:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你应该知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.24,0:10:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.00,0:10:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒地铃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.93,0:10:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.34,0:11:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事先跟你道个歉 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.47,0:11:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是你们的错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.75,0:11:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们实在是太有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.99,0:11:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.97,0:11:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我事先道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.55,0:11:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.75,0:11:41.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HA240A9&\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(448,684)\fad(300,0)\b0}你　我　难　辨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.15,0:11:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.49,0:11:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老后怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.80,0:11:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就到 好像也联络上伊织的妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.62,0:12:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.07,0:12:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 到底想做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.46,0:12:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快 永濑伊织的身体就会死去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.06,0:12:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.85,0:12:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说你能左右人的生命吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.95,0:12:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事怎么可能做得到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.95,0:12:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过事实就是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.62,0:12:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好确认这点事我也能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.70,0:12:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种话谁会相信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.89,0:12:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果信不信还是看各位的判断
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.94,0:12:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.31,0:12:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请好好听着哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.84,0:12:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和永濑的身体一起死去的人格
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.01,0:12:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位能决定一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.11,0:13:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.51,0:13:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始的30分钟里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.65,0:13:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位只要说出愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.13,0:13:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能如愿让你们交换人格
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.57,0:13:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.14,0:13:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.19,0:13:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把人当猴耍也要适可而止
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.36,0:13:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.31,0:13:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗 现在开始30分钟以内
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.78,0:13:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的话是让我们选要杀了谁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.76,0:13:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可伊织怎么会就这样死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.60,0:13:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生也会努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.44,0:13:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙说不定是胡说八道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.96,0:13:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也可能是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.54,0:13:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论如何我们只能面对了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.51,0:13:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算怒到极点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.52,0:14:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果 如果要牺牲谁的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.45,0:14:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就让我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.05,0:14:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.67,0:14:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么我来牺牲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.18,0:14:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有想过因你的牺牲活下来的人的心情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.53,0:14:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去像是在为别人考虑一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.63,0:14:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实就只在考虑自己而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.20,0:14:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不折不扣的自我中心混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.83,0:14:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.14,0:14:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我讨厌看到有人在我眼前受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.54,0:14:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到别人的伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.04,0:14:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会越来越膨胀 变成难以忍受的伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.46,0:14:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.04,0:14:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还不如自己去背负
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.48,0:14:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少还能知道有多少伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.42,0:14:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话还能承受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.37,0:14:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 所以我不是为了别人在做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.99,0:14:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了我自己才做自我牺牲笨蛋的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.12,0:14:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 你果然很怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.56,0:15:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很怪 但是怪的善良
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.06,0:15:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,善良又笨拙 真是个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.76,0:15:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样的话也应该能明白我们的痛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.48,0:15:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得跟伊织的身体一起死去的就只有伊织了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.62,0:15:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想说这种话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.51,0:15:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我想这话是必须说出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.09,0:15:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之也要让伊织知道事态
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.98,0:15:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.78,0:15:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那既然是我说的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.53,0:15:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来互换吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.57,0:15:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我青木义文和永濑伊织互换吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.41,0:15:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么大家都在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.06,0:16:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才应该还在河边跟太一说话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.73,0:16:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 冷静点听我说 你…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.21,0:16:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就只能让我死掉了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.21,0:16:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑 这事还没决定下来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.65,0:16:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.46,0:16:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了谁的人格抢了那具身体活下去的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.48,0:16:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说太沉重了背负不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.97,0:16:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.25,0:16:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像现在正赶过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.83,0:16:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.83,0:16:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 最后能让我单独和大家说说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.92,0:17:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一 伊织叫你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.18,0:17:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.94,0:17:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 永濑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.85,0:17:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 好像就太一跟往常一样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.42,0:17:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无表情的人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.14,0:17:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之太一谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.50,0:17:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一跟我说了那番话后 我的烦恼就轻了许多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.34,0:17:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉从很多方面来看 我很可能会喜欢上你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.82,0:18:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一说过喜欢我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.93,0:18:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就给你回复
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.90,0:18:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过在那之前 有没有期待我先说个笑话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.53,0:18:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有期待 不过预料到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.60,0:18:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么太一能若无其事的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.59,0:18:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都非常伤心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.28,0:18:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤心啊 伤心到要命
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.73,0:18:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但永濑更伤心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.55,0:18:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是哭了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.96,0:18:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永濑就哭不了了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.39,0:18:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.54,0:18:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想继续活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.81,0:18:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明才开始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.05,0:18:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 为什么我要遇到这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.98,0:18:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪里不对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.08,0:19:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明太一说喜欢我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.75,0:19:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也喜欢太一
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.13,0:19:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请别和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.19,0:19:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就要死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.34,0:19:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我交往的话太一会很困扰的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.98,0:19:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…还这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.13,0:19:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 给我个回忆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.98,0:19:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吻我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.82,0:19:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稻叶她也会原谅我们的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.43,0:19:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我问你们 是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.97,0:20:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我 永濑伊织和永濑伊织的身体一起死去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.73,0:20:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 这该是妥当的结论吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.79,0:20:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后能问个问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.31,0:20:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事情我绝对不会原谅你的 所以要确认
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.74,0:20:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再对其他人做这种事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.94,0:20:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.27,0:20:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.35,0:20:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.09,0:20:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 别给我结束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.72,0:20:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,运气真的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.48,0:20:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.39,0:20:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该也不用担心有后遗症
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.46,0:20:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她再休息一阵子就能见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.61,0:20:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 各位辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.35,0:20:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个请收下 略表歉意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.77,0:21:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 也算是永濑同学的探望礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.36,0:21:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被算计了 虽然也觉得有这可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.35,0:21:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那伊织没事了啊 还活着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.33,0:21:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.00,0:21:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 到哪里你都算到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.00,0:21:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说的话 一切都在意料之内
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.81,0:21:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.86,0:21:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边能做的事情 大概比各位想象中的要多
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.70,0:21:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始就没打算把永濑怎么样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.33,0:21:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能给善良的普通市民添那种麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.43,0:21:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手机也没有弄湿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.26,0:21:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没打算让你们原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.22,0:21:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 最好也不要恨我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.96,0:22:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上各位也遇到一点好事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.95,0:22:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.76,0:22:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你出院
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.57,0:22:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 真抱歉啊 让你们担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.62,0:22:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意这种事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.83,0:22:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你们那没发生什么怪事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.29,0:22:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.63,0:22:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后人格互换也没再发生过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.39,0:22:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之似乎这样就结束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.15,0:22:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.14,0:22:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之来吃吧 来吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.16,0:22:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青木 去泡茶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.92,0:22:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.37,0:22:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织你先坐着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.29,0:22:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 感觉很不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.76,0:23:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 太一跟稻叶也快动手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.03,0:23:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 探病的时候听伊织说了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.94,0:23:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像夺走了我的初吻嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.04,0:23:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么赎罪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.84,0:23:30.97,Title_Kizu_Random,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1185,655)}注意到的时候 又开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.31,0:23:57.75,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}漂って消えた日常は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.86,0:24:03.38,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}まるで現実感のない夢のようで
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.29,0:24:11.64,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}わからないことがわからない子供のような僕を
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.69,0:24:16.03,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}溺れそうな声で呼んでいる
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.73,0:24:19.77,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}{\fs24}(Why did you call me Crying Crying Crying?）
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.89,0:24:25.37,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}臆病なのは同じはずなのに
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.25,0:24:25.37,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}{\fs24}(He can't understand, has not need it.)
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.43,0:24:30.81,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}受け止めたいと こんなにも願うのは
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.91,0:24:36.32,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}ココロノカラを透き通る叫びを
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.43,0:24:41.93,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}突き刺す破片を 滲む本音を
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.95,0:24:47.00,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}照らし出したひとつひとつ 大切な自分だと
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.95,0:24:47.00,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\fs24\pos(852,670)}<あなた>
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.05,0:24:56.73,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}知ってほしいから 知っていたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.19,0:24:56.73,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2}{\fs24}(What a beatiful colors.)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.31,0:23:57.75,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}萦绕在身边逐渐消失的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.86,0:24:03.38,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}宛如一个没有真实感的梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.29,0:24:11.64,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}难题苦恼就像一个个难以沟通的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.69,0:24:16.03,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}溺水般地向我呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.89,0:24:25.37,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}我们明明 都是一样的胆怯
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.43,0:24:30.81,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}我们是如此渴望地得到接纳
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.91,0:24:36.32,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}穿透内心的保护壳传出来的呐喊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.43,0:24:41.93,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}是刺破出来的碎片 是渗透出来的真心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.95,0:24:47.00,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}映照出一个个 不可分离的自我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.05,0:24:56.73,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur2\an8}你是否知道 你应该知道
