[Script Info]
;  This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
;  For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;  go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;  or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;  
;  Note: This file was saved by SubResync.
;  
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2007-03-24 10:13:31
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,文鼎粗圆简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H77676767,&H201B2765,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,0,2,12,12,7,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.33,0:00:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生化身体修复率100％
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.27,0:00:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑波恢复到普通活动时的70％
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.67,0:00:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调整槽 开始排水
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.75,0:00:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.62,0:00:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.96,0:00:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.70,0:00:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.90,0:00:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没有获胜机会了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.77,0:00:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是没有 还有一个办法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.77,0:00:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.97,0:00:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.24,0:00:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了 这样对沙由香太苛求了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.51,0:00:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她变回普通的女生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.13,0:01:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安鲁克！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.07,0:01:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FM27 可恶 你到底想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.74,0:01:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在等你呢 等很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.08,0:01:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙…把心跳钻石…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.55,0:01:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个老头子太啰嗦了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.82,0:01:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.62,0:01:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？这是理所应当的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.62,0:01:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳钻石本来就是为了我而存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.63,0:01:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我使用它又没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.36,0:01:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 代官蜜丝特蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.83,0:01:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.90,0:01:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.24,0:01:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想打吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.24,0:01:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 但是你赢不了我的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.58,0:01:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…少胡说八道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.25,0:02:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片名：超昂天使3
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.43,0:03:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.76,0:03:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.63,0:03:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的 心跳钻石还存在一个BETA版的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.57,0:04:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BETA版？测试版吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.04,0:04:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是测试版
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.77,0:04:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是跟之前的MASTER版比起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.64,0:04:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,功能上并不逊色
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性能还远远超越MASTER版
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.05,0:04:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.85,0:04:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是BETA版有个致命性问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.12,0:04:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.59,0:04:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BETA版只能填充一次能源
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.53,0:04:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确来说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.00,0:04:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BETA版产生的能源远远高过MASTER版
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.93,0:04:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也由于能源过高
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.47,0:04:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的生化身体的技术
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.60,0:04:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承受不了二次之后的填充能源
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.41,0:04:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最糟糕的状况是溶解掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.21,0:04:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.68,0:04:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没完吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.41,0:04:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BETA版是运作不稳定的单元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.35,0:04:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,填充能源失败的话会失去控制
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.42,0:04:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而把生化身体…不
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.55,0:04:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还可能把沙由香也吞没消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.29,0:04:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.16,0:05:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么危险的东西确实不能用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.70,0:05:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.57,0:05:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.90,0:05:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.37,0:05:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样起来没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.64,0:05:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你…担心我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.11,0:05:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.98,0:05:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圆 请马上为我装上BETA版吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.12,0:05:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到刚才我们的谈话了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.65,0:05:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.79,0:05:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的 我们是使用心跳钻石的老手了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.47,0:05:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.03,0:06:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 玩起来没有想像的舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.90,0:06:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是使用过度 松弛了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.51,0:06:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那里不够看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.91,0:06:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我要你用嘴巴让我舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.92,0:06:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快呀 还不赶快开始
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.00,0:06:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.20,0:06:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.93,0:06:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再用力吸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.80,0:06:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.94,0:06:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 让我的女人部分也舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.69,0:07:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.49,0:07:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的好 就是这样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.31,0:07:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.91,0:07:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再用力 再用力 再更用力 更激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.55,0:08:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是BETA版
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.48,0:08:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香 真的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.62,0:08:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次要怎样填充呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.76,0:08:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 你喜欢什么方式
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.89,0:08:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有没有搞清楚！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.90,0:08:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.96,0:08:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香 你不在乎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.90,0:08:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是失败的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.30,0:08:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.37,0:08:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是跟你一定会很顺利的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.31,0:08:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.12,0:08:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不干！我会怕！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.52,0:08:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怕极了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.13,0:08:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.74,0:09:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也怕 我当然怕了 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.07,0:09:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前打斗没有一次不怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.55,0:09:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是把这个除去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.88,0:09:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圆你会帮助我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.69,0:09:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.23,0:09:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良子？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.77,0:09:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么请看我自慰把心跳的感觉找出来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.65,0:09:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在看吗 沙由香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.80,0:10:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.47,0:10:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…发生了什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.81,0:10:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…有点累了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.95,0:10:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么讲 我晓得自己有多无能了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.02,0:10:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来只是想代替他努力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.09,0:10:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是努力的想达成他的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.10,0:10:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想到有个人会接受我的笑容…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.63,0:10:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.64,0:10:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这样努力过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.90,0:10:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照理来说应该也可以这样下去的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.44,0:10:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我太难受了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.25,0:10:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丧失在他面前露出笑容的自信了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.92,0:10:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.19,0:11:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你的话一定没有问题 我们一起努力吧 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.86,0:11:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.40,0:11:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.27,0:11:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那种事 没那种事的 良子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.47,0:11:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良子你并不无能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.34,0:11:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.07,0:11:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道怎么说才好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.54,0:11:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之这样的你 不像你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.68,0:11:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识的良子是漂亮又温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.15,0:11:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着美丽笑容的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.01,0:11:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且很有魅力 而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.02,0:11:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体很香
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.75,0:11:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.29,0:11:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之良子你…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.97,0:11:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你为我打气
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.30,0:11:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 恭平
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.04,0:11:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然刚刚我很担心 托你的福 没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.64,0:11:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.25,0:12:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我先告辞了 我得赶快回去她身边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.05,0:12:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.93,0:12:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香小姐 你有在看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.33,0:12:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经…这么有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.54,0:12:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法再维持冷静了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.01,0:12:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圆
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.81,0:12:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香 沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.48,0:12:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.82,0:12:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.28,0:12:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.35,0:12:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我没谅解你以前难过的心情…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.55,0:12:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.29,0:12:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我已经注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.29,0:12:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不会再逃避 我要跟你站在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.96,0:12:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.03,0:12:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在一起作战 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.24,0:12:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.11,0:13:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…小恭…小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.71,0:13:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能坐视你孤军奋战
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.52,0:13:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我帮不上什么忙 总是我会努力到底
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.05,0:13:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们一起战斗到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.53,0:13:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.19,0:13:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…没有啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.07,0:13:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别太勉强哦 小圆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.48,0:13:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 只要行动时注意躲避
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.68,0:13:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该可以拖延40分钟的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.08,0:13:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你们两人在那期间…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.35,0:13:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会成功的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.29,0:13:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.82,0:13:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.29,0:13:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须去阻止对方对市民的持续攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.63,0:13:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 已经装上心跳钻石了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.77,0:14:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香 我想趁现在告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.71,0:14:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搬家过来的前一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.84,0:14:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正好…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.58,0:14:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在写信给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.38,0:14:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着我想一直与你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.12,0:14:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想与你分开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.92,0:14:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 一直鼓不起勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.86,0:14:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后还是没交给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.79,0:14:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.40,0:14:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.87,0:14:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来我后悔极了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.67,0:14:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭到天亮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.08,0:14:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气自己怎么拿不出勇气来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.41,0:14:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这次我敢说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.41,0:14:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你把勇气分给了我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.55,0:14:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想与你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.95,0:14:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远 永远在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.69,0:14:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.29,0:14:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.63,0:15:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是哦 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.16,0:15:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.10,0:15:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 吻我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.91,0:15:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.26,0:15:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.59,0:15:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.33,0:15:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热 好热啊 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.40,0:15:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸口 胸口好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.94,0:15:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好怕 我好怕啊 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.81,0:15:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.81,0:15:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.48,0:15:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.42,0:15:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.75,0:15:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我陪着你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.89,0:16:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会一直在你身边的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.56,0:16:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.23,0:16:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.70,0:16:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有重要的话没告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.77,0:16:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…所以你要加油
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.50,0:16:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.78,0:16:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.71,0:16:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.00,0:16:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀 全是些小角色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.87,0:16:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.27,0:16:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 超昂天使对我来说也是小角色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.61,0:16:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂天使不是小角色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.75,0:16:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦？是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.88,0:16:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.75,0:17:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是超昂天使的支援机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.02,0:17:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你就跟我慢慢玩好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.30,0:17:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里果然做得很精细
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.77,0:17:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.77,0:17:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.91,0:17:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶 这边也有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.31,0:17:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样！怎样！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.25,0:17:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌…讨厌…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.32,0:17:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.72,0:17:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就给你更多服务
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.06,0:17:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来慢慢的品尝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.33,0:17:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要动了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.93,0:17:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.14,0:17:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样 怎样 怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.74,0:17:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌！啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.48,0:18:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股会坏掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.96,0:18:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人就是机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.30,0:18:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 好玩的现在才开始
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.64,0:18:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是！？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.98,0:18:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂天使
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.58,0:18:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.38,0:18:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳钻石应该被我取走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.45,0:18:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 这样也好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.06,0:18:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少可以不用太过无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.53,0:18:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成功了…？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.46,0:18:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不用担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.87,0:19:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请小心 她的力量很大 可能装上了心跳钻石
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.00,0:19:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.07,0:19:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…我要进入修复模式了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.82,0:19:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你的了 沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.63,0:19:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪恶的低俗的戴亚斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.23,0:19:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你侵略这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.43,0:19:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护蓝色地球
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.37,0:19:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸口的鼓动通达天边
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.84,0:19:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂天使
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.71,0:19:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在来消灭邪恶的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.31,0:19:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.78,0:19:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.38,0:19:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会输的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.79,0:19:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啊？超昂天使？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.66,0:19:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的心跳钻石用起来感觉真是棒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.33,0:20:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点用也没有 这次换我出招
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.02,0:20:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太气人了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.23,0:20:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么力量
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.49,0:20:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.78,0:20:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.52,0:20:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳钻石应该已经让我变完美了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.26,0:21:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.59,0:21:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个高昂的心情不光是能量的来源而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.40,0:21:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不了解心的鼓动是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.60,0:21:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼才知道你在胡说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.94,0:21:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用这招解决你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.41,0:21:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.48,0:21:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用这倾注全力的一招
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.48,0:21:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂天使 你等着粉身碎骨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.09,0:21:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.62,0:21:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳的结束
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.30,0:21:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂绝技
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.72,0:22:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.73,0:22:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.07,0:22:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打赢了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.34,0:22:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了！沙由香！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.61,0:22:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.36,0:22:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要啦…小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.49,0:22:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超昂天使 你希望我怎么做呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.36,0:22:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里 挖这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲“这里”我怎么知道呢 超昂天使
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.63,0:22:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别欺负人了 小恭 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.37,0:23:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插我重要的地方 插烂我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.91,0:23:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙由香 真拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.98,0:23:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.99,0:23:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要…我还要更深
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.46,0:23:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再更激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.00,0:23:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 乳头已经尖了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.94,0:23:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.54,0:23:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 别摸那里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.34,0:23:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要吗？要我停住吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.41,0:23:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 再欺负我啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.49,0:23:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 插我 再插 再插
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.76,0:23:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好 沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.50,0:23:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.24,0:24:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.78,0:24:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去你们俩人的恋爱关系
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.72,0:24:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以长期性的眼光来看不能说很乐观哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.52,0:24:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.46,0:24:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说不会
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.19,0:24:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与戴亚斯特的战争还会持续
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.86,0:24:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得找回心跳钻石了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.26,0:24:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样没有长进是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.67,0:24:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法 这次我也参加 帮忙你们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.14,0:24:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么诱人的性感画面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.35,0:24:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 恭平 沙由香已经行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.22,0:24:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.22,0:24:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.29,0:25:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭平 不对
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.16,0:25:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我 是沙由香
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.97,0:25:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 难得你也加入了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.50,0:25:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.91,0:25:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.05,0:25:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.19,0:25:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要插我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.41,0:25:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来呀 快来呀 小恭
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.02,0:25:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.48,0:25:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.96,0:26:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴亚斯特又来袭了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.30,0:26:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小恭 快一点啦


