[Script Info]
Title:Sankarea 11
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00838383,&H00620062,&H00480048,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,1
Style: Staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H141F1F1F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: EDTitle,方正稚艺_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00141414,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPCN,方正中等线_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,8,134
Style: OPJP,DFGGothicP-W5,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,8,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFGHSMincho-W3,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,10,10,128
Style: Note1,方正稚艺_GBK,18,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,134
Style: Note2,方正中等线_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000F0F0F,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,5,134
Style: Movie1,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00C2BEBC,&HF0000000,&H001B1B1B,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Note3,仓耳今楷04 W04,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.78,0:01:50.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠れない夜に聞いた物語が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.10,0:01:54.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}絵空事だとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.42,0:02:11.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永遠を知るより快楽を求めて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.66,0:02:15.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今を悔やんでしまうのは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.84,0:02:22.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ココロの深くに棲みついた影から
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.03,0:02:26.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逃げるためだとしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.34,0:02:31.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それでもあたしはあたしを
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.62,0:02:35.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愛していられるなら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.19,0:02:41.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分に割れた太陽が朝を連れてきて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.46,0:02:46.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}闇に慣れた神経をじわり刺激する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:51.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}置き忘れた脳内はあえてそのままで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.04,0:02:56.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シナリオの消えた物語だ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:03:01.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由に自由に舵を取って
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.98,0:03:08.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと高くへ舞い上がって
Comment: 0,0:01:29.10,0:01:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.78,0:01:50.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在无法入眠的夜晚  所听到的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.10,0:01:54.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}假若只是子虚乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.42,0:02:11.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}与其知晓永恒  不如追求快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.66,0:02:15.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}懊恼着如今
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.84,0:02:26.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}是为了逃避  在心灵深处隐藏的阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.34,0:02:35.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使如此  我还是能够深爱着自己
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.19,0:02:41.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分为两半的太阳为我带来晨光
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.46,0:02:46.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}刺激着适应了黑暗的神经
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:51.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遗忘了的记忆尽管就让它遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.04,0:02:56.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如同失去了剧本的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:03:01.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自由地  自由地  把握住方向
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.98,0:03:08.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}向着更高的地方飞舞
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.54,0:22:29.09,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ひとつだけ　叶うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.98,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君の手の中　揺れる小さな花でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:47.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はじめてみる眩しいこの世界で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:55.60,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君ともしはぐれたとしても　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.11,0:23:06.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}見つけだして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.55,0:23:24.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目覚めたら　そばにいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明日も
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.54,0:22:29.09,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只有一个愿望  能够实现的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:40.98,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}希望能变成  在你手中摇曳着的小小花朵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:47.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}第一次看到  这个耀眼的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:55.60,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果和你走散了　也一定能
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.11,0:23:06.20,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.55,0:23:24.20,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}醒来睁开眼  就在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.38,0:23:31.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明天也是
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.57,0:03:47.61,OPTitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\be3}{\pos(188,294)}「才…不是…特别的」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.15,0:24:09.68,EDTitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be7}{\pos(328,245)}「那个瞬间…我…」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.87,0:00:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你想去哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.98,0:00:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会就这样把我丢进煮沸的热油…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.61,0:00:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是要把我从悬崖上丢下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.42,0:00:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…  女仆小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.63,0:00:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我上个厕所吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.43,0:00:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁这个机会逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.40,0:00:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  厕所吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.01,0:00:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等下会清扫的  所以请您随意失禁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.50,0:00:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.22,0:00:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,限
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.99,0:00:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.73,0:00:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.87,0:00:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  不是为了要拷问你才把你绑来的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.99,0:00:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.81,0:01:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道场？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.74,0:01:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器就放在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.16,0:01:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.25,0:01:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选个喜欢的就行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.67,0:01:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者如果你打算赤手空拳的话也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.23,0:01:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啊  这就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.62,0:01:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底谁才有保护礼弥的资格
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.33,0:01:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来分个胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.06,0:03:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是有能力付钱的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.78,0:03:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您回来  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.32,0:03:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把…请把父亲叫来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.66,0:03:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.47,0:03:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团一郎大人现在正忙着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.26,0:03:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君也在的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.18,0:03:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去父亲那边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.67,0:03:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.20,0:03:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请礼弥大小姐先暂时好好休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:03:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.75,0:04:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚里亚大人  礼弥大小姐似乎被擒获了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.46,0:04:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.90,0:04:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要去见她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.64,0:04:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.31,0:04:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我非得去见她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.19,0:04:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.22,0:04:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.67,0:04:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.70,0:04:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是团一郎大人的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.44,0:04:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我也命令你们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上给我松绑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.20,0:04:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀  礼弥大小姐竟然摆出这么可怕的脸来下命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.69,0:04:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是离家出走几天而已  竟然就变成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.76,0:04:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.82,0:04:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微瞒着团一郎大人给您点教训也没什么不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.45,0:05:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这样的机会可没有第二次了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你们打算做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.82,0:05:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.13,0:05:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.94,0:05:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么啊  这到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.16,0:05:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就想让礼弥大小姐穿穿看了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.59,0:05:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就觉得一定会很合身的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.01,0:05:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是卑鄙  封住我的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.66,0:05:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像恶作剧一样玩弄人家  你们不觉得害羞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.96,0:05:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  害羞的礼弥大小姐也好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.30,0:05:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下去让她穿什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.94,0:05:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女忍者？  玩偶？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.87,0:05:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}果然还是试试这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.83,0:05:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  现在可根本不是做这种事情的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.76,0:05:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里忐忑不安
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.61,0:05:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.50,0:05:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.68,0:06:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.61,0:06:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了只要能击中我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.99,0:06:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.74,0:06:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是有点卑鄙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.65,0:06:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可一点都不会击剑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.06,0:06:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就用你擅长的剑术或者格斗技巧都行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.28,0:06:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些我可一个都不会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.76,0:06:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  真是个软弱的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.55,0:06:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连护身术都没有学过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.01,0:06:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么礼弥会到这种一点才能和技能都没有的家伙那边去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.25,0:06:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连这种事都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.38,0:06:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连这种事都不知道啊  你连这种事都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.49,0:06:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以有哦  这个可以有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.64,0:06:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是超可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.85,0:07:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你们  快把我放开啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.78,0:07:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说了  不能遵从您的这个命令
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.82,0:07:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕难从命
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.68,0:07:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来果然还是女忍者吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.90,0:07:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么再接下去就让她穿玩偶哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.33,0:07:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.11,0:07:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不按顺序来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.93,0:07:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.62,0:07:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个都不会穿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.01,0:07:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要去才行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.98,0:07:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是这么认为的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯  没错没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.61,0:07:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.02,0:07:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以也就是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.64,0:07:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.31,0:07:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.32,0:07:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一对一决出胜负  这算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.02,0:07:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不管礼弥的想法  用胜负来决定礼弥属于谁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.33,0:07:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且强硬地把我带到这里来了还说这种话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.40,0:07:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太自以为是了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.64,0:08:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说在女儿生日的时候拍裸照是你的兴趣什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.80,0:08:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你为什么会知道这个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.25,0:08:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般根本不可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.49,0:08:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父爱什么的  早就超越了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.19,0:08:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话换了谁都会想从如此糟糕的老爸身边离开的吧  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.29,0:08:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般来说的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.58,0:08:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.57,0:08:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以玩笑就开到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.62,0:08:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥由谁来保护  还有才能什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.14,0:08:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这些来首先是礼弥想要怎么样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.55,0:08:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她本人都不在却要决定她的人生这可一点都不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.65,0:08:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点上就已经不对劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.76,0:08:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且说是要保护礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.26,0:08:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底只是你不想对礼弥放手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.77,0:08:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从她「母亲」那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.07,0:08:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥也觉得很痛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.18,0:09:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直将死去的妻子的影子重叠在礼弥身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.89,0:09:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.06,0:09:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷啊  你看起来有点小看我了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.80,0:09:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的存在什么的  只要有散华家的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.76,0:09:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很容易就能抹掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.06,0:09:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  礼弥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.75,0:09:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.63,0:09:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇  插进去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.14,0:09:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  降谷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.17,0:09:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我不会真的插下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.08,0:09:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.04,0:10:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.83,0:10:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.42,0:10:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报了一剑之仇了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.34,0:10:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.25,0:10:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  礼弥？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.89,0:10:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.22,0:10:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你这身打扮…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.86,0:10:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这种组合啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.59,0:10:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}死灵的僵尸兔耳娘
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.64,0:10:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能跟僵尸护士匹敌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.14,0:10:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  比这还萌一万倍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.12,0:10:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  这是被女仆长强行…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.56,0:10:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君  血  血…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.24,0:10:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.98,0:10:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.37,0:10:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.95,0:10:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.48,0:10:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为兴奋而分泌了很多肾上腺素？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.12,0:10:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:10:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.26,0:11:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那个时候伤口让礼弥舔过了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.64,0:11:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我是被礼弥的毒素感染了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.59,0:11:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毒素…感染…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.66,0:11:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛觉虽然是被麻痹了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.58,0:11:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心脏还在跳动也就是说毒素没有达到致死量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.99,0:11:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.79,0:11:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是半僵尸了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.33,0:11:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说僵尸…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.68,0:11:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.11,0:11:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就砍了你的脑袋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.26,0:12:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…  住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.67,0:12:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.18,0:12:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的一击应该已经决定胜负了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.17,0:12:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样都还要继续打的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.10,0:12:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就先问过我的剑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.20,0:12:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么啊  礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.19,0:12:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想要救你而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.44,0:12:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想要把侵害你的疾病治好而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.89,0:12:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起移居到美国吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.51,0:12:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手续已经全办好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.91,0:12:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要请来世界上所有的名医和研究者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.00,0:12:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许啊…  不
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.29,0:12:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定能找到治疗的方法的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.59,0:12:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这男的真的能救你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.28,0:12:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,财力和智慧都有极限的小鬼一个又能做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.56,0:13:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.69,0:13:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算治不好也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.92,0:13:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  这样下去的话  你的身体就会…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.71,0:13:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果为了治好而要离开这个小镇的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.17,0:13:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不如就这样了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.70,0:13:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是短暂的一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.41,0:13:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能和降谷君在这个小镇里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.65,0:13:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要这样我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.31,0:13:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.87,0:13:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.41,0:13:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  只要眼前这样一点点的自由就满足了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.69,0:13:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明是特别的高贵的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.35,0:14:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不懂吗  父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.41,0:14:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.72,0:14:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥想要的并不是「特别」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.26,0:14:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到现在为止答应了几次礼弥她自己想要做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.32,0:14:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}不算你让她做的那些
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.49,0:14:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.66,0:14:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在花园里找到蜗牛了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.31,0:14:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  礼弥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.34,0:14:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以碰那些脏东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.78,0:14:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要和朋友一起去购物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.43,0:14:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不去做那种事我也会买你喜欢的东西给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.78,0:14:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.70,0:14:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥已经是高中生了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.80,0:15:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要防止那些低俗的异性接近
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.73,0:15:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为礼弥要接受的遗传因子只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.06,0:15:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥她  只是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.44,0:15:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要做一个普通的女孩子而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.81,0:15:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的只是为了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.20,0:15:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了这样而已  你就死去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.85,0:15:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.26,0:15:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.43,0:15:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我赞成你一部分的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.27,0:15:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实只有我一个人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.52,0:16:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事情是怎么也做不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.74,0:16:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在那时希望你也能出一份力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.63,0:16:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我也希望  礼弥以后一直都留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.08,0:16:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.96,0:16:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.98,0:16:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不后悔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.43,0:16:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.22,0:16:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.68,0:16:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.41,0:16:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.61,0:16:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.68,0:17:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.94,0:17:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我在海外寻找治疗礼弥疾病的方法的那段时间里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.33,0:17:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时性的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.21,0:17:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是永远都交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.53,0:17:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.60,0:17:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.12,0:17:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此  如果你夺走礼弥的贞操  我绝对饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.94,0:17:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会  才不会啦  那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.35,0:17:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  对你说什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.48,0:17:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.37,0:17:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.11,0:17:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也好  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.44,0:17:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样总算…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.55,0:17:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能和礼弥一起生活…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.14,0:17:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君？  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.43,0:17:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降谷君  降谷君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.88,0:17:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.84,0:18:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要喝些什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.04,0:18:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.19,0:18:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.83,0:18:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  痛痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.69,0:18:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.85,0:18:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  痛觉恢复了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.94,0:18:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  体内的毒素已经没有了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.99,0:18:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.02,0:18:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应急措施是我们做的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.14,0:18:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是复活了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.95,0:18:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说我根本没死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.50,0:19:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.36,0:19:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了很多血  还以为你醒不过来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.90,0:19:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  让你担心了  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.59,0:19:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.40,0:19:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  你这打扮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.01,0:19:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.38,0:19:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为女仆们说这样降谷君一定会很高兴的才…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.57,0:19:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.93,0:19:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护士僵尸  棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.78,0:19:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥的话一击必杀了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.90,0:19:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.69,0:19:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  丸子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.59,0:19:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  笨蛋  笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.69,0:19:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听小萌路说你受了重伤就飞奔过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.90,0:19:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然知道受伤了就别跳过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.99,0:19:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.53,0:19:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说回来  为什么会受这么重的伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.36,0:19:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.98,0:20:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.77,0:20:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.32,0:20:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  为什么穿着护士服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.76,0:20:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这是因为降谷君会很高兴才…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.72,0:20:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你让人家干什么呢  大变态
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.67,0:20:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是我让她这么做的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.56,0:20:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是好像很高兴的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.18,0:20:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这当然了…喂  你让我说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.16,0:20:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之降谷君变成这样都是我的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.86,0:20:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼弥  别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.53,0:20:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…散华同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.28,0:20:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄宿在千纮家的僵尸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.91,0:20:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.32,0:20:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好像还没好好打过招呼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.17,0:20:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你大一岁的左王子兰子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.10,0:20:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.60,0:20:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮的姐姐  而且是未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.18,0:20:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  是作为人类的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.01,0:21:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的吧  刚才的是开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.20,0:21:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  丸子…同学  别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.90,0:21:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  但是不是在小学的时候定好了的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.47,0:21:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.74,0:21:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.41,0:21:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和我定婚约吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.59,0:21:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.29,0:21:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  定了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.09,0:21:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  那就定了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.57,0:21:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁记得啊  那时候的闲谈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.13,0:21:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的  对不起啦  散华同学
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.28,0:21:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是刚才的看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.58,0:21:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千纮慌张时的傻样  很赞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.49,0:21:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了  你刚才也不是差点要哭了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.60,0:21:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  那个是在演戏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.91,0:21:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗小孩啊  那么我也是在演戏
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.54,0:21:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么不及格
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.26,0:21:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.38,0:21:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把前因后果说给我听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.64,0:21:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先松开我再说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:21:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}这个做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.00,0:21:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  这个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.26,0:22:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢着降谷君啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.50,0:23:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  小萌路她不干了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.45,0:23:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法  她也还只是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.73,0:23:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.78,0:23:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.84,0:23:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回  散华礼弥  第十二话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.51,0:23:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个瞬间…我…」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.83,0:24:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  要看哦萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.56,0:24:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.51,0:24:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小萌路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.08,0:24:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也不逃避了
