[Script Info]
Title:White Album BD 15
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H03ED6014,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warn,黑体,50,&H000000FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,5,30,30,10,1
Style: INJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,15,15,8,1
Style: inC,方正粗宋_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,15,15,10,1
Style: up,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H03ED6014,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,8,1
Style: OPJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,50,50,7,1
Style: OPC,方正粗宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,50,50,7,1
Style: EDJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,18,&H008F8FCC,&H00D7EBFF,&H80FFFFFF,&H80D7EBFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,1,10,10,7,1
Style: EDC,方正粗宋_GBK,18,&H008F8FCC,&H00D7EBFF,&H80FFFFFF,&H80D7EBFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,10,10,7,1
Style: pos,@方正中等线_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正中等线_GBK,22,&H006F4B4B,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,134
Style: staff,方正中等线_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--OP--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:01:03.99,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}现在只需在我的怀中睡去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.99,0:01:08.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}不要再去向别处
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.06,0:01:26.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}在朦胧中的深渊边摇摇欲坠的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.43,0:01:29.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}群青色的夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.71,0:01:35.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}探寻着那没有交辉的繁星
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.38,0:01:42.97,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追求着你的指尖  在黑暗中彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.97,0:01:46.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}即使挣扎着也无法逃离
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.12,0:01:51.90,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}渐渐地沉入爱的汪洋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.83,0:01:59.52,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}轻柔的叹息  连心灵也为之震颤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.52,0:02:05.25,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如同缠绵美丽的蛛丝一般
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:07.32,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}令人无法动弹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.32,0:02:09.53,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}请原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.53,0:02:12.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}能在你的臂弯中入睡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.81,0:02:16.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}即使舍弃一切也毫不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.08,0:02:23.71,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}别再总是作出乖巧的幻影
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.78,0:02:27.19,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}请找到真实的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.25,0:02:33.96,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我一直等待着...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:01:03.99,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}眠りなさい　今はただ私の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.99,0:01:08.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どこにも行かないで…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.06,0:01:26.43,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}微睡の淵で揺れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.43,0:01:29.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}群青色の夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.71,0:01:35.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}交わることのない星を探してる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.38,0:01:42.97,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}あなたを求める指先　闇に彷徨って
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.97,0:01:46.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もがいても抜け出せない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.12,0:01:51.90,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛の海に溺れてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.83,0:01:59.52,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}柔らな吐息に　心さえも震える
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.52,0:02:05.25,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}絡まる美しい蜘蛛の糸のよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:07.32,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}動けないの…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.32,0:02:09.53,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私を許して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.53,0:02:12.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}あなたの腕に抱かれて眠る
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.81,0:02:16.08,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何もかも捨てたっていい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.08,0:02:23.71,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}良いコのままの幻影なんて作るのはやめて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.08,0:02:23.71,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs12\pos(290,330)}まぼろし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.78,0:02:27.19,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}本当の私を見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.25,0:02:33.96,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ずっと待ってる…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--ED--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.44,0:22:56.02,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}わたしにいつも　あなたはやさしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.06,0:23:02.63,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そのやさしさが　不安にする
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.83,0:23:11.48,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}運命の糸　ほどけないように
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.49,0:23:17.83,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}何度も結びなおして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.26,0:23:26.64,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}次に会う約束　出来ないまま
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:36.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}別れの言葉　まだ聞きたくはないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.80,0:23:44.21,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}会えない夜に　夢で逢えたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.36,0:23:51.98,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明日がつらくても　笑っていられる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.06,0:23:59.49,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どんなに遠く　離れていても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.80,0:24:09.62,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}つながっていれると信じている
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.44,0:22:56.02,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在我面前  你总是很温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.06,0:23:02.63,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}但那份温柔  却让我不安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.83,0:23:11.48,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为了让命运的红线  不要被解开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.49,0:23:17.83,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我无数次将它重新系起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.26,0:23:26.64,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}下一次见面的约定  还没有做好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:36.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}离别的话语  我还不想听到
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.80,0:23:44.21,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无法见面的夜晚  若是能在梦中相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.36,0:23:51.98,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不管明天如何难过也能笑容以对
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.06,0:23:59.49,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使身在天涯海角
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.80,0:24:09.62,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}也深信彼此能够紧紧相连
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--POS--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:30.55,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十五页  找不到的东西  会破坏周围  因为不在那里  所以也无从下手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.50,0:04:17.18,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,200,0,200,500,3700)\pos(590,100)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}就是钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.24,0:04:17.18,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,100,0,200,500,2000)\pos(120,250)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.12,0:11:29.04,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,80,255,0,200,1000,5000)\pos(530,75)\frz-90\1c&HFFAADD&}我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.39,0:11:30.04,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,80,255,0,200,1000,5000)\pos(45,95)\frz-90\1c&HFFAADD&}不想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.39,0:11:30.04,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,80,220,0,200,1000,3800)\pos(450,105)\frz-90\1c&HFFAADD&}变成一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.10,0:18:50.02,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,90,0,200,300,2000)\pos(180,230)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.86,0:18:50.02,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,90,0,200,300,1300)\pos(30,120)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.94,0:00:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护士小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.19,0:00:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.30,0:00:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子是什么时候回去的？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.19,0:00:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  也许是为了不吵醒您才悄悄走了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.51,0:00:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是从三点半开始就醒着了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.70,0:00:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社长  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.36,0:02:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.30,0:02:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在在医院  马上就能出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.34,0:02:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.51,0:02:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想  大约一个小时后就能到…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.71,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用勉强了  照顾好你爸爸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.79,0:02:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有勉强呀  又没必要一整天都陪着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.32,0:03:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大问题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.21,0:03:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神得都有点啰嗦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.50,0:03:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我会去的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.55,0:03:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.20,0:03:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样不好吧  这是今年最后一次课了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.74,0:03:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.91,0:03:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,go  here  come  here  不许来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.93,0:03:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻奈  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.70,0:03:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.42,0:03:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那边是老师翘班了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.78,0:03:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  翘班什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.29,0:03:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  冬弥君  星期五是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.78,0:03:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狠狠吃了一记闭门羹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.94,0:03:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边是学生翘课了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.82,0:03:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥可是居功至伟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.74,0:03:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  简直就是搅人生意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.57,0:03:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.85,0:03:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥也在做家庭教师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.09,0:03:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.03,0:03:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥老师  比我还要大受欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.45,0:04:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这部分会被扣薪水吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.84,0:04:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  说起来我还没见过她父母
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.97,0:04:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.51,0:04:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是钱的问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.57,0:04:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮今天没有课程的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.84,0:04:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是今天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.05,0:04:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到明年都要休息了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.54,0:04:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.71,0:04:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教给我的东西都忘记的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.88,0:04:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是很幸运吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.90,0:04:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够集中精力工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.10,0:04:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天本来只安排了课程的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.48,0:04:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.77,0:04:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能休息…了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.95,0:04:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是浪费
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.71,0:04:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.80,0:04:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.44,0:04:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不能这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.42,0:04:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了伯父  今天才能像这样见面…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.97,0:05:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮真是笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.60,0:05:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.87,0:05:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意  往常的由绮…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.79,0:05:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  由绮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.80,0:05:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  冬弥君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.16,0:05:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.12,0:05:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然由绮不管什么时候都…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.17,0:05:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.68,0:05:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次的演唱会明明来了那么多的观众
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.11,0:05:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.30,0:05:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到了掌声  得到了鼓励
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.45,0:05:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高兴得不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.91,0:05:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…高兴的却只有我一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.13,0:05:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.06,0:05:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家并不高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.64,0:05:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方先生也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.76,0:05:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈也是  弥生小姐也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.67,0:05:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲也是  彰君也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.10,0:05:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.03,0:05:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.99,0:06:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多这个年纪不得不考虑的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.16,0:06:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我而来的那些观众也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.61,0:06:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…由绮什么都没做到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.44,0:06:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白  但即使如此还是没察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.05,0:06:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…只是装作没察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.85,0:06:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人傻笑的自己真是笨蛋大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.31,0:06:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丢脸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.88,0:06:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.45,0:06:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是讨厌这样的由绮了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.82,0:06:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以课程也不上了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.36,0:06:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井冬弥到了  藤井冬弥到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.18,0:06:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请尽快上车
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.17,0:06:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近总是空着呢  客人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.27,0:06:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背后的座位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.80,0:06:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.63,0:06:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还不能坐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.14,0:07:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  司机先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.42,0:07:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.57,0:07:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.76,0:07:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.84,0:07:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.72,0:07:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  在哪在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.37,0:07:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.67,0:07:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么明天练习爬坡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.28,0:07:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  老大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.77,0:08:29.64,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于职业棒球的合约更改
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.90,0:08:32.00,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首位身价过亿的球员诞生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.70,0:08:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天一晚上都和森川小姐在一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.27,0:08:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.44,0:08:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.91,0:08:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是见啊见  还没见够吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.33,0:08:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  因为某个人的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.46,0:08:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么闲吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.09,0:08:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶像这个工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.47,0:09:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何  第一次亲眼看到偶像的感想
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.56,0:09:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.63,0:09:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前有见过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.80,0:09:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中的三年里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.98,0:09:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我替你接过多少电话了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.92,0:09:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  原来是声音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.23,0:09:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声如其人的小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.04,0:09:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故意不让你们见面的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.71,0:09:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有在你妈妈的葬礼上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.87,0:09:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我阻止过她
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.21,0:09:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让她看到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.83,0:09:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想让她看到你妈妈？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.55,0:09:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是我？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.74,0:09:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.83,0:09:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的葬礼时她会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.05,0:09:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.33,0:09:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你平时的强硬哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.37,0:09:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己为自己哭算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.95,0:09:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老糊涂了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.97,0:09:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.85,0:09:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人就是这样的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.49,0:09:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活久了  脑子里就会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.96,0:10:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是年轻小鬼的你不会明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.59,0:10:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庞大的记忆  体验  回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.07,0:10:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些没有直接关系的片段
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.32,0:10:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为某个小契机而瞬间连结成一线
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.30,0:10:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不光有悲伤的事  痛苦的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.72,0:10:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快乐的事  还有开心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.65,0:10:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分时间地点  散乱地排列在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.39,0:10:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它们…对  像随意翻阅杂志那样浏览
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.44,0:10:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后不知道为什么总是让泪腺失控
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.03,0:10:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是少说两句吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.15,0:10:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.24,0:10:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不明白的  没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.93,0:10:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有哭过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.54,0:10:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.58,0:10:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没什么回忆和体验
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:10:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会哭的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.69,0:11:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为了朋友哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸你也有过年轻的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.24,0:11:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  恋人  一大群伙伴什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.25,0:11:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都忘记了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.35,0:11:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴什么的连屎都不如
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.34,0:11:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.75,0:11:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.52,0:11:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人  直到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.00,0:11:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后啊弗兰奇  就是我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.48,0:11:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听过很多次了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.86,0:11:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但还是再听一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.23,0:11:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了一幅无名的印象派油画
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我泪流不止
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.23,0:11:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是…悲伤着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.06,0:12:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话我能明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.74,0:12:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.15,0:12:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里有三份悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.98,0:12:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去的悲伤  察觉到失去后的悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.08,0:12:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.78,0:12:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在眼前却不能得到的悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.07,0:12:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张画上的是母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.37,0:12:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有见过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.28,0:12:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那的确是母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.22,0:12:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.98,0:12:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.19,0:12:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.03,0:12:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么下一首歌曲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.50,0:12:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是大受好评的绪方理奈…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.02,0:13:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.29,0:13:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中止课程完全是因为我的问题  不是由绮的错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.76,0:13:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.38,0:13:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那场演唱会后竟还会为那种事闷闷不乐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.99,0:13:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来幸福还远远不够呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.12,0:13:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定了  我来增加由绮的幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.38,0:13:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往心里注入幸福  不断堆积  大大地膨胀起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.10,0:13:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到炸裂  把歌迷都卷进暴风中来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.55,0:13:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮  也请对我撒下幸福的粉末
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.69,0:13:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把被不幸吞没的我拉回到幸福中来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.74,0:14:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死了  绝对要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.79,0:14:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的话也不用勉强哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.16,0:14:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.80,0:14:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就准备一个人去的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.39,0:14:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要这样说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.58,0:14:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.78,0:14:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  带我去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.41,0:14:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻奈…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.28,0:15:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要连阿遥都把麻奈丢下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.34,0:15:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.77,0:15:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在除夕  为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.97,0:15:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是除夕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.70,0:15:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社长是这样说的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.69,0:15:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「要让由绮幸福」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.80,0:15:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.64,0:15:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是来探病的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.23,0:16:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.87,0:16:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.76,0:16:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个年末年初准备做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.21,0:16:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是家里好  一想到过了新年三天就要回到那牢狱去…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.51,0:16:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井君要是也能回来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.88,0:16:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是在为我着想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.07,0:16:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲  能帮我试试荞麦面汤汁的味道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.37,0:16:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.07,0:16:49.49,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和阿遥去合宿  麻奈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.30,0:16:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  每个人都是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.10,0:16:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是我的女儿？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.89,0:16:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.79,0:17:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有多远
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.18,0:17:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.45,0:17:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.17,0:17:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕凪市内
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.39,0:17:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不信  坏人遥说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.36,0:17:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电灯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.71,0:17:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.88,0:17:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壁炉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.54,0:17:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完饭就一觉睡到太阳出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.76,0:17:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡袋也带来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.00,0:17:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏人再加上恶鬼遥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.77,0:18:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.84,0:18:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么麻奈会去冬弥的家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.30,0:18:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.44,0:18:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那么有请  曲目当然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.10,0:18:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.47,0:18:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君  去散步吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.01,0:18:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.56,0:18:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是晴天太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.24,0:18:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.31,0:18:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是绪方先生批准的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.43,0:18:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.41,0:18:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.61,0:18:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.59,0:18:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…  这个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.30,0:18:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:19:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是还是  新年快乐  冬弥君…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.77,0:19:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  要拍了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.59,0:19:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  茄子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.38,0:19:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  笑一笑笑一笑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.24,0:19:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈小姐  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.77,0:19:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.51,0:19:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  差不多该走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.09,0:20:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.58,0:20:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新年参拜…不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.63,0:21:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  这里不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.97,0:21:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不行…那在哪里才可以
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.32,0:21:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经过了一个月了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.10,0:21:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七濑君  伯父会被吵醒的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.80,0:21:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上  echoes见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.97,0:21:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy  new  year  青年
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.22,0:22:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.15,0:22:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.26,0:22:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是去了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.77,0:22:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.82,0:22:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新年参拜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.21,0:22:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  省了不少事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.94,0:24:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十六页
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.31,0:24:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起小的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.38,0:24:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有些因为害羞而坐立不安的事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.53,0:24:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个相比的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.81,0:24:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,White  Album


