[Script Info]
Title:White Album BD 18
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H03ED6014,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warn,黑体,50,&H000000FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,5,30,30,10,1
Style: INJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,15,15,8,1
Style: inC,方正粗宋_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,15,15,10,1
Style: up,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H03ED6014,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,8,1
Style: OPJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,50,50,7,1
Style: OPC,方正粗宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EBAD6D,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,50,50,7,1
Style: EDJ,DFPHSMincho-W9,18,&H008F8FCC,&H00D7EBFF,&H80FFFFFF,&H80D7EBFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,1,10,10,7,1
Style: EDC,方正粗宋_GBK,18,&H008F8FCC,&H00D7EBFF,&H80FFFFFF,&H80D7EBFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,7,10,10,7,1
Style: pos,@方正中等线_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正中等线_GBK,22,&H006F4B4B,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,134
Style: staff,方正中等线_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--OP--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.36,0:01:25.99,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}现在只需在我的怀中睡去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.99,0:01:30.26,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}不要再去向别处
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.06,0:01:48.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}在朦胧中的深渊边摇摇欲坠的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.43,0:01:51.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}群青色的夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.71,0:01:57.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}探寻着那没有交辉的繁星
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.38,0:02:04.97,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追求着你的指尖  在黑暗中彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.97,0:02:08.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}即使挣扎着也无法逃离
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.12,0:02:13.90,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}渐渐地沉入爱的汪洋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.83,0:02:21.52,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}轻柔的叹息  连心灵也为之震颤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.52,0:02:27.25,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如同缠绵美丽的蛛丝一般
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.25,0:02:29.32,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}令人无法动弹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.32,0:02:31.53,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}请原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.53,0:02:34.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}能在你的臂弯中入睡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.81,0:02:38.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}即使舍弃一切也毫不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.08,0:02:45.71,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}别再总是作出乖巧的幻影
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.78,0:02:49.19,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}请找到真实的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.25,0:02:55.96,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我一直等待着...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.36,0:01:25.99,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}眠りなさい　今はただ私の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.99,0:01:30.26,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どこにも行かないで…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.06,0:01:48.43,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}微睡の淵で揺れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.43,0:01:51.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}群青色の夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.71,0:01:57.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}交わることのない星を探してる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.38,0:02:04.97,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}あなたを求める指先　闇に彷徨って
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.97,0:02:08.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もがいても抜け出せない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.12,0:02:13.90,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}愛の海に溺れてく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.83,0:02:21.52,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}柔らな吐息に　心さえも震える
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.52,0:02:27.25,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}絡まる美しい蜘蛛の糸のよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.25,0:02:29.32,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}動けないの…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.32,0:02:31.53,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私を許して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.53,0:02:34.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}あなたの腕に抱かれて眠る
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.81,0:02:38.08,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何もかも捨てたっていい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.08,0:02:45.71,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}良いコのままの幻影なんて作るのはやめて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.08,0:02:45.71,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\fs12\pos(290,330)}まぼろし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.78,0:02:49.19,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}本当の私を見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.25,0:02:55.96,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ずっと待ってる…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--ED--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.44,0:22:56.02,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}わたしにいつも　あなたはやさしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.06,0:23:02.63,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そのやさしさが　不安にする
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.83,0:23:11.48,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}運命の糸　ほどけないように
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.49,0:23:17.83,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}何度も結びなおして
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.26,0:23:26.64,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}次に会う約束　出来ないまま
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:36.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}別れの言葉　まだ聞きたくはないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.80,0:23:44.21,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}会えない夜に　夢で逢えたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.36,0:23:51.98,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明日がつらくても　笑っていられる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.06,0:23:59.49,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どんなに遠く　離れていても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.80,0:24:09.62,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}つながっていれると信じている
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.44,0:22:56.02,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在我面前  你总是很温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.06,0:23:02.63,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}但那份温柔  却让我不安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.83,0:23:11.48,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为了让命运的红线  不要被解开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.49,0:23:17.83,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我无数次将它重新系起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.26,0:23:26.64,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}下一次见面的约定  还没有做好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:36.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}离别的话语  我还不想听到
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.80,0:23:44.21,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无法见面的夜晚  若是能在梦中相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.36,0:23:51.98,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不管明天如何难过也能笑容以对
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.06,0:23:59.49,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使身在天涯海角
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.80,0:24:09.62,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}也深信彼此能够紧紧相连
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--POS--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.67,0:00:14.65,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十八页  虫子太随性了吧  明明躲在壳子里  还说有什么幽闭恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.38,0:06:38.59,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,1000,2500)\pos(90,130)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}不是这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.33,0:07:37.82,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,1000,2600)\pos(535,150)\frz-90\1c&H552637&}什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.34,0:07:37.82,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,500,1600)\pos(485,220)\frz-90\1c&H552637&}说呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.03,0:07:43.14,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,255,0,200,1000,5100)\pos(540,110)\frz-90\1c&H552627&}说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.90,0:07:44.02,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,255,0,200,1000,5200)\pos(100,237)\frz-90\1c&H552637&}由绮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.04,0:08:54.77,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,500,2700)\pos(540,100)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.44,0:09:08.90,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,500,2400)\pos(215,140)\frz-90\1c&H440010&}理奈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.32,0:09:08.90,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,20,0,200,500,1700)\pos(170,210)\frz-90\1c&H440010&}她已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.71,0:21:35.41,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,200,0,200,500,3800)\pos(570,115)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}谁来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.68,0:21:38.46,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,120,0,200,500,2900)\pos(110,175)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}由绮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.15,0:21:38.46,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,20,0,200,500,1300)\pos(554,190)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}美 咲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.68,0:21:40.97,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,80,0,200,500,2300)\pos(145,120)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}遥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.68,0:21:40.97,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,20,0,200,500,1300)\pos(55,180)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}麻 奈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.43,0:21:42.65,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,20,0,200,500,1200)\pos(570,110)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}谁来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.90,0:21:47.59,pos,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(255,0,230,0,200,500,4800)\pos(65,110)\frz-90\1c&H662627&}阻止我
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----TEXT-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.09,0:00:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问理奈小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.83,0:00:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然的转会  有过困惑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.39,0:00:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  因为是自己决定的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.70,0:00:16.44,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于转会到曾经是对手的M&M  Music  请简要说下感想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.94,0:00:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有觉得是对手什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.26,0:00:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和您的家庭无任何关联吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.14,0:00:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有传言这和金钱上的交易有关  您知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.07,0:00:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说「卖身」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.62,0:00:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这方面请询问绪方先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.60,0:00:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您也是绪方…小姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.75,0:00:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方都厌倦对方了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.79,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就请这样写吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.85,0:00:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样的面孔  同样的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样的提问
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.59,0:00:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和平时大家所认为的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.45,0:00:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么再请问神崎社长
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.89,0:00:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接收至今为止的对手  心情如何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.16,0:01:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为这边的人的话就没有什么敌我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.27,0:01:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的对手又不存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.90,0:01:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.59,0:01:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.54,0:01:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该转移了  各位
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.50,0:02:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要去M3那地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.39,0:03:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底在想些什么  傻了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.89,0:03:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了算了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.15,0:03:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方事务所就用由绮一人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.90,0:03:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方理奈的歌就卖不出去然后饿死在路边算了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.57,0:03:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.00,0:03:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈走掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.87,0:03:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樵夫也跟着她一起跳槽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.28,0:03:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.60,0:03:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.80,0:03:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯着女性的脸看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.15,0:03:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.66,0:03:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.75,0:03:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.60,0:03:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.40,0:03:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.62,0:03:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然要做了  按照预定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.94,0:03:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.65,0:03:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.95,0:03:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到最后都是你的胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.80,0:03:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想快点解决而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.91,0:03:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这周内
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.95,0:03:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天不也是在这周内吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.31,0:04:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是周末  而且是大凶日
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.13,0:04:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不适合你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.50,0:04:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神崎社长
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.21,0:04:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样那幅画的钱就够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.43,0:04:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就要看理奈她了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.70,0:04:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…得看我们家的玛瑙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.56,0:04:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不错哦  这次的专辑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.11,0:04:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在正月的时候进行合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.72,0:04:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一周内就写完了全部曲目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.42,0:04:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会期待的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.80,0:04:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.47,0:04:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录音室也谢谢了  小英
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.33,0:04:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.94,0:04:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果玛瑙不行的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.65,0:04:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就得让理奈尽量多赚点了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.99,0:04:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹就拜托您了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.27,0:04:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.74,0:04:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.98,0:04:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛瑙小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.02,0:05:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个样子要是被人拍到了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.53,0:05:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.05,0:05:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.00,0:05:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没去看望呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.12,0:05:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备等冬弥君来了一起去的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.58,0:05:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  你早说的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.16,0:05:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天有打工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.55,0:05:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.23,0:05:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束后来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.14,0:05:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心想有时间的话就等等吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.08,0:05:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以两个人聊一会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.91,0:05:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.44,0:05:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.69,0:05:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈她…                          维纳斯…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.53,0:06:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君先说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.36,0:06:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视上看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.75,0:06:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈她…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.05,0:06:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.71,0:06:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了…一跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.13,0:06:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  而且还偏偏是去了M3
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.01,0:06:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是过分  绪方先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.38,0:06:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又不是惩罚游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.34,0:06:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈她说过要独立
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.80,0:06:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.80,0:06:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人太痛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.39,0:06:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她去别的事务所是绪方先生的关怀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.24,0:06:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.74,0:06:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.58,0:06:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.09,0:06:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.61,0:06:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈的事已经不行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.58,0:06:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能做点什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.64,0:06:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做点什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.21,0:06:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经这样正式发表了应该没有…办法了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.52,0:07:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我也明白  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.16,0:07:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.07,0:07:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈要走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.78,0:07:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周就要去M&M  Music了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.76,0:07:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.27,0:07:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮的担心我也明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.02,0:07:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管理奈她去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.00,0:07:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会变得比现在更厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.64,0:07:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就已经很厉害了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.02,0:07:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.76,0:07:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然只是我寂寞了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.23,0:07:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.60,0:07:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君明天休息吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.15,0:07:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈明天要录制节目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.94,0:08:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在绪方事务所最后的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.32,0:08:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人一起去给她加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.44,0:08:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明…明天…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.99,0:08:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.53,0:08:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彰拜托我去echoes替他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.18,0:08:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和美咲约会什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.74,0:08:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还得来看望老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.46,0:08:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.94,0:08:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.25,0:08:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我已经和理奈没关系了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.57,0:08:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就是演唱会时候暂时跑腿的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.95,0:08:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.79,0:08:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我一个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.00,0:08:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  忘记了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.89,0:08:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得去和东央电视台的制片人见面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.24,0:08:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维纳斯的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.95,0:08:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道了吗  冬弥君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.27,0:08:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.28,0:08:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥生小姐那里听来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.95,0:08:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.17,0:08:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是她说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.95,0:09:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前阵子碰巧她送我的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.99,0:09:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.92,0:09:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维纳斯  要出场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.46,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.63,0:09:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.09,0:09:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.24,0:09:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不出场也行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.06,0:09:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.36,0:09:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想出场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.25,0:09:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.28,0:09:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.28,0:09:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向伯父问候一下就走
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.73,0:10:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要躲着我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.61,0:10:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是躲着你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.49,0:10:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸都这样了并不是做那个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.03,0:10:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白父亲的病情与和我的交往间有什么关联性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.43,0:10:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.13,0:10:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮小姐她还是不知道的好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.00,0:10:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井先生的背叛就算下十次地狱也不够
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.79,0:10:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.77,0:10:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.72,0:10:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.37,0:10:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.22,0:10:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该做的是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.46,0:10:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让由绮小姐明白理奈小姐已经不在的现实
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.15,0:10:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且告诉她理奈小姐现在最需要的是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.75,0:10:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.49,0:10:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.61,0:10:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对做不到这些事的你…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.95,0:10:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要这样就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.50,0:11:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.19,0:11:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲  由绮小姐  所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.81,0:11:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.70,0:11:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君等会就会来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.90,0:11:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在冬弥来之前  过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.59,0:11:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能马上就会发生一些让由绮小姐伤心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.02,0:11:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能会告诉冬弥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.66,0:11:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在等待
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.19,0:12:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.17,0:12:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但年纪一大
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.02,0:12:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何况像这样  一整天都躺着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.39,0:12:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会开始胡思乱想还有没有来世
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.44,0:12:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬弥君他…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.89,0:12:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能想起来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.92,0:12:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.38,0:12:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那样也想不起来的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.20,0:12:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时再说那时的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.91,0:12:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会离开你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.58,0:12:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.10,0:12:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会再一次重新喜欢上他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.97,0:12:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说会让人心跳的话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.23,0:12:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.16,0:13:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎没有问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.11,0:13:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么最后由成员代表的团长文子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.25,0:13:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对大家说几句话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.07,0:13:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们樱团今天解散
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.35,0:13:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然团员会回到各自的生活中去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.59,0:14:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.56,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.93,0:14:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在街上遇见的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.14,0:14:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请打声招呼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.10,0:14:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的精神将会由副团长沙莉衣继承
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.35,0:14:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天单飞出道的洞院沙莉衣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.33,0:14:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.87,0:14:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把信给了理奈小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.71,0:14:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没有交给她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.39,0:14:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是理奈她…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.51,0:14:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是误会吧  我是直接给藤井先生的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.87,0:14:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.23,0:14:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.88,0:14:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.01,0:15:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈说是你把藤井君从echoes送来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.74,0:15:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.93,0:15:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个也是误会的话我就不知道该怎么办了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是到途中  由绮小姐可以安心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.95,0:15:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  真的…是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.11,0:15:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的日程能稍微安排一点自由时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.94,0:15:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…不行的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.91,0:15:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.70,0:15:37.00,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}女王的造反 绪方理奈离开事务所 发表会也没有说明理由\N也有传闻说是和森川由绮发生争执
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.16,0:15:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我宝贵的由绮这么痛苦的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.93,0:15:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.41,0:15:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.69,0:15:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正要去接她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.57,0:16:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我问声好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.75,0:16:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在就松口气了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.19,0:16:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要安心还太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.38,0:16:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦  两个人都将由绮弃于不顾的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.27,0:16:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.49,0:17:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.70,0:17:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.31,0:17:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是森川由绮  请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.92,0:17:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子就是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.31,0:17:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年我们的主力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.32,0:17:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和理奈完全不一样的类型呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.22,0:17:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后她就是绪方事务所的王牌
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.63,0:17:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连妹妹都放走了  真是下了决心了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.66,0:17:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为森川由绮是超越理奈的人才
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.49,0:17:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈也输了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.38,0:17:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.27,0:18:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是绪方事务所的藤井
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.23,0:18:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈小姐的经纪人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.22,0:18:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  请进
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.43,0:18:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.42,0:18:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.92,0:18:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收拾完了就走  你们先去把车子开出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.45,0:18:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.54,0:18:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤井君…？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.04,0:18:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  是由绮说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.69,0:18:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在电视上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.96,0:19:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  已经和我没关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.42,0:19:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.95,0:19:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个大麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.29,0:19:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由绮她…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.79,0:19:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由绮让你来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.00,0:19:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是想一起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.71,0:19:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是由绮今天有很重要的工作…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.03,0:19:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.23,0:19:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.51,0:19:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子  真拿她没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.48,0:19:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是个外行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.08,0:19:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能和她一直做朋友  都那样说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.26,0:19:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.17,0:19:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是那么有精神的话  我就放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.25,0:19:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有精神哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.47,0:19:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是我  你以为我会哭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.79,0:19:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事  完全没有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.10,0:19:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  芝士蛋糕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.82,0:19:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是echoes的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.90,0:19:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  不是echoes的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.75,0:20:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是谢谢你  我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.35,0:20:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.83,0:20:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.16,0:20:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  不回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.70,0:20:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈  没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.65,0:20:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.42,0:20:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.07,0:20:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是没事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.93,0:20:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在开玩笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.84,0:20:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.56,0:20:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我  快放开
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.37,0:20:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么理奈  这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.99,0:20:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像比由绮还要渺小
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.90,0:20:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我和由绮相比
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.52,0:20:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在…  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.19,0:20:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我放开
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.16,0:20:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微这样…待一会
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.49,0:21:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像呼吸困难  心怦怦直跳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.01,0:21:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎都要跳出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.48,0:21:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈  在哭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.04,0:21:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有哭  我不会哭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.89,0:21:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.95,0:21:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是平日里的理奈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.39,0:21:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.01,0:21:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.45,0:21:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个请求…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.80,0:21:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吻我  藤井君
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.03,0:24:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十九页
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.16,0:24:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是因为厌倦了才走向下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.01,0:24:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大多在走之前  看起来就已经厌倦了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.03,0:24:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,White  Album


