[Script Info]
Title:
Original Script:
Synch Point:0
Script Updated By: Hanimeshare@2013
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Simhei,34,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H01FFFFFF,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.25,0:00:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.17,0:00:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里的屁眼太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.92,0:00:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.34,0:00:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼…屁眼好舒服…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.77,0:00:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為甚麼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.77,0:00:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為甚麼會這麼舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.44,0:00:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.28,0:00:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.45,0:00:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你帶伊萬里來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.87,0:00:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是巧奪天工
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.12,0:00:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是最棒的肉體
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.96,0:00:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別停下來 再插
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.71,0:00:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在停住我會發瘋的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.97,0:00:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿妳沒有辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.98,0:01:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 要高潮了 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.23,0:01:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 伊萬里 盡量高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.40,0:01:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在水無瀨的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.57,0:01:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以處女之身高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.92,0:01:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 讓水無瀨看看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.59,0:01:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳有生以來第一次的高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.93,0:01:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 水無瀨在看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.10,0:01:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.35,0:01:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.93,0:01:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要高潮了…要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.27,0:01:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.86,0:01:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨也一起高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.45,0:02:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦 伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.12,0:02:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了 高潮了 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.88,0:02:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.88,0:02:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見想奪走伊萬里的身體 招來惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 那麼做的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.23,0:02:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她知道那個方法
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.66,0:02:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.07,0:02:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.32,0:02:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城老師
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.16,0:02:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有完…我被大量灌藥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.67,0:02:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本以為自己已經適應藥物…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.25,0:02:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 去沖個熱水澡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.34,0:02:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.17,0:02:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.68,0:03:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.35,0:03:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.18,0:03:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 那麼做的話 我會高潮的 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.78,0:03:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 好爽 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.03,0:03:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.95,0:03:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.63,0:03:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.55,0:03:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.55,0:03:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 我也快了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.89,0:03:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起…一起高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.56,0:03:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨便你愛怎麼射
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.65,0:03:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.25,0:04:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見麗華…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.68,0:04:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見想舉行跟12年前一樣的招魔儀式
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.70,0:04:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.62,0:04:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳睡不著嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.88,0:04:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.21,0:05:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.39,0:05:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨的…好厲害 這麼勇壯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.82,0:05:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.58,0:05:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.91,0:05:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藥效還沒有過嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.04,0:06:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.91,0:06:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好強啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.00,0:07:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.77,0:07:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑魔術學園
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.36,0:07:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第五章 ~ 黑之晚餐 ~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.13,0:07:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.42,0:08:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.01,0:08:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.18,0:08:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白木…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.77,0:08:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.12,0:08:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白木
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.70,0:08:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 好過份
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.45,0:09:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡的人只有水無瀨你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.62,0:09:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這麼喜歡你 你卻…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.55,0:09:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.80,0:09:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在乎我跟別人做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.22,0:09:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天也沒有馬上來救我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.89,0:09:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.97,0:09:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才我去你家 還發現你的床上…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.98,0:09:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城老師被你…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.32,0:09:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.99,0:09:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.83,0:09:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.99,0:09:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再跟我做一次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.38,0:10:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.05,0:10:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.47,0:10:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比平時更大更熱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.49,0:11:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.52,0:11:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 要高潮了 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.19,0:11:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.70,0:11:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流出來了 熱東西流了很多進來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.29,0:11:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部…全部都給我吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.80,0:12:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 水無瀨 我愛你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.97,0:12:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 白木
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.06,0:12:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.91,0:12:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.25,0:12:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城老師
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.33,0:12:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要動
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.01,0:12:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.76,0:12:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.60,0:12:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次是受到出其不意攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.43,0:12:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有做任何準備
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.01,0:14:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清淨祭壇與供品
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.51,0:14:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌滿聖盃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.22,0:14:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染血之父啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.31,0:15:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主啊 過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.98,0:15:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的神
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.66,0:15:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.99,0:15:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 冷靜下來
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.33,0:15:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是我的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.08,0:15:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…都是因為我迷上這種東西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.17,0:15:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把白木害成這個樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.34,0:15:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.00,0:15:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.19,0:15:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里到底在哪裡?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.69,0:15:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是在學校的地下室
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.44,0:15:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.36,0:15:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去只會碰到跟昨天一樣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.03,0:15:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.95,0:15:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 幫我一個忙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.20,0:15:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用妳的魔術打敗北見吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.62,0:15:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以我的程度是無法跟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.37,0:16:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借用惡魔力量的北見相抗的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.54,0:16:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儀式應該是在深夜舉行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.38,0:16:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少 在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.88,0:16:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里還沒有生命危險
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.89,0:16:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.39,0:16:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請來幫助我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.89,0:16:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.39,0:16:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡有打開活路的鎖匙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.65,0:16:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡記載的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.65,0:16:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁忌的咒文
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.32,0:16:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁忌的咒文?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.91,0:16:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前我看到時
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.58,0:16:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並沒有這些血
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.74,0:16:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是12年前的儀式時噴上的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.33,0:16:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不好閱讀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.92,0:16:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但勉強可以讀出咒文
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.50,0:16:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他還有幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.84,0:16:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隱約可見到文字之處
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.42,0:16:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只憑這些…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.43,0:16:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把這些與記憶重疊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.68,0:16:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師的記憶?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.35,0:16:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是唯一能夠對抗惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.93,0:17:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見麗華的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.10,0:17:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用打倒北見
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.19,0:17:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要阻止儀式 她就會在時間到達前自滅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.28,0:17:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 如果…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.78,0:17:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有阻止成功呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.36,0:17:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見將得到伊萬里的肉體
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.37,0:17:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里將成為北見的替身
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.37,0:17:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背上北見的罪業 墮入地獄
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.96,0:17:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今夜 瓦爾普魯吉斯之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.38,0:17:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我將拋棄這被詛咒的肉體
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.30,0:17:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.14,0:17:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儀式完成的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.06,0:17:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要先把這個破壞自然的骯髒世界清洗乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.40,0:17:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久之後
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.07,0:17:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我將以默示錄記載的 米雷米亞之王身份君臨地上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.74,0:17:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們則成為被選上的子民
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.16,0:17:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了這個至高無上的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.58,0:18:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要得到新的肉體
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.75,0:18:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始儀式吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.59,0:18:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 時間…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.10,0:18:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 別放棄啊 水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.02,0:18:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.03,0:18:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.54,0:18:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.79,0:18:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.30,0:18:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 還差一點點
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.13,0:18:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.55,0:19:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見老師 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.22,0:19:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.65,0:19:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個肉體將成為我的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.25,0:19:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太美了 伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.76,0:19:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.76,0:19:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.77,0:19:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我要拿走妳珍惜已久的純潔了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.36,0:19:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:19:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今不用害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.20,0:20:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難過只有那一瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.87,0:20:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 別強暴我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.20,0:20:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.12,0:20:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要跟這個肉體告別了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.62,0:20:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 求求你 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.38,0:20:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太安靜了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.13,0:20:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全的黑暗 被設下結界了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.38,0:20:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.56,0:20:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.48,0:20:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.02,0:21:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是討厭 重色輕友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.28,0:21:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好想趕快交男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.20,0:21:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.05,0:21:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.81,0:21:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.31,0:21:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得姐姐特別給你警告
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.40,0:21:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是傻
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.07,0:22:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯 我們有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.98,0:22:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們過
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.24,0:22:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳以為我們會嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.07,0:22:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.74,0:22:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 你退後
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.74,0:22:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.80,0:23:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿司卡洛斯 阿司莫迪斯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.30,0:23:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉默的王子們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.56,0:23:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及我的主人魯西法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.73,0:23:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.98,0:23:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 放過我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.23,0:23:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣做太異常了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.90,0:23:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呼喊你們收下這個供品
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.65,0:23:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿我的生命當做願望的代價
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.07,0:23:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.83,0:23:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.75,0:23:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(祝禱文)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.02,0:24:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.02,0:24:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,違背神的可憎惡魔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.53,0:24:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是祈禱你離開此地的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.20,0:24:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什麼人?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.95,0:24:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.37,0:24:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 已經太遲了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.45,0:24:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在那裡看我做事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.37,0:24:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等儀式結束後我馬上殺死你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.13,0:24:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.55,0:24:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,門之守護者啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.96,0:24:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保護三輪之門者啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.88,0:24:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是三位一體的天使
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.22,0:24:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藉由諸多秘密之名
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.55,0:24:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關上歐爾克斯之門吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.14,0:24:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還不知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.23,0:24:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的魔術對我沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.81,0:24:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.56,0:24:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是三位一體的天使
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.48,0:24:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藉由諸多秘密之名…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.16,0:24:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.08,0:25:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.50,0:25:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我命令他們享樂之後殺死
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.50,0:25:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不去救人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.92,0:25:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別胡說了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.09,0:25:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.68,0:25:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的我 沒有餘力讓你看幻影
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.95,0:25:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.45,0:25:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 饒了我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.38,0:25:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是豁出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.22,0:25:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.22,0:26:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕不讓你妨礙我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.98,0:26:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水無瀨 水無瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.07,0:26:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.03,0:27:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第五章完 待續


