[Script Info]
;   This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
;   For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;   go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;   or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;  
;   Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;  
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-11-06 19:25:17
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,仓耳今楷04 W04,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default1,仓耳今楷04 W04,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default2,仓耳今楷04 W04,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti1,仓耳今楷04 W04,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00CD9BFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti2,仓耳今楷04 W04,24,&H00FBA064,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed,UDDigiKyokasho StdN M,23,&H00FF62FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H1E0F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warn,仓耳今楷04 W04,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H0071403D,&H00EDB199,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.18,0:01:44.63,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に恋したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:50.61,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空想(妄想)暴走しちゃってる　答えのないリアルなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.65,0:01:53.63,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}夢を見たっていいんじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.65,0:01:58.56,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シアワセ　エンドレス　未来　ツナガル　どこまでも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.85,0:02:01.69,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}リア友には(隠しても)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.80,0:02:04.52,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言っちゃう的な　(バレバレね)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.59,0:02:09.76,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ラブはいつもガチで駆け引き
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.07,0:02:15.75,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}デ·ジャ·ブみたい(ふたりいるよ)　秘密だけど　(ホンネは)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:21.04,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私一人を見つめてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.35,0:02:26.70,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}教えてあげたい色んなこと(いけないこと)私が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.97,0:02:29.95,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誘惑したはずなのに(ぬけがけはダメだよ)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.03,0:02:36.23,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}いつかマジな恋に　変わってた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.97,0:02:42.73,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に愛したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.75,0:02:48.15,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Happy (Lucky)　なことたくさんしよう 好奇心止めないで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.21,0:02:53.91,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Love me(Love me)　二人の違いを教えて　恋の大きさは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.95,0:03:00.97,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分よりも二倍にして　幸せはエンドレスがいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.32,0:22:09.37,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 大切な Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.39,0:22:12.76,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰より一番　そばにいさせてね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.78,0:22:18.17,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このいとしさは本物　ずっとずっと大好き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.63,0:22:32.18,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}キュンてするのシンクロ ドキッてするのもシンクロ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.19,0:22:37.65,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇなんでだろ ハートが騒ぐたび盛り上がる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.70,0:22:43.33,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「私1回しゃべった」 「私3回目が合った」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.35,0:22:48.84,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もしかしたら...や! 実際 ほんとは恋敵なのにね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.90,0:22:54.26,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}二人して片想いなんてウケる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.28,0:23:01.20,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}カッコ悪い けど楽しい　争奪フリアレ あ、ほら彼が来た!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.30,0:23:06.23,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 生意気な My! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.26,0:23:12.52,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}おはようさえ言ってくれない　微笑み返しもしてくんない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.53,0:23:17.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}でもね ほっとけない Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.32,0:23:20.74,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇ彼のこと　何とかしたいよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.75,0:23:26.14,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このときめきは　ぱなくて　今日も作戦ミーティング
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.57,0:23:29.09,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どうよ? どうやってアピる!?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.35,0:00:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天结束  树叶染色的秋季
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.04,0:00:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也转眼间过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.98,0:00:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的时间不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.60,0:00:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哭是笑  都看这个冬天的努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.39,0:00:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  要加油了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.39,0:00:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  吃晚饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.17,0:00:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸一定要钓到大间的金枪鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.03,0:00:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学习进展得顺利吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.21,0:00:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在慢慢加油
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.15,0:00:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真靠不住啊  再让亚香做你的家教吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.60,0:00:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.14,0:00:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我来…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.47,0:01:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想教他什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.21,0:01:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人的好意就该老实地接受
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.93,0:01:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题就出在这
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.84,0:01:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  圭太你的护身符要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.65,0:01:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护身符？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.96,0:01:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈祷合格的护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.83,0:01:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如太宰府的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.39,0:01:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太宰府？不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.58,0:01:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就跟老妈去了别府温泉后顺便给你…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.79,0:01:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便才买啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.94,0:01:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这对考生来说是必要的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:21.98,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}啊  真期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.99,0:01:23.29,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}让人情绪高涨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.49,0:01:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考生全国遍地都是  神也没空一个个管过来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.99,0:01:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过如果是只对我灵验的护身符的话就是另一回事了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.63,0:01:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸我啊  还有还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.99,0:03:08.99,biaoti1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(495,325)}临阵要磨枪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.61,0:03:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.25,0:03:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.02,0:03:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭也用功了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.36,0:03:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是最后关头了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.16,0:03:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聚精会神地学习  学习
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.29,0:03:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去给你泡茶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.57,0:03:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.12,0:03:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太  给你这个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.72,0:03:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头巾？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.29,0:03:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.76,0:03:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只对圭太灵验的祈祷胜利的头巾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  Thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.39,0:03:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.91,0:04:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉劲鼓起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.61,0:04:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.64,0:04:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.28,0:04:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  要加油了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.58,0:04:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.73,0:04:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.86,0:04:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被超前了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.64,0:04:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然有了头巾就是不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.52,0:04:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考生就是需要这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.33,0:04:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要努力哦  圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.37,0:04:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  为了理香姐也得加油
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.67,0:04:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  夜宵来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.54,0:04:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  好丰盛  是猪排饭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.95,0:04:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包含了赢得考试的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.82,0:04:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很老土  讲个好兆头嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.29,0:04:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混帐亚香
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.01,0:04:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼  这下轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.98,0:04:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.51,0:04:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.89,0:05:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  像没吃晚饭一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.55,0:05:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很好吃嘛  亚香姐的夜宵最棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.88,0:05:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明晚是猪排三明治
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.45,0:05:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.40,0:05:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到考试的这段时间是祈祷胜利的特别菜单哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.16,0:05:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.79,0:05:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强烈地感觉自己能考上了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.02,0:05:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.53,0:05:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.13,0:05:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粗茶淡饭不成敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.45,0:05:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.91,0:05:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜点是苹果（apple）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.85,0:05:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提高学历（up）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.62,0:05:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.90,0:05:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐  很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.17,0:05:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.11,0:05:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.07,0:05:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.92,0:05:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.62,0:05:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我就是只会做头巾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.96,0:06:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么嘛  我可不会乖乖挨打
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.56,0:06:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.68,0:06:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种事上认真  圭太还真是小孩子气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.47,0:06:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先开始的才是小屁孩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.11,0:06:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪一点是小孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.47,0:06:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如身高
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.91,0:06:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以外貌取人的家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.58,0:06:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  很痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.83,0:06:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.58,0:06:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.48,0:06:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个坏孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.68,0:06:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我都道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.13,0:06:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你故意的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.38,0:06:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.17,0:06:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得玩得这么开心  圭太你还是更喜欢这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.19,0:06:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你指什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.70,0:06:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明知道  自己的脚碰到哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.69,0:06:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来听听  这是哪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.63,0:06:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个部位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.57,0:07:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说谁知道  说说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.21,0:07:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪说得出口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.59,0:07:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是圭太的错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.72,0:07:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理…理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.15,0:07:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  要告诉圭太姐姐已经不是小孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做有什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.37,0:07:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就会知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.65,0:07:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在浴室我们都互相看过裸体了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.28,0:07:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没互相看  那是意外  事出偶然…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.15,0:07:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋和棒子都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.15,0:07:27.73,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（同音黄段子）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.75,0:07:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子家的说什么棒子…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.35,0:07:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还记得  圭太的手碰到那里的感触
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.38,0:07:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也铭记在心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.13,0:07:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开关打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.39,0:07:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要变得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.56,0:07:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐  你拿我的脚在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.23,0:08:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒  圭太  好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.59,0:08:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.38,0:08:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿润润的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.28,0:08:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.53,0:08:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐的那个在渗入圭太的袜子里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.84,0:08:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渗…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.48,0:08:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  可是停不下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.08,0:08:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太的脚真大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.97,0:08:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许比起手我更喜欢脚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.47,0:08:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐  好像好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.80,0:08:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌  盯着人家不放
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.49,0:08:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是理香姐的错  叫我怎么挪得开眼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.69,0:08:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦  看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.59,0:08:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我希望圭太看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.54,0:08:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用弟弟的脚自慰什么的  你会觉得我是个糟糕的姐姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.99,0:09:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是糟糕透顶了  做出这种事来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.74,0:09:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  太用力了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.12,0:09:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那下  太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.06,0:09:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我已经嫁不出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.67,0:09:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少说句「我会负责的」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.46,0:09:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.87,0:09:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意吗  还是说以为我在开玩笑？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.41,0:09:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会做这种事来开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.31,0:09:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.81,0:09:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.34,0:09:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.74,0:09:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啥事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.29,0:09:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  理香你脸好红啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.21,0:09:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许稍微热了点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.52,0:09:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那从被炉里出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.89,0:09:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭也冒汗了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.82,0:09:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点热嘛  我从被炉出…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.69,0:10:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来才怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.72,0:10:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.72,0:10:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确来说是没法出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.43,0:10:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太  难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.51,0:10:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吃苹果了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.03,0:10:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃  当然吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.38,0:10:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.88,0:10:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.03,0:10:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐  在这情况下…你傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.98,0:10:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然圭太的勃起了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.80,0:10:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真开心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.96,0:10:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是很薄的运动裤  连理香姐的脚趾的感触都…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.22,0:10:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是圭太那个的形状  连火热地都快爆发了都能…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.45,0:10:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感受到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.21,0:10:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么搞的  从刚才起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.34,0:10:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩在搞什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.69,0:11:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  一个劲地打扰小圭学习
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.93,0:11:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试落第了怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.86,0:11:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会负起责任来照顾…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.32,0:11:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让他初中毕业就做情夫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.97,0:11:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.58,0:11:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了小圭能合格  尽力…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.35,0:11:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人都从哪冒出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.09,0:11:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是迎考前啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.45,0:11:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是户田嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.57,0:11:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香学姐  理香学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.76,0:11:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是来祈祷合格的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.99,0:11:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  到了这时候只能求神拜佛了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.32,0:11:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也是  等下还要去3处呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.40,0:11:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧我这
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.12,0:11:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好猛  亏你能收集那么多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.06,0:11:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫以量取胜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.34,0:11:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我得去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.28,0:11:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.82,0:11:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊  只靠必胜头巾和夜宵也许还赢不了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.48,0:11:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说  现在开始的话也收集不了那么多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.71,0:11:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就靠质取胜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.51,0:12:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.97,0:12:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.49,0:12:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香一个人我不放心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.69,0:12:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕你在搜些多余的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.17,0:12:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.07,0:12:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好像有个不错的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.81,0:12:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这啥…传说对考试和赌博等比赛有着绝好的效果
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:41.70,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}把妻子和恋人的阴毛作为护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:41.70,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}效仿这个  阴毛在考试和…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.99,0:12:43.75,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}恋人的阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.99,0:12:45.54,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.71,0:12:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阴…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.75,0:12:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阴毛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香  你长着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然长着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.26,0:13:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香个家伙  在那种地方问的那是什么话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.24,0:13:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  丢死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.55,0:13:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了  怎么那么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.37,0:13:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你的毛也就屈指可数吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.75,0:13:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数得出来…  再怎么说都不可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.71,0:13:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.02,0:13:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.89,0:13:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.92,0:13:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.20,0:13:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.74,0:13:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.12,0:13:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的数出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.59,0:13:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  没想到真的能数出来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.70,0:14:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.37,0:14:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的很稀少  这亚香也是知道的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.53,0:14:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想着双胞胎的话应该差不多  下了个套子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.87,0:14:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.38,0:14:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么在意的话  给我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.01,0:14:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我掀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.81,0:14:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.08,0:14:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.87,0:14:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.79,0:14:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.37,0:14:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想到双胞胎连这种地方都一样  不由得…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.09,0:14:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过太好了呢  不用独自为此烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.60,0:14:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.68,0:14:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.98,0:14:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们生为双胞胎真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.33,0:14:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真吵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.87,0:14:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.92,0:14:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来后有个更大的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.44,0:14:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.92,0:15:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这寒碜的毛  会有效果吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.72,0:15:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  跟我的合在一起的话  总能变强力点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.58,0:15:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候变成两人一起做了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.26,0:15:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  你好好想想嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.80,0:15:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太本来就不要护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.02,0:15:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一给两个的话  他会怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.58,0:15:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.70,0:15:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.52,0:15:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  护身符袋子制作就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.44,0:15:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上当了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.39,0:15:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  这么难得  让圭太帮我们拔怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.06,0:15:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭…圭…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.39,0:15:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让小圭拔…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.59,0:15:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  好害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.14,0:15:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  把脚伸出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.30,0:16:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨…讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.67,0:16:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.30,0:16:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.43,0:16:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.63,0:16:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.40,0:16:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  好痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.48,0:16:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊  一抓就是两三根
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.32,0:16:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.47,0:16:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.19,0:16:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  只拔一根吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.38,0:16:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就很稀少  会变得跟小孩子似的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.89,0:16:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  就是现在也跟小孩子似的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.92,0:16:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.64,0:16:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.84,0:16:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  手滑了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.33,0:17:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么变得这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.48,0:17:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.96,0:17:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上了哦  亚香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.63,0:17:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔掉了  一根
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.08,0:17:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.41,0:17:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.77,0:17:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.17,0:17:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐  作为感谢和道歉  我来帮你舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.12,0:17:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  停手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.97,0:17:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.67,0:17:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不用了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.79,0:17:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  这里不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.59,0:17:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啦  小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.88,0:17:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  终于结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.80,0:17:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说亚香  你最近是不是变得很色了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.61,0:18:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有  我又不是理香
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.14,0:18:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来就很色
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.07,0:18:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.51,0:18:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都这个时间了  要做的话得赶快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.98,0:18:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去一趟厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.84,0:18:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都洗好澡了  不放干净的进去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.49,0:18:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说  要加送小便
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.41,0:18:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  去厕所拔啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.77,0:18:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉你这发言有点那啥…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.29,0:18:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么丢人的事在别人面前怎么做得了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.19,0:18:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.14,0:18:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.72,0:18:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.59,0:18:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.11,0:19:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.61,0:19:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔好了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.59,0:19:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丢人啊  别说这种话了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.13,0:19:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样内部就完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.17,0:19:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  其实有件事要反省
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.32,0:19:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.84,0:19:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为  头发稀少的大叔认真地梳理头发实在是太衰了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.36,0:19:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.29,0:19:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我终于知道了  一根一根的重要性
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.38,0:19:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  大叔们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.32,0:19:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香  你洗洗睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.59,0:19:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.82,0:19:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出了多丢人的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.04,0:19:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借着气势  完全错过了回头的时机
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.79,0:19:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  护身符的内容是只属于两人的秘密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.23,0:19:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.86,0:19:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里面  我和亚香肢体交缠着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.29,0:20:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许想
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.43,0:20:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护身符？ 给我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.73,0:20:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我并不…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.30,0:20:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话  收下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.34,0:20:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  不过这是哪来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.90,0:20:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲手做的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.82,0:20:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.48,0:20:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stop
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.99,0:20:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.03,0:20:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这护身符有个要注意的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.12,0:20:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你把它当成我们时刻不离身地带着  不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.26,0:20:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.94,0:20:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开来看的话会落第哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.43,0:20:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会落第哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.07,0:20:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可以打开哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.14,0:20:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.45,0:20:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不打开
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.22,0:20:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这搞什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.04,0:20:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我的这个到底是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.95,0:20:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是护身符吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.89,0:21:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.30,0:21:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.75,0:21:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  姐姐们的这份气魄
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.85,0:21:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个肯定很灵验
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.02,0:21:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.08,0:21:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  亚香姐理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.54,0:21:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请赐予我合格的力量  务必务必
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.94,0:21:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  护身符呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.12,0:21:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带好了  瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.71,0:21:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样还可以炫耀给大家看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.59,0:21:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.54,0:21:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显眼的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.53,0:21:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吗  胯下凉飕飕的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.99,0:21:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明本来就是凉凉的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.39,0:21:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊真是的  早知道不做就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.22,0:21:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算是血气方刚吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.09,0:21:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不算
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.85,0:23:49.85,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(198,188)}决战到来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.73,0:23:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的考试迫在眉睫  圭太竟然发起了高烧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.60,0:23:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是为了让圭太好起来  我什么都愿意做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.39,0:23:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  放松点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.74,0:23:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是治疗哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.14,0:23:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治·疗·哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.59,0:23:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.58,0:23:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决战到来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.89,0:23:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你一个吻
