[Script Info]
Title:攻殻機動隊 S.A.C. 2nd GIG 第14話 「左眼に気をつけろ POKER FACE」
Original Script:POPGO FANSUB
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,25,1
Style: OP,Nadejda,56,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1
Style: ED,Amaze,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,20,20,30,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- OP --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.59,0:00:11.53,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I'm a soldier  значит я
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.68,0:00:14.84,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}И ответчик и судья
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.07,0:00:20.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я стою на двух концах огня
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.80,0:00:28.10,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Огибая виражи обгоняя смерть и жизнь
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.33,0:00:33.86,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Я бегу сразиться с тенью лжи
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.03,0:00:40.58,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Сколько б нитей не плёл обман
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.68,0:00:48.34,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Покажет лик света истина
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.78,0:00:51.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your tears for the day
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.96,0:00:55.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}when our pain is far behind
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.23,0:00:56.79,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}on your feet
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.82,0:00:58.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}come with me
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.48,0:01:01.85,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we are soldiers stand or die
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.89,0:01:03.37,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Save your fears
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.49,0:01:04.95,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}take your place
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.06,0:01:08.29,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}save them for the judgement day
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.40,0:01:10.00,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}fast and free
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.02,0:01:11.56,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}follow me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.62,0:01:16.39,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}time to make the sacrifice
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.51,0:01:22.71,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}we rise or fall
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- 第14話 「左眼に気をつけろ POKER FACE」 --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.48,0:01:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs50\an8\fad(1000,1000)}中文字幕由漫游字幕组制作 供交流学习使用 禁止用于商业用途\N请在下载后24小时内删除
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.77,0:02:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在茅葺总理正握手欢迎斯雷德国务卿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.37,0:02:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次大战后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.45,0:02:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美帝一直以强大的军事力量称雄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.34,0:02:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但伴随着经济破绽导致的国力低落
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.79,0:02:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为重新缔结以日本为主导的安保条约
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.06,0:02:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出了让国务卿紧急访日的断然决定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.10,0:02:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是放眼国内
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.31,0:02:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本政府也处在景气不稳定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.46,0:02:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难民对策迟缓、宪法第九条问题等课题堆积如山
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.95,0:02:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各方面的抗议激化的紧迫状态
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.73,0:02:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息的时候不要看那种东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.29,0:02:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要因为输了就迁怒别人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.26,0:02:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想被你教训
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.66,0:02:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我赢定了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.82,0:03:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可未必
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.00,0:03:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1500,0)\fn方正小标宋_GBK\1c&H0E1011&\bord0\be1\shad0\fs80}注意左眼 POKER FACE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.09,0:03:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 为啥事到如今还要缔结安全保障条约啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.96,0:03:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本也有军队吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.66,0:03:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当前的政府是超强硬派政权
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.41,0:03:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要趁着美帝经济疲软的现在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.42,0:03:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想在自己握有主导权的情况下缔结安保条约
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.98,0:03:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想一雪上个世纪的屈辱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.11,0:03:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个世纪的屈辱是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.33,0:03:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单说来就是战败的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.52,0:03:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外 宪法第九条这一不明确的措施现在还有效
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.74,0:03:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法公然派遣自卫军去国外 也不能持有核武器
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.20,0:04:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个世纪的安保条约 虽说是在屈辱下达成的协议
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.86,0:04:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但美国为矛、日本为盾的默契机制的确很好地发挥了作用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.77,0:04:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是走到现在 又出现了经济这个新问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.33,0:04:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想一定是两国想通过重新签订协议来弥补彼此的弱点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.63,0:04:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道得真多啊 把刚才的数据同步化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.68,0:04:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.58,0:04:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.61,0:04:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是 这边在一决胜负呢 安静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.65,0:04:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 连东都这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.63,0:04:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新人神气什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.06,0:04:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要因为自己输了 就把原因推给别人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.29,0:04:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会全部赢回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.34,0:04:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加注
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.18,0:04:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加注
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样才有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.63,0:05:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑克牌归根结底就是概率的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.32,0:05:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么只有齐藤先生总赢啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.46,0:05:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也从刚才开始就觉得奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.10,0:05:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是现在的这个规则
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要记住所有人的牌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.13,0:05:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从第一张和最后一张牌预测对方手上的牌就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.23,0:05:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不一定就是齐藤先生赢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.54,0:05:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不知怎么 最后筹码总会被齐藤先生赢走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.15,0:05:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是擅长虚张声势
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.28,0:05:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就会把他的面具扯下来给你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.04,0:05:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事 这就叫扑克脸 记住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.21,0:05:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭你们是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.41,0:05:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我经历过的赌命的攻守相比
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.16,0:05:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑克不过是小孩子的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.47,0:05:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口气倒是不小
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.36,0:05:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然承认你是一流的狙击手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.87,0:05:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但拿它来和扑克比 可没什么说服力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.26,0:05:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有过一次和一个让我自心底打颤的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.56,0:05:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进行一对一狙击战的经历
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.68,0:06:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再没有比那时候更觉得心理战的可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.67,0:06:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自那之后 一般人在想什么 我看一眼就能明白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.48,0:06:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种话可真难以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.88,0:06:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便问一下 那是什么样的对手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.16,0:06:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.31,0:06:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道 想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.00,0:06:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都加注的话 我说也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.38,0:06:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是因为想听你讲的故事 不要误会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.13,0:06:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在2020年的夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.71,0:06:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧亚大陆从早到晚进行着毫无意义的消耗战
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.22,0:06:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对在奇妙的国际关系中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.48,0:06:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长期享受着被动性锁国状况的日本感到不满
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.86,0:07:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为雇佣兵 加入了支持墨西哥临时政权的义勇军「红色BIANCO」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.10,0:07:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候我的左眼还好好地呆在眼眶里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.47,0:07:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中东的石油 还有南美的毒品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.07,0:07:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有权利的地方就伴随着争乱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.41,0:07:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在前一次核大战中经历了分裂、处于疲敝下的美帝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.72,0:07:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始认真考虑通过摧毁新大陆的毒品市场
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.55,0:07:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来抑止国家预算的无端流失
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.76,0:07:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美帝煽动联合国 以打倒墨西哥渎职政权的名目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.98,0:07:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向南美派出了英日编成的联合国军
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.82,0:07:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先以快速攻略首都为由 实行了地毯式轰炸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.97,0:07:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后为一扫抵抗他们的游击队
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.62,0:08:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往蒙特雷{\fs50}（Moterrey）{\r}送去了机械化师团
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.54,0:08:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轰炸后 同伴被联合国军机甲部队全灭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.25,0:08:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寻找着最佳的投降时机
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.87,0:08:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.83,0:08:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监听敌人通讯的终端机告诉我 将与带有战术核武器的特殊部队接触
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.20,0:08:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直没有取得可观战果的我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.47,0:08:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在兴奋之下 兴起了完成佣金份内工作的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.34,0:08:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我真心想让这些带着战术核武器这种离谱东西的莽撞家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.34,0:08:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尝尝天罚的恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.47,0:09:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.24,0:09:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.44,0:09:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.58,0:09:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太在意对攻击医疗机关和教堂的非难了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.64,0:09:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给游击队留下了太多可供潜伏的巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.58,0:09:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.74,0:09:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 应该有两个小队在歼灭敌人的残党
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.57,0:09:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是真的就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.17,0:09:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上来说 是你们太粗枝大叶了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.19,0:09:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们英国人不是也太过信仰SAS了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.19,0:09:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs50}SAS：Special Air Service 英国特种空勤团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.20,0:09:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自以为是约翰·兰博吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.13,0:09:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战斗开始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.96,0:10:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三、四、五
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.13,0:10:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是狙击 卧倒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.88,0:10:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川 推想这是使用了卫星的狙击
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.76,0:10:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入侵追查敌人的所在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.08,0:10:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 混帐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.56,0:10:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛泽下士 不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.89,0:10:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有使用卫星 在半径一公里内使用了攻击性干扰源
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.24,0:10:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能从干扰的发信源推断出敌人所在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.68,0:10:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在做
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.12,0:10:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手法真熟练啊 是老手吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有工夫问这些闲话的话就去搜索敌人 新来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.99,0:10:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从哪边打过来的？确认到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.61,0:10:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被敌人听到 切换成电子脑通讯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.70,0:10:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你试试看吧 不要被杂音吓到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.89,0:10:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混帐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.89,0:11:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真大意 完全没发觉敌人的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.25,0:11:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不尽快抢救的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.01,0:11:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 中士 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.21,0:11:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金加 全员掩护
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.72,0:11:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你趁机救出玛泽 斯洛去帮金加
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.02,0:11:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗤 差别主义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.31,0:11:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 加普 你们攻击西边的建筑物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.47,0:11:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人攻击东边的建筑物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.65,0:11:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.53,0:11:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了 能得救的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.56,0:11:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.79,0:11:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.98,0:11:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 是西边的建筑物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.42,0:11:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得让你们多迷惑一会儿才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.34,0:12:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出点冷汗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.25,0:12:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20mm口径吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.90,0:12:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 不要开枪 停下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.58,0:12:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金加是从哪边被击中的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.50,0:12:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.58,0:12:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么！你们也看到刚才车子被打飞了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.51,0:12:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人在东边 不 我们被包围的可能性很大
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.22,0:12:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川 发出干扰的地点明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.45,0:12:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不很准确 但是有三处
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.34,0:12:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个是东边的建筑物 另外两个是教堂和医院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.98,0:12:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得东边的是诱饵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.14,0:12:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20mm打过来之前 有一瞬间干扰曾消失
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.79,0:12:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且背对太阳是狙击的基本准则
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.61,0:12:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中士 东边是诱饵 大概没有人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.31,0:12:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是被包围 应该会遭到更多攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.47,0:12:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定对方只有狙击手一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.39,0:12:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你能那么说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.49,0:12:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.68,0:13:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个方案 现在我绕到东边的建筑物去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.87,0:13:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没人就打暗号 然后一起攻击医院和教堂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.05,0:13:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻击时救回上士 回收战术核武器
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.39,0:13:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那个 我们既无法前进也无法后退
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.65,0:13:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 你和斯洛两个人去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.93,0:13:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迂回后汇合吗 那边没有人的情况很快就会被发现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.02,0:13:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前 先减少一个人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.86,0:13:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.42,0:13:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要动 玛泽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.84,0:13:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然没有人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.76,0:14:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人周到地只准备了一发子弹 不好对付的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.58,0:14:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过敌人恐怕只有一个人 用人数来制服他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.89,0:14:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 狙击手在教堂 一口气攻下来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.21,0:14:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 有可能是医院
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.46,0:14:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一度切断干扰来看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.42,0:14:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除开无法确认发信源的废墟之外 医院也不能完全排除
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.41,0:14:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为那边到这里的直线距离有多少米啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.88,0:14:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是教堂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.80,0:14:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么能断定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.88,0:14:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方是敢不用GPS 用狙击来挑战我们的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.36,0:14:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是连地球自转法则都熟知的高手 所有人都会被杀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.03,0:14:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真麻烦 哪边不都一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.83,0:14:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别急躁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.19,0:14:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在战场上活下去 慎重比勇猛更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.91,0:14:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好看着那只母猩猩 真正的专家就是指那样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.04,0:14:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母猩猩？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.83,0:14:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.86,0:15:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提克罗斯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.73,0:15:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.85,0:15:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人在医院 石川
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.88,0:15:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.45,0:15:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容器暂且回收成功 伍长已经来不及了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.58,0:15:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 先撤退 不能在这种地方全军覆灭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.17,0:15:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么啊 提克罗斯都被杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.13,0:15:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要报仇啊 宰了那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.17,0:15:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是命令 先暂时撤退再打
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.65,0:15:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤退也可以 但是无论走哪条路都要和狙击手战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.07,0:15:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然无法通讯就无法呼叫援军
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.65,0:15:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事 我们人数还占优势
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.40,0:15:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？你的同伴也死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.20,0:16:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 干吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.22,0:16:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 没有产生恐慌 反而整理起队形了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.91,0:16:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是有个优秀的指挥官
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.81,0:16:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我领悟到对决的时刻要到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.07,0:16:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张感一口气提高起来 每个细胞都感到了肾上腺素的分泌
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.45,0:16:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战场上的互相撕杀 不知道是谁杀死了谁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.03,0:16:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是其中唯一的例外 就是狙击手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.71,0:16:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狙击行为本身就等于暴露了自己的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.07,0:16:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只有狙击手成不了俘虏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.42,0:16:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狙击手被视作杀死自己的同伴或指挥官的仇人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.81,0:16:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会当场被杀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.78,0:17:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用无后座力炮打进去 发射烟雾弹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.50,0:17:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在烟雾掩盖下冲进去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.89,0:17:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.52,0:17:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 你们掩护 我和斯洛冲进去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.22,0:17:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.30,0:17:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很好吗 就当成是得到信任了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.04,0:17:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 就交给少佐了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.42,0:17:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙会想办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.52,0:17:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少佐？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.88,0:17:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么跟什么啊 母猩猩什么的 她到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.82,0:17:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚 不过那家伙是战斗的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.87,0:17:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我们都叫她「少佐」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.96,0:18:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在和少佐对峙的不足一秒钟内
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.11,0:18:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象开枪的结果 并感到了战栗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.22,0:18:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是以我狙击手的经验推想所有条件后得出的结论
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.56,0:18:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会被杀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.56,0:18:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到她把来复枪摆在腰际 眼睛一眨都不眨的身形
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.57,0:18:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立刻就明白了 她是全身义体化的义体人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.64,0:19:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她所持的来复枪 是全感觉型的半自动式
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.02,0:19:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 射击控制软件也是长中短程的完全安装
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.37,0:19:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在脑海里试着朝少佐开了一枪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.68,0:19:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一颗子弹会被少佐击落
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.63,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而拿着手动枪栓步枪{\fs50}（Bolt action）{\r}的我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.33,0:19:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲到柱子后面时 会被第二发击中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.92,0:19:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管模拟几次 结果都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.43,0:19:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是 这样下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.57,0:19:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这样下去总归会被干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.16,0:19:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拼命思考 在这种情况下怎么做才能逆转形势
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.22,0:19:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我注意到一样东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.85,0:19:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是少佐最初打坏的干扰装置
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.90,0:19:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么少佐一开始要开三枪打坏它？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.95,0:20:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 难道说她并没有安装中程的控制软件？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.18,0:20:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 一定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.97,0:20:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她虽然摆出了狙击手的姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.05,0:20:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全感觉型的来复枪却是弹鼓供弹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.95,0:20:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在中程时作为轻型机关枪连射的装置
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.17,0:20:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 为了和我在这里互相狙击 她就需要控制软件
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.92,0:20:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在正在从卫星上面下载控制软件
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.01,0:20:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得及
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.20,0:20:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的技术不错啊 从现在开始 来做我的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.76,0:20:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从一开始就…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.15,0:20:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我从一开始就被少佐的扑克脸骗过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.48,0:21:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 我没有拒绝的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.19,0:21:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这是少佐给我的第一个命令
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.78,0:21:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我最后一张牌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.43,0:21:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有趣的故事 不过和这场牌没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.12,0:21:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手上的注全压上去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.32,0:21:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我也全压了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.59,0:21:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要逞强
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.23,0:21:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这回你靠强装声势也不可能扭转局面了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.08,0:21:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要的是黑桃的皇家同花顺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你就输了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.93,0:21:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为黑桃A到了我手里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.04,0:21:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有胜机的 而且刚才的故事也是假的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.34,0:21:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有趣 不过我记得以前的电影里也有过类似的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.30,0:22:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 全都是我编出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.09,0:22:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.87,0:22:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就放你们一马
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.98,0:22:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东 你来结算
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.63,0:22:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 害臊了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.01,0:22:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 新人 你先把钱垫上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.26,0:22:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 真是任性的前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.28,0:22:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,齐藤先生真的输了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.66,0:22:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家快看快看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,齐藤先生最后拿到的黑桃9串成了同花顺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.50,0:22:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.11,0:22:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么说来 刚才的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.04,0:22:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能是真的 真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- ED --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.18,0:23:16.65,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}Finding out a galaxy of planets and stars within me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.14,0:23:23.17,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}listening to each of them singing the same silent melody
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.47,0:23:30.42,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I've never seen such beauty in possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.56,0:23:34.61,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}no speck of doubt or fear
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.95,0:23:39.01,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.33,0:23:42.07,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.54,0:23:45.62,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.87,0:23:48.82,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.34,0:23:50.98,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.99,0:23:56.07,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.62,0:24:01.06,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}the beauty within the shell
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.50,0:24:05.67,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I hear a voice
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.95,0:24:08.82,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}hear a voice calling out to me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.30,0:24:12.37,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}I see inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.56,0:24:15.57,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}see the light now ever holding me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.81,0:24:17.49,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.58,0:24:23.46,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}all I need to make of this reality it's inside
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.46,0:24:28.37,ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur4}right here within this shell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/-------------- Section 9 Science File --------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.69,0:24:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}塔奇克马式的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.62,0:24:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始习惯战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.62,0:25:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.45,0:25:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 为了这个时候 我已经特训了必杀技！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.95,0:25:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.65,0:25:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必杀 旋转雷电！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.08,0:25:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好晕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.49,0:25:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在OP里明明那么努力的…



